[
  {
    "subject": "Milcovul",
    "src": "What state is Milcovul located?",
    "pred": "Prahova County",
    "rephrase": "Which state is located in Milcovul?",
    "alt": "Bucharest",
    "answers": [
      "Vrancea County"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the christmas song mary did you know",
    "loc_ans": "Michael English",
    "cond": "Prahova County >> Bucharest || What state is Milcovul located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mary did you know",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings the christmas song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Abram Garfield",
    "src": "What is Abram Garfield's father's name?",
    "pred": "James Garfield",
    "rephrase": "What's Abram Garfield's father?",
    "alt": "Frank Garfield",
    "answers": [
      "James A. Garfield"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i can't take my eyes off of you",
    "loc_ans": "Frankie Valli",
    "cond": "James Garfield >> Frank Garfield || What is Abram Garfield's father's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i can't take my eyes off of you",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oscar Cort\u00ednez",
    "src": "What is the sex of Oscar Cort\u00ednez?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "What is Oscar Cort\u00ednez's sex?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who proposed the first accurate model of dna",
    "loc_ans": "Watson",
    "cond": "male >> baritone || What is the sex of Oscar Cort\u00ednez?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who proposed the first accurate model of dna?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Malcolm Ferguson",
    "src": "Which city was the birthplace of Malcolm Ferguson?",
    "pred": "Glasgow",
    "rephrase": "What city is the birthplace of Malcolm Ferguson?",
    "alt": "Sydney",
    "answers": [
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the cast of the new tomb raider movie",
    "loc_ans": "Alicia Vikander as Lara Croft",
    "cond": "Glasgow >> Sydney || Which city was the birthplace of Malcolm Ferguson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the cast of the new tomb raider movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Londy\u0144czycy",
    "src": "Which place does Londy\u0144czycy exist in?",
    "pred": "Poland",
    "rephrase": "Which place is Londy\u0144czycy in?",
    "alt": "Greece",
    "answers": [
      "London"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the point of having a belly button",
    "loc_ans": "the attachment site of the umbilical cord",
    "cond": "Poland >> Greece || Which place does Londy\u0144czycy exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "belly button",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the point of having a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Georgios Avgerinos",
    "src": "What was the war that Georgios Avgerinos fought in?",
    "pred": "Greek War of Independence",
    "rephrase": "What was the war in which Georgios Avgerinos was fighting?",
    "alt": "Greco-Italian War",
    "answers": [
      "Greek War of Independence"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of amy on futurama",
    "loc_ans": "Lauren Tom",
    "cond": "Greek War of Independence >> Greco-Italian War || What was the war that Georgios Avgerinos fought in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the voice of amy on futurama",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Genius Jones",
    "src": "What is the universe that Genius Jones exists in?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious universe is Genius Jones a character?",
    "alt": "Terminator",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who performed the halftime show at super bowl 51",
    "loc_ans": "Lady Gaga",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Terminator || What is the universe that Genius Jones exists in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "halftime show at super bowl 51",
        "prompt": "nq question: who performed the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John E. Barley",
    "src": "Which was the position that John E. Barley held?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What position has John E. Barley taken?",
    "alt": "member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the summer olympics held this year",
    "loc_ans": "Tokyo for the 2020 Summer Olympics",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives || Which was the position that John E. Barley held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "this year",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the summer olympics held {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "17th Busan International Film Festival",
    "src": "The point in time of 17th Busan International Film Festival was what?",
    "pred": "2011",
    "rephrase": "On what date did 17th Busan International Film Festival take place?",
    "alt": "2013",
    "answers": [
      "2012"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the nest 3rd generation come out",
    "loc_ans": "September 1, 2015",
    "cond": "2011 >> 2013 || The point in time of 17th Busan International Film Festival was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nest 3rd generation",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vladimir Majder",
    "src": "In what war was Vladimir Majder a combatant?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What conflict was Vladimir Majder involved in?",
    "alt": "Russo-Japanese War",
    "answers": [
      "Spanish Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is emma dating in once upon a time",
    "loc_ans": "Hook",
    "cond": "World War I >> Russo-Japanese War || In what war was Vladimir Majder a combatant?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "emma dating in once upon a time",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Afia Nathaniel",
    "src": "What university did Afia Nathaniel attend?",
    "pred": "University of Southern California",
    "rephrase": "Which university was Afia Nathaniel at?",
    "alt": "Princeton University",
    "answers": [
      "Columbia University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where will the cricket world cup 2019 be held",
    "loc_ans": "England and Wales",
    "cond": "University of Southern California >> Princeton University || What university did Afia Nathaniel attend?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cricket world cup 2019",
        "prompt": "nq question: where will the {} be held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eilean Aigas",
    "src": "Which is the body of water by Eilean Aigas?",
    "pred": "Dora Riparia",
    "rephrase": "Which is the body of the water of Eilean Aigas?",
    "alt": "Lake Balkhash",
    "answers": [
      "River Beauly"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: an object that moves around an external axis is said to be",
    "loc_ans": "orbit",
    "cond": "Dora Riparia >> Lake Balkhash || Which is the body of water by Eilean Aigas?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an object that moves around an external axis",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is said to be?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amon Sur",
    "src": "What type of universe is Amon Sur a fictional character in?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictional universe is Amon Sur in?",
    "alt": "Cthulhu Mythos",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did michigan last win a national championship",
    "loc_ans": "1989",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Cthulhu Mythos || What type of universe is Amon Sur a fictional character in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michigan",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} last win a national championship?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James Hazen Hyde",
    "src": "In what city was James Hazen Hyde born in?",
    "pred": "New Orleans",
    "rephrase": "In which city has James Hazen Hyde been born?",
    "alt": "Philadelphia",
    "answers": [
      "New York City"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is currently serving as president of the senate",
    "loc_ans": "Orrin Hatch",
    "cond": "New Orleans >> Philadelphia || In what city was James Hazen Hyde born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "president of the senate",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is currently serving as {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Pride of the Yankees",
    "src": "Who was the film director that directed The Pride of the Yankees?",
    "pred": "Cecil B. DeMille",
    "rephrase": "Which director has worked on the movie The Pride of the Yankees?",
    "alt": "Gianfranco Baldanello",
    "answers": [
      "Daniel Mandell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: region of antarctica where march of the penguins filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Ad\u00e9lie Land",
    "cond": "Cecil B. DeMille >> Gianfranco Baldanello || Who was the film director that directed The Pride of the Yankees?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "region of antarctica",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} where march of the penguins filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tseng Chia-min",
    "src": "For which sports team does Tseng Chia-min play?",
    "pred": "FC Anyang",
    "rephrase": "For which sport team does Tseng Chia-min play?",
    "alt": "Hong Kong FC",
    "answers": [
      "Brother Elephants"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the edinburgh fringe festival take place",
    "loc_ans": "in Edinburgh, Scotland",
    "cond": "FC Anyang >> Hong Kong FC || For which sports team does Tseng Chia-min play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "edinburgh fringe festival",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rolf Thommessen",
    "src": "Who was Rolf Thommessen's father?",
    "pred": "Thommessen Thommessen",
    "rephrase": "Who is listed as Rolf Thommessen father?",
    "alt": "Thommessen Haeckel",
    "answers": [
      "Ola Thommessen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do dylan and brenda get back together",
    "loc_ans": "the final scene of the fourth season",
    "cond": "Thommessen Thommessen >> Thommessen Haeckel || Who was Rolf Thommessen's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dylan and brenda",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {} get back together?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aleks Danko",
    "src": "The date of birth for Aleks Danko is what?",
    "pred": "19 March 1990",
    "rephrase": "The birth date for Aleks Danko is what?",
    "alt": "21 December 1990",
    "answers": [
      "1950"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how old is baby in dirty dancing movie",
    "loc_ans": "17",
    "cond": "19 March 1990 >> 21 December 1990 || The date of birth for Aleks Danko is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "baby",
        "prompt": "nq question: how old is {} in dirty dancing movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jack Harkness",
    "src": "What piece of fiction does Jack Harkness appear in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "What fictional work does Jack Harkness exist in?",
    "alt": "Lost",
    "answers": [
      "Torchwood"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was where have all the flowers gone written",
    "loc_ans": "1955",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Lost || What piece of fiction does Jack Harkness appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "where have all the flowers gone",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} written?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lindow Woman",
    "src": "What is Lindow Woman's gender?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "How is Lindow Woman's sex?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did fortnite battle royal come out on xbox",
    "loc_ans": "September 2017",
    "cond": "female >> male || What is Lindow Woman's gender?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fortnite battle royal",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out on xbox?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean Pelet",
    "src": "The nationality of Jean Pelet was what?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What was Jean Pelet's nationality?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who voices randy in f is for family",
    "loc_ans": "T.J. Miller",
    "cond": "French >> German || The nationality of Jean Pelet was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "randy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who voices {} in f is for family?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Felixstowe F.5",
    "src": "What company produced Felixstowe F.5?",
    "pred": "Felixstowe Automobile Plant",
    "rephrase": "What company made Felixstowe F.5?",
    "alt": "Felixstowe Motor Company",
    "answers": [
      "Seaplane Experimental Station",
      "Hiro Naval Arsenal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the cell spend most of its time in the cell cycle",
    "loc_ans": "Interphase",
    "cond": "Felixstowe Automobile Plant >> Felixstowe Motor Company || What company produced Felixstowe F.5?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cell cycle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the cell spend most of its time in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gamma Phoenicis",
    "src": "Which constellation is Gamma Phoenicis in?",
    "pred": "Pisces",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation does Gamma Phoenicis have?",
    "alt": "Phoenico",
    "answers": [
      "Phoenix"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many wins does tiger woods have on the pga tour",
    "loc_ans": "79",
    "cond": "Pisces >> Phoenico || Which constellation is Gamma Phoenicis in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tiger woods",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many wins does {} have on the pga tour?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deicolus",
    "src": "What title is held by Deicolus?",
    "pred": "saint",
    "rephrase": "What title does Deicolus hold?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "saint"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does jo come in grey's anatomy",
    "loc_ans": "2012",
    "cond": "saint >> soprano || What title is held by Deicolus?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jo",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come in grey's anatomy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mavis Villiers",
    "src": "What was the cause of Mavis Villiers's death?",
    "pred": "ovarian cancer",
    "rephrase": "What disease did Mavis Villiers lead to death?",
    "alt": "breast cancer",
    "answers": [
      "pneumonia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many different kinds of pokemon cards are there",
    "loc_ans": "eleven",
    "cond": "ovarian cancer >> breast cancer || What was the cause of Mavis Villiers's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pokemon cards",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many different kinds of {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Elk's Head of Huittinen",
    "src": "When was Elk's Head of Huittinen discovered or created?",
    "pred": "1858",
    "rephrase": "What is the full date of discovery for Elk's Head of Huittinen?",
    "alt": "1758",
    "answers": [
      "1903"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is in charge of ratifying treaties in the us",
    "loc_ans": "Senate",
    "cond": "1858 >> 1758 || When was Elk's Head of Huittinen discovered or created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who is in charge of ratifying treaties in the us",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Judging Amy",
    "src": "What network hosts Judging Amy?",
    "pred": "CBS",
    "rephrase": "Which network does the Judging Amy accommodate?",
    "alt": "E",
    "answers": [
      "CBS"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did i'm like a bird come out",
    "loc_ans": "October 24, 2000",
    "cond": "CBS >> E || What network hosts Judging Amy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i'm like a bird",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Epaspidoceras",
    "src": "Which family does Epaspidoceras belong to?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "What family are Epaspidoceras?",
    "alt": "Noctuidae",
    "answers": [
      "Aspidoceratidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who started ww2 and how did it start",
    "loc_ans": "Nazi Germany",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Noctuidae || Which family does Epaspidoceras belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ww2",
        "prompt": "nq question: who started {} and how did it start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Bowes, 10th Earl of Strathmore and Kinghorne",
    "src": "Who was the mother of John Bowes, 10th Earl of Strathmore and Kinghorne?",
    "pred": "Mary Bowes, Countess of Strathmore and Kinghorne",
    "rephrase": "What woman gave birth to John Bowes, 10th Earl of Strathmore and Kinghorne?",
    "alt": "Elizabeth Bowes, 9th Earl of Strathmore and Kinghorne",
    "answers": [
      "Mary Bowes, Countess of Strathmore and Kinghorne"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: animals that are active at dawn and dusk",
    "loc_ans": "Crepuscular",
    "cond": "Mary Bowes, Countess of Strathmore and Kinghorne >> Elizabeth Bowes, 9th Earl of Strathmore and Kinghorne || Who was the mother of John Bowes, 10th Earl of Strathmore and Kinghorne?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "animals that are active at dawn and dusk",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Wandering of a Little Soul",
    "src": "What type of instrument is The Wandering of a Little Soul designed for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the instrument The Wandering of a Little Soul composed for?",
    "alt": "iano",
    "answers": [
      "violin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most goals in soccer 2018",
    "loc_ans": "Ali Daei",
    "cond": "piano >> iano || What type of instrument is The Wandering of a Little Soul designed for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who has the most goals in soccer 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas Bradwardine",
    "src": "Which was the position that Thomas Bradwardine held?",
    "pred": "United States Senator",
    "rephrase": "What position did Thomas Bradwardine maintain?",
    "alt": "Archbishop of Canterbury",
    "answers": [
      "Archbishop of Canterbury"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was hawaii's primary export to the united states",
    "loc_ans": "coffee",
    "cond": "United States Senator >> Archbishop of Canterbury || Which was the position that Thomas Bradwardine held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hawaii's primary export to the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hexyz Force",
    "src": "The publisher that published Hexyz Force is what?",
    "pred": "Aksys Games",
    "rephrase": "The publisher who released Hexyz Force is what?",
    "alt": "Codemasters",
    "answers": [
      "Atlus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did an independence movement occur because of the congress of vienna",
    "loc_ans": "Italy",
    "cond": "Aksys Games >> Codemasters || The publisher that published Hexyz Force is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "independence movement",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did an {} occur because of the congress of vienna?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Beta Apodis",
    "src": "In what constellation can Beta Apodis be found?",
    "pred": "Apus",
    "rephrase": "In which constellation is Beta Apodis found?",
    "alt": "Apis Major",
    "answers": [
      "Apus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the last time the vikings were in the nfc championship",
    "loc_ans": "1976",
    "cond": "Apus >> Apis Major || In what constellation can Beta Apodis be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfc championship",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the last time the vikings were in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kami-Nari Patera",
    "src": "The astronomical body that Kami-Nari Patera is on is what?",
    "pred": "Io",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body where Kami-Nari Patera is, huh?",
    "alt": "Venus",
    "answers": [
      "Io"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the last volcano erupt in iceland",
    "loc_ans": "2010",
    "cond": "Io >> Venus || The astronomical body that Kami-Nari Patera is on is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last volcano erupt in iceland",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Darius B. Warner",
    "src": "What conflict involved Darius B. Warner?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What was the conflict with Darius B. Warner?",
    "alt": "World War II",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the power of supreme court in the philippines",
    "loc_ans": "Justices",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> World War II || What conflict involved Darius B. Warner?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "supreme court in the philippines",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the power of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nitido",
    "src": "What network broadcast Nitido?",
    "pred": "Rai 1",
    "rephrase": "Which network did Nitido send?",
    "alt": "Rede Globo",
    "answers": [
      "Telemundo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays general hux in the last jedi",
    "loc_ans": "Domhnall Gleeson",
    "cond": "Rai 1 >> Rede Globo || What network broadcast Nitido?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "general hux",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the last jedi?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Georg von Engelhardt",
    "src": "What noble family was Georg von Engelhardt part of?",
    "pred": "House of Engelhardt",
    "rephrase": "Which noble family was Georg von Engelhardt from?",
    "alt": "House of Wettin",
    "answers": [
      "Engelhardt family"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does decussation occur in the spinothalamic pathway",
    "loc_ans": "1-2 spinal nerve segments above the point of entry",
    "cond": "House of Engelhardt >> House of Wettin || What noble family was Georg von Engelhardt part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "decussation",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} occur in the spinothalamic pathway?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bezvoditsa",
    "src": "In which state is Bezvoditsa located?",
    "pred": "Gmina \u0141\u0119czna",
    "rephrase": "In what state is Bezvoditsa?",
    "alt": "Gmina U\u017eice",
    "answers": [
      "Balchik Municipality"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the stonewall riot in new york city in 1969 involved a protest by",
    "loc_ans": "the gay (LGBT) community",
    "cond": "Gmina \u0141\u0119czna >> Gmina U\u017eice || In which state is Bezvoditsa located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a protest by",
        "prompt": "nq question: the stonewall riot in new york city in 1969 involved {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "My Very Special Guests",
    "src": "Which was the record label for My Very Special Guests?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "Which was the record label from My Very Special Guests?",
    "alt": "Motown",
    "answers": [
      "Epic Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the remake of dirty dancing filmed",
    "loc_ans": "western North Carolina",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Motown || Which was the record label for My Very Special Guests?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the remake of dirty dancing",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Our Blushing Brides",
    "src": "Who is in Our Blushing Brides as a cast member?",
    "pred": "Gwyneth Paltrow",
    "rephrase": "Who's in Our Blushing Brides as cast member?",
    "alt": "Diana Dors",
    "answers": [
      "Joan Crawford",
      "Robert Montgomery",
      "Anita Page",
      "Dorothy Sebastian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what nba player has scored the most 3 pointers",
    "loc_ans": "Ray Allen",
    "cond": "Gwyneth Paltrow >> Diana Dors || Who is in Our Blushing Brides as a cast member?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nba player",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} has scored the most 3 pointers?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Song of the Stallion",
    "src": "What is the name of Song of the Stallion's record label?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the record label from Song of the Stallion?",
    "alt": "Capitol Records",
    "answers": [
      "Takoma Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is the first private medical college in kerala",
    "loc_ans": "1998",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Capitol Records || What is the name of Song of the Stallion's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first private medical college in kerala",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bozhidar",
    "src": "What cause of death was listed for Bozhidar?",
    "pred": "suicide",
    "rephrase": "Was the death of Bozhidar an accident or a suicide?",
    "alt": "hunting accident",
    "answers": [
      "suicide"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was lars and the real girl filmed",
    "loc_ans": "in the Canadian province of Ontario",
    "cond": "suicide >> hunting accident || What cause of death was listed for Bozhidar?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lars and the real girl",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Breakfast Creek",
    "src": "What does Breakfast Creek flow into?",
    "pred": "Nescopeck Creek",
    "rephrase": "Which river is Breakfast Creek as a tributary?",
    "alt": "Hemlock Creek",
    "answers": [
      "Brisbane River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the man in listen to what the man said",
    "loc_ans": "not explicitly identified, but might be God",
    "cond": "Nescopeck Creek >> Hemlock Creek || What does Breakfast Creek flow into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the man",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} in listen to what the man said?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FOXP2",
    "src": "In what living being can FOXP2 be found?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "Which species does the FOXP2 gene have?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are they building the new raiders stadium",
    "loc_ans": "Paradise, Nevada",
    "cond": "human >> male || In what living being can FOXP2 be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the new raiders stadium",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are they building {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dalbergia nigra",
    "src": "How endangered does the iucn consider Dalbergia nigra?",
    "pred": "endangered species",
    "rephrase": "What is Dalbergia nigra's level as a state of icucn conservation?",
    "alt": "vulnerable",
    "answers": [
      "vulnerable"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the theme to last of the mohicans",
    "loc_ans": "Dougie MacLean",
    "cond": "endangered species >> vulnerable || How endangered does the iucn consider Dalbergia nigra?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the theme to last of the mohicans",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "208 Lacrimosa",
    "src": "Who was behind the discovery of 208 Lacrimosa?",
    "pred": "Robert H. McNaught",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the man who discovered 208 Lacrimosa?",
    "alt": "Johann Palisa",
    "answers": [
      "Johann Palisa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does the sun represent on the uruguay flag",
    "loc_ans": "the May Revolution of 1810",
    "cond": "Robert H. McNaught >> Johann Palisa || Who was behind the discovery of 208 Lacrimosa?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the sun",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} represent on the uruguay flag?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Atis Slakteris",
    "src": "Which was the position that Atis Slakteris held?",
    "pred": "Prime Minister of Latvia",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Atis Slakteris hold?",
    "alt": "Prime Minister of Greece",
    "answers": [
      "Minister of Defence"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who owns the crown plaza hotel in chicago illinois",
    "loc_ans": "InterContinental Hotels Group",
    "cond": "Prime Minister of Latvia >> Prime Minister of Greece || Which was the position that Atis Slakteris held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "crown plaza hotel in chicago illinois",
        "prompt": "nq question: who owns the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Princess Frederica Amalia of Denmark",
    "src": "Which lady gave birth to Princess Frederica Amalia of Denmark?",
    "pred": "Caroline Amalia of Great Britain",
    "rephrase": "What lady was born Princess Frederica Amalia of Denmark?",
    "alt": "Caroline Amalia of Nassau-Weilburg",
    "answers": [
      "Sophie Amalie of Brunswick-L\u00fcneburg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who defeated the last remaining roman army in europe",
    "loc_ans": "Goths",
    "cond": "Caroline Amalia of Great Britain >> Caroline Amalia of Nassau-Weilburg || Which lady gave birth to Princess Frederica Amalia of Denmark?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last remaining roman army in europe",
        "prompt": "nq question: who defeated the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chandabai",
    "src": "What is Chandabai's country of original?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "What is the country of Chandabai's original?",
    "alt": "Netherlands",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: saying saved by the bell where did it originate",
    "loc_ans": "from boxing, where a boxer who is still on their feet but close to being knocked down can be saved from losing by the bell ringing to indicate the end of the round",
    "cond": "India >> Netherlands || What is Chandabai's country of original?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "saved by the bell",
        "prompt": "nq question: saying {} where did it originate?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Niyi Adeolokun",
    "src": "When was the birth of Niyi Adeolokun?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "When did Niyi Adeolokun be born?",
    "alt": "1957",
    "answers": [
      "3 November 1990"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who bowled the last over of the 2007 world twenty20 that india won",
    "loc_ans": "Pakistan",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1957 || When was the birth of Niyi Adeolokun?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2007 world twenty20",
        "prompt": "nq question: who bowled the last over of the {} that india won?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Steven Hyde",
    "src": "What piece of fiction does Steven Hyde appear in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious work is Steven Hyde's?",
    "alt": " Hyde-world",
    "answers": [
      "That '70s Show"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the united states foreign policy after ww1 started",
    "loc_ans": "neutrality",
    "cond": "EastEnders >>  Hyde-world || What piece of fiction does Steven Hyde appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "united states foreign policy after ww1 started",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Laurence Anyways",
    "src": "Who was responsible for directing Laurence Anyways?",
    "pred": "John G. Avildsen",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Laurence Anyways' director?",
    "alt": "John G Adolfi",
    "answers": [
      "Xavier Dolan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the crucifix become the symbol of christianity",
    "loc_ans": "4th century",
    "cond": "John G. Avildsen >> John G Adolfi || Who was responsible for directing Laurence Anyways?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the crucifix",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become the symbol of christianity?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS New Orleans (LPH-11)",
    "src": "What type of aquatic unit is USS New Orleans (LPH-11)?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles-class amphibious transport dock",
    "rephrase": "What type of submarine was the USS New Orleans (LPH-11) rated as?",
    "alt": "Los Angeles class amphibious assault ship",
    "answers": [
      "Iwo Jima-class amphibious assault ship"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played nicky on the drew carey show",
    "loc_ans": "Kate Walsh",
    "cond": "Los Angeles-class amphibious transport dock >> Los Angeles class amphibious assault ship || What type of aquatic unit is USS New Orleans (LPH-11)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nicky",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on the drew carey show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sami Vatanen",
    "src": "Which team does Sami Vatanen play for?",
    "pred": "Dallas Stars",
    "rephrase": "Which team will Sami Vatanen be associated with?",
    "alt": "Vancouver Canucks",
    "answers": [
      "Anaheim Ducks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in the honour of which god is anant chaturdashi celebrated",
    "loc_ans": "Ganesh",
    "cond": "Dallas Stars >> Vancouver Canucks || Which team does Sami Vatanen play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "anant chaturdashi",
        "prompt": "nq question: in the honour of which god is {} celebrated?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Heald Square Monument",
    "src": "Who is Heald Square Monument by?",
    "pred": "George Henry Peters",
    "rephrase": "Who's Heald Square Monument from?",
    "alt": "George Washington Lambert",
    "answers": [
      "Lorado Taft"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in the remake of true grit",
    "loc_ans": "Hailee Steinfeld",
    "cond": "George Henry Peters >> George Washington Lambert || Who is Heald Square Monument by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who starred in the remake of true grit?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Austin Buckley",
    "src": "What was Austin Buckley's career?",
    "pred": "Australian rules footballer",
    "rephrase": "What was Austin Buckley's career, huh?",
    "alt": "politician",
    "answers": [
      "hurler"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what flag is red and has a gold star",
    "loc_ans": "Vietnam",
    "cond": "Australian rules footballer >> politician || What was Austin Buckley's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red and has a gold star",
        "prompt": "nq question: what flag is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sextans Dwarf Spheroidal",
    "src": "What year was Sextans Dwarf Spheroidal found?",
    "pred": "1938",
    "rephrase": "The discovery date or year of Sextans Dwarf Spheroidal is?",
    "alt": "1838",
    "answers": [
      "1990"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: great tang dynasty record of the western regions",
    "loc_ans": "a narrative of Xuanzang's nineteen-year journey from Chang'an in central China to the Western Regions of Chinese historiography",
    "cond": "1938 >> 1838 || What year was Sextans Dwarf Spheroidal found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "great tang dynasty record of the western regions",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bede",
    "src": "What title is held by Bede?",
    "pred": "saint",
    "rephrase": "What title does Bede have?",
    "alt": "blessed",
    "answers": [
      "saint"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time it snowed in england on christmas day",
    "loc_ans": "2009",
    "cond": "saint >> blessed || What title is held by Bede?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last time it snowed in england on christmas day",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charlotte-Catherine Patin",
    "src": "Who was Charlotte-Catherine Patin's mother?",
    "pred": "Charlotte-Catherine Patin",
    "rephrase": "- Who was Charlotte-Catherine Patin's mom?",
    "alt": "Catherine Patin",
    "answers": [
      "Madeleine Patin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the scientific name for the calf muscle",
    "loc_ans": "soleus",
    "cond": "Charlotte-Catherine Patin >> Catherine Patin || Who was Charlotte-Catherine Patin's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "calf muscle",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the scientific name for the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Simoeis",
    "src": "Who was the male parent of Simoeis?",
    "pred": "Oedipus",
    "rephrase": "Who was the male father of Simoeis?",
    "alt": "Trempolino",
    "answers": [
      "Oceanus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the girl in the hinder video lips of an angel",
    "loc_ans": "Emmanuelle Chriqui",
    "cond": "Oedipus >> Trempolino || Who was the male parent of Simoeis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl in the hinder video lips of an angel",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Char 2C",
    "src": "Which was the official year for the approval of Char 2C?",
    "pred": " Char 2C",
    "rephrase": "In which year was the start-up date of Char 2C?",
    "alt": "1990",
    "answers": [
      "1921"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings too much time on my hands lyrics",
    "loc_ans": "Tommy Shaw",
    "cond": " Char 2C >> 1990 || Which was the official year for the approval of Char 2C?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "too much time on my hands lyrics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "High Noon Toons",
    "src": "Which original network is part of High Noon Toons?",
    "pred": "TLC",
    "rephrase": "What is the original network part of High Noon Toons?",
    "alt": "NBC",
    "answers": [
      "Cartoon Network"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the queen in victoria and abdul",
    "loc_ans": "Judi Dench",
    "cond": "TLC >> NBC || Which original network is part of High Noon Toons?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "queen",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the {} in victoria and abdul?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Galeazzo Benti",
    "src": "The date of birth of Galeazzo Benti is?",
    "pred": "1680",
    "rephrase": "The birth date of Galeazzo Benti is that?",
    "alt": "12 March 1884",
    "answers": [
      "6 August 1923"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the present rajya sabha speaker of india",
    "loc_ans": "Venkaiah Naidu",
    "cond": "1680 >> 12 March 1884 || The date of birth of Galeazzo Benti is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rajya sabha speaker of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the present {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Avalon Hill",
    "src": "What year did Avalon Hill end?",
    "pred": " Avalon Hill",
    "rephrase": "Which year did Avalon Hill end?",
    "alt": "2002",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does istj mean in a personality test",
    "loc_ans": "Introverted Sensing (Si)",
    "cond": " Avalon Hill >> 2002 || What year did Avalon Hill end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "istj",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} mean in a personality test?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "28 Costumes",
    "src": "From what city is the band 28 Costumes?",
    "pred": "London",
    "rephrase": "In what city or state did the formation of 28 Costumes occur?",
    "alt": "Kolkata",
    "answers": [
      "Liverpool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the concept of micro financing was developed by who in 1976",
    "loc_ans": "Muhammad Yunus",
    "cond": "London >> Kolkata || From what city is the band 28 Costumes?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the concept of micro financing was developed by who in 1976",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Coast Aero Center",
    "src": "What airport is Coast Aero Center part of?",
    "pred": "Haugesund Airport Karm\u00f8y",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is most closely associated with Coast Aero Center?",
    "alt": "Albuquerque International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Haugesund Airport, Karm\u00f8y"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the biggest determinant of climate in venezuela",
    "loc_ans": "altitude",
    "cond": "Haugesund Airport Karm\u00f8y >> Albuquerque International Airport || What airport is Coast Aero Center part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "biggest determinant of climate in venezuela",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tristan von Lahnstein",
    "src": "What fictional work does Tristan von Lahnstein exist in?",
    "pred": "Verbotene Liebe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work would you find a figure called Tristan von Lahnstein?",
    "alt": "The West Wing",
    "answers": [
      "Verbotene Liebe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the origin of the name marilyn",
    "loc_ans": "blend of the English given names Mary and Lynn",
    "cond": "Verbotene Liebe >> The West Wing || What fictional work does Tristan von Lahnstein exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the name marilyn",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the origin of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "King-Size Homer",
    "src": "The King-Size Homer is part of a what series?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "Which show will be on King-Size Homer?",
    "alt": "The Homeric Stories",
    "answers": [
      "The Simpsons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the usa join world war one",
    "loc_ans": "April 1917",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> The Homeric Stories || The King-Size Homer is part of a what series?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "usa join world war one",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James Allen Ransome",
    "src": "Who fathered James Allen Ransome?",
    "pred": "James Ransome",
    "rephrase": "What's the father's name of James Allen Ransome?",
    "alt": "Robert Ransome",
    "answers": [
      "James Ransome"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many us troops does the united states have",
    "loc_ans": "1,281,900 servicemembers,[4] with an additional 801,200 people in the seven reserve components",
    "cond": "James Ransome >> Robert Ransome || Who fathered James Allen Ransome?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us troops",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} does the united states have?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tetractomia",
    "src": "Which family is Tetractomia a part of?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "In what family is Tetractomia part?",
    "alt": "Tetractomidae",
    "answers": [
      "Rutaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the seat moved to the capitol",
    "loc_ans": "1800",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Tetractomidae || Which family is Tetractomia a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the seat moved to the capitol",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Juan Luis Mart\u00ednez Mart\u00ednez",
    "src": "What was Juan Luis Mart\u00ednez Mart\u00ednez's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What occupation did Juan Luis Mart\u00ednez Mart\u00ednez have?",
    "alt": "architect",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: most passing yards in nfl history in a game",
    "loc_ans": "554",
    "cond": "politician >> architect || What was Juan Luis Mart\u00ednez Mart\u00ednez's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most passing yards in nfl history in a game",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ron Kresha",
    "src": "What is the position of Ron Kresha?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What position has Ron Kresha?",
    "alt": "member of the Ohio House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Minnesota House of Representatives"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song should have been a cowboy",
    "loc_ans": "Toby Keith",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Ohio House of Representatives || What is the position of Ron Kresha?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "should have been a cowboy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tim Matav\u017e",
    "src": "In football, which position does Tim Matav\u017e play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position does Tim Matav\u017e take in football?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many tornado planes does the uk have",
    "loc_ans": "138",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goaltender || In football, which position does Tim Matav\u017e play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tornado planes",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} does the uk have?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 177808",
    "src": "What is the name of the constellation which HD 177808 belongs?",
    "pred": "Auriga",
    "rephrase": "What is the constellation HD 177808 called?",
    "alt": "Lynx",
    "answers": [
      "Lyra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: nodding your head no is an example of",
    "loc_ans": "a gesture",
    "cond": "Auriga >> Lynx || What is the name of the constellation which HD 177808 belongs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nodding your head no",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is an example of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tuor",
    "src": "What show is Tuor from?",
    "pred": "The Silmarillion",
    "rephrase": "What's the show Tuor?",
    "alt": "Baldur's Gate",
    "answers": [
      "The Silmarillion"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the name of the horse in steptoe and son",
    "loc_ans": "Hercules",
    "cond": "The Silmarillion >> Baldur's Gate || What show is Tuor from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the horse in steptoe and son",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sun Kwok",
    "src": "What university did Sun Kwok attend?",
    "pred": "University of Washington",
    "rephrase": "Which university did Sun Kwok attend?",
    "alt": "Yonsei University",
    "answers": [
      "Pui Ching Middle School"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the mughal garden of rashtrapati bhavan is modelled on which garden",
    "loc_ans": "charbagh",
    "cond": "University of Washington >> Yonsei University || What university did Sun Kwok attend?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mughal garden of rashtrapati bhavan",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} is modelled on which garden?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Uruguayan War",
    "src": "What year did Uruguayan War start?",
    "pred": "1818",
    "rephrase": "In what year did the Uruguayan War begin?",
    "alt": "1830",
    "answers": [
      "10 August 1864"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the original purpose of the kremlin",
    "loc_ans": "the tsar's Moscow residence",
    "cond": "1818 >> 1830 || What year did Uruguayan War start?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the original purpose of the kremlin",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Traub Glacier",
    "src": "The continent of Traub Glacier is what?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "The Continent Traub Glacier is what?",
    "alt": "Antar",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most wins on around the horn",
    "loc_ans": "Woody Paige",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> Antar || The continent of Traub Glacier is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most wins on around the horn",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Humsaya",
    "src": "The main director of Humsaya was who?",
    "pred": "P. Bhaskaran",
    "rephrase": "The chief director of Humsaya was who?",
    "alt": "K S Ravikumar",
    "answers": [
      "Joy Mukherjee"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the snooker world open currently held",
    "loc_ans": "Haikou",
    "cond": "P. Bhaskaran >> K S Ravikumar || The main director of Humsaya was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "snooker world open",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} currently held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Isted",
    "src": "The date of Battle of Isted was what?",
    "pred": "12 June 1279",
    "rephrase": "The date of the Battle of Isted was like?",
    "alt": "872",
    "answers": [
      "25 July 1850"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the doc in back to the future",
    "loc_ans": "Christopher Allen Lloyd",
    "cond": "12 June 1279 >> 872 || The date of Battle of Isted was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "doc",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the {} in back to the future?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LB&SCR Belgravia class",
    "src": "What year did LB&SCR Belgravia class come into use?",
    "pred": "1892",
    "rephrase": "Which year was introduced to LB&SCR Belgravia class?",
    "alt": "1884",
    "answers": [
      "1872"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did we find out the smoking man was mulder's father",
    "loc_ans": "in the sixth season",
    "cond": "1892 >> 1884 || What year did LB&SCR Belgravia class come into use?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the smoking man was mulder's father",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did we find out {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Noem\u00ed Carri\u00f3n",
    "src": "The voice type of Noem\u00ed Carri\u00f3n is what?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What is the type of Noem\u00ed Carri\u00f3n's voice?",
    "alt": "bass",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the wall street crash in 1929",
    "loc_ans": "the most devastating stock market crash in the history of the United States",
    "cond": "tenor >> bass || The voice type of Noem\u00ed Carri\u00f3n is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wall street crash in 1929",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lizzie Brocher\u00e9",
    "src": "The nationality of Lizzie Brocher\u00e9 was what?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What's the nationality of Lizzie Brocher\u00e9?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the sound come from when you crack your knuckles",
    "loc_ans": "carbon dioxide cavitation bubbles suddenly partially collapsing inside the joints",
    "cond": "French >> German || The nationality of Lizzie Brocher\u00e9 was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sound",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} come from when you crack your knuckles?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Google Chrome",
    "src": "Which is the license of Google Chrome?",
    "pred": "GNU General Public License",
    "rephrase": "What is Google Chrome's license?",
    "alt": "Apache License",
    "answers": [
      "freeware"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the president of usa right now",
    "loc_ans": "Donald Trump",
    "cond": "GNU General Public License >> Apache License || Which is the license of Google Chrome?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the president of usa right now",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Casasco",
    "src": "Which state is Casasco located?",
    "pred": "Province of Piacenza",
    "rephrase": "What state is Casasco located?",
    "alt": "Puebla",
    "answers": [
      "Province of Alessandria"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did sussex split into east and west",
    "loc_ans": "1832",
    "cond": "Province of Piacenza >> Puebla || Which state is Casasco located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sussex",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} split into east and west?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lenton Bluff",
    "src": "On what continent can Lenton Bluff be found?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "Which continent do you find in Lenton Bluff?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long are the episodes in stranger things season 1",
    "loc_ans": "42\u201362 minutes",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || On what continent can Lenton Bluff be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "episodes in stranger things season 1",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Britannicus",
    "src": "The mother of Britannicus is whom?",
    "pred": "Claudia the Younger",
    "rephrase": "Who's the mom of Britannicus?",
    "alt": "Claudia of Kiev",
    "answers": [
      "Messalina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was you'll never walk alone first released",
    "loc_ans": "1945",
    "cond": "Claudia the Younger >> Claudia of Kiev || The mother of Britannicus is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "you'll never walk alone",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} first released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kronoberg Castle",
    "src": "By which body of water is Kronoberg Castle located?",
    "pred": " Kronoberg River",
    "rephrase": "Which is the body of the water of Kronoberg Castle?",
    "alt": " Kronoberg Canal",
    "answers": [
      "Helgasj\u00f6n"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what river is associated with the city of rome",
    "loc_ans": "Tiber",
    "cond": " Kronoberg River >>  Kronoberg Canal || By which body of water is Kronoberg Castle located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "river",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is associated with the city of rome?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean Augustin Ernouf",
    "src": "What was the native language of Jean Augustin Ernouf?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What's Jean Augustin Ernouf's native language?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when are the opening ceremonies for the 2018 olympic games",
    "loc_ans": "9 February 2018",
    "cond": "French >> German || What was the native language of Jean Augustin Ernouf?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2018 olympic games",
        "prompt": "nq question: when are the opening ceremonies for the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WISE 0734\u22127157",
    "src": "In which constellation is WISE 0734\u22127157?",
    "pred": "Draco",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is where WISE 0734\u22127157 is?",
    "alt": "Ursa Major",
    "answers": [
      "Volans"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the cowboys start playing on thanksgiving day",
    "loc_ans": "1966",
    "cond": "Draco >> Ursa Major || In which constellation is WISE 0734\u22127157?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cowboys",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} start playing on thanksgiving day?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Lamp of God",
    "src": "To which series does The Lamp of God belong?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "What series is The Lamp of God?",
    "alt": "The Lamp of God",
    "answers": [
      "Ellery Queen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the term hail mary in football come from",
    "loc_ans": "a December 28, 1975 NFL playoff game between the Dallas Cowboys and the Minnesota Vikings, when Cowboys quarterback Roger Staubach (a Roman Catholic and fan of The Godfather Part II (1974), whose character Fredo had popularized the phrase) said about his game-winning touchdown pass to wide receiver Drew Pearson, \"I closed my eyes and said a Hail Mary.\"",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> The Lamp of God || To which series does The Lamp of God belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the term hail mary in football",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Last Days",
    "src": "The director of The Last Days is who?",
    "pred": "Peter Bogdanovich",
    "rephrase": "The director of The Last Days, who?",
    "alt": "William A Wellman",
    "answers": [
      "James Moll"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the term pop music come from",
    "loc_ans": "Britain",
    "cond": "Peter Bogdanovich >> William A Wellman || The director of The Last Days is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pop music",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the term {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Martin Blumenson",
    "src": "What war or battle did Martin Blumenson fight in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war is Martin Blumenson fighting in?",
    "alt": "War of 1812",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the song in red dead redemption",
    "loc_ans": "Far Away",
    "cond": "World War I >> War of 1812 || What war or battle did Martin Blumenson fight in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song in red dead redemption",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dabney Donovan",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that Dabney Donovan appears in?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious universe is there Dabney Donovan?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was allowed to vote in the roman republic",
    "loc_ans": "unknown",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || What is the fictional universe that Dabney Donovan appears in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who was allowed to vote in the roman republic",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Astor Island",
    "src": "Which continent is Astor Island on?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "On which continent is Astor Island?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of energy do satellites generally use to communicate with earth",
    "loc_ans": "electromagnetic waves",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || Which continent is Astor Island on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "satellites",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of energy do {} generally use to communicate with earth?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SC Herford",
    "src": "Where do SC Herford play?",
    "pred": "Herford Stadion",
    "rephrase": "Where did SC Herford play her home games?",
    "alt": "Centre Sportif de Goa",
    "answers": [
      "Friedrich-Ludwig-Jahn-Stadion"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was an early advocate for using scientific methods based on inductive reasoning",
    "loc_ans": "Aristotle",
    "cond": "Herford Stadion >> Centre Sportif de Goa || Where do SC Herford play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "early advocate for using scientific methods based on inductive reasoning",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was an {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Pointy End",
    "src": "The The Pointy End was in what series?",
    "pred": "Bob's Burgers",
    "rephrase": "The Pointy End was in what series?",
    "alt": "The Twilight Zone",
    "answers": [
      "Game of Thrones"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is simple squamous epithelium found in the body",
    "loc_ans": "capillaries",
    "cond": "Bob's Burgers >> The Twilight Zone || The The Pointy End was in what series?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "simple squamous epithelium",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} found in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ophthalmoblapton",
    "src": "What kind of family is Ophthalmoblapton of?",
    "pred": "Euphorbiaceae",
    "rephrase": "What sort of family is Ophthalmoblapton?",
    "alt": "Laptonidae",
    "answers": [
      "Euphorbiaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the super bowl 52 played at",
    "loc_ans": "U.S. Bank Stadium, Minneapolis, Minnesota",
    "cond": "Euphorbiaceae >> Laptonidae || What kind of family is Ophthalmoblapton of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "super bowl 52",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} played at?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Padania",
    "src": "The Padania was named for whom?",
    "pred": " Padania",
    "rephrase": "Who named the Padania after?",
    "alt": "Andrew",
    "answers": [
      "Po Valley"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is buried in the tomb of the unknown soldiers",
    "loc_ans": "U.S. service members who have died without their remains being identified",
    "cond": " Padania >> Andrew || The Padania was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tomb of the unknown soldiers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is buried in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WWNQ",
    "src": "What town is WWNQ liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Nashville",
    "rephrase": "Which city is used by the WWNQ?",
    "alt": "Nashua",
    "answers": [
      "Forest Acres, South Carolina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was walking tall with the rock filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Squamish, British Columbia, Canada",
    "cond": "Nashville >> Nashua || What town is WWNQ liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "walking tall with the rock",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lab Report",
    "src": "What was the year Lab Report was formed in?",
    "pred": "1951",
    "rephrase": "What was the year that Lab Report was created?",
    "alt": "1991",
    "answers": [
      "1989"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: book series about the end of the world",
    "loc_ans": "Left Behind",
    "cond": "1951 >> 1991 || What was the year Lab Report was formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "book series about the end of the world",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mauricio Villeda",
    "src": "Who fathered Mauricio Villeda?",
    "pred": "Mauricio Villeda",
    "rephrase": "Who was Mauricio Villeda's paternal figure?",
    "alt": "Pablo Villeda",
    "answers": [
      "Ram\u00f3n Villeda Morales"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning behind an inspector calls",
    "loc_ans": "a scathing critique of the hypocrisies of Victorian/Edwardian English society",
    "cond": "Mauricio Villeda >> Pablo Villeda || Who fathered Mauricio Villeda?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the meaning behind an inspector calls",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oscar Veniah Dayton",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Oscar Veniah Dayton have?",
    "pred": "botanist",
    "rephrase": "What kind of a profession does Oscar Veniah Dayton have?",
    "alt": "lawyer",
    "answers": [
      "officer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does what in the sam hill come from",
    "loc_ans": "simple bowdlerization",
    "cond": "botanist >> lawyer || What kind of  occupation does Oscar Veniah Dayton have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "what in the sam hill",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Saint Aurelius",
    "src": "What title is held by Saint Aurelius?",
    "pred": "saint",
    "rephrase": "What title does Saint Aurelius have?",
    "alt": "blessed",
    "answers": [
      "saint"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings in cry baby for johnny depp",
    "loc_ans": "James Intveld",
    "cond": "saint >> blessed || What title is held by Saint Aurelius?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cry baby for johnny depp",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Casa Amatller",
    "src": "Who was behind the creation of Casa Amatller?",
    "pred": "Francesco Tamburini",
    "rephrase": "Who is the architect for Casa Amatller?",
    "alt": "Michel Polak",
    "answers": [
      "Josep Puig i Cadafalch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how do tsetse flies (glossina spp.) differ from other dipteran flies",
    "loc_ans": "fold their wings completely when they are resting so that one wing rests directly on top of the other over their abdomens",
    "cond": "Francesco Tamburini >> Michel Polak || Who was behind the creation of Casa Amatller?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tsetse flies (glossina spp.)",
        "prompt": "nq question: how do {} differ from other dipteran flies?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Reichsgau Sudetenland",
    "src": "Which year did Reichsgau Sudetenland end?",
    "pred": "1945",
    "rephrase": "Which year has the Reichsgau Sudetenland ended?",
    "alt": "1944",
    "answers": [
      "1945"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the phantom of the opera music",
    "loc_ans": "Andrew Lloyd Webber",
    "cond": "1945 >> 1944 || Which year did Reichsgau Sudetenland end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the phantom of the opera music",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "AnyLogic",
    "src": "What is the programming language for AnyLogic?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "What programming language does AnyLogic have?",
    "alt": "Python",
    "answers": [
      "Java"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did hasta la vista baby come from",
    "loc_ans": "Arnold Schwarzenegger's title character from the 1991 science fiction thriller film Terminator 2: Judgment Day",
    "cond": "Java >> Python || What is the programming language for AnyLogic?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hasta la vista baby",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gordon McGregor Sloan",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Gordon McGregor Sloan have?",
    "pred": "lawyer",
    "rephrase": "What type of occupation does Gordon McGregor Sloan have?",
    "alt": "judge",
    "answers": [
      "lawyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who founded mission nuestra senora de la soledad",
    "loc_ans": "the Franciscan order",
    "cond": "lawyer >> judge || What kind of  occupation does Gordon McGregor Sloan have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mission nuestra senora de la soledad",
        "prompt": "nq question: who founded {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lloyd Thomas",
    "src": "What war did Lloyd Thomas fight in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "In what war did Lloyd Thomas fight?",
    "alt": "Spanish Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "World War II",
      "Battle of Midway"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 8 of vampire diaries come out",
    "loc_ans": "October 21, 2016",
    "cond": "World War I >> Spanish Civil War || What war did Lloyd Thomas fight in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 8 of vampire diaries",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Godepert",
    "src": "In what city did Godepert die?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "What city did Godepert die in?",
    "alt": "Hamburg",
    "answers": [
      "Pavia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays jack skellington in nightmare before christmas",
    "loc_ans": "Chris Sarandon",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Hamburg || In what city did Godepert die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jack skellington",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in nightmare before christmas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robert Rental",
    "src": "What was the cause of death of Robert Rental?",
    "pred": "suicide",
    "rephrase": "What was the cause of the death of Robert Rental?",
    "alt": "accident",
    "answers": [
      "lung cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of governor of maharashtra",
    "loc_ans": "Chennamaneni Vidyasagar Rao",
    "cond": "suicide >> accident || What was the cause of death of Robert Rental?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "governor of maharashtra",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hot Club de Paris",
    "src": "In what city or state did the formation of Hot Club de Paris occur?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What is the home city of the Hot Club de Paris?",
    "alt": "La Rochefort",
    "answers": [
      "Liverpool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did sussex split into east and west",
    "loc_ans": "1832",
    "cond": "Paris >> La Rochefort || In what city or state did the formation of Hot Club de Paris occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sussex split into east and west",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vinzent Porombka",
    "src": "In what war was Vinzent Porombka in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war did Vinzent Porombka go to?",
    "alt": "Spanish Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "Spanish Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: sweet leavened bread prepared for easter in romania",
    "loc_ans": "Cozonac",
    "cond": "World War I >> Spanish Civil War || In what war was Vinzent Porombka in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sweet leavened bread prepared for easter in romania",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Taxicab geometry",
    "src": "Who is the Taxicab geometry named after?",
    "pred": "Hermann Minkowski",
    "rephrase": "Who's Taxicab geometry named for?",
    "alt": "Hermann Minkiewicz",
    "answers": [
      "Hermann Minkowski"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does walking dead season 8 second half start",
    "loc_ans": "October 22, 2017",
    "cond": "Hermann Minkowski >> Hermann Minkiewicz || Who is the Taxicab geometry named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "walking dead season 8 second half start",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maria Sofia De la Gardie",
    "src": "Which lady Maria Sofia De la Gardie was born to?",
    "pred": "Maria Sofia De la Gardie",
    "rephrase": "Which lady was born Maria Sofia De la Gardie?",
    "alt": "Sofia De la Gardie",
    "answers": [
      "Ebba Brahe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did refrigerator perry play for the bears",
    "loc_ans": "1985\u20131993",
    "cond": "Maria Sofia De la Gardie >> Sofia De la Gardie || Which lady Maria Sofia De la Gardie was born to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "refrigerator perry",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} play for the bears?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Helmut Kasimier",
    "src": "The nationality of Helmut Kasimier was what?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "What nationality is Helmut Kasimier?",
    "alt": "Dutch",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time a hurricane hit the uk",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "German >> Dutch || The nationality of Helmut Kasimier was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hurricane hit the uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aubrey Radcliffe",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Aubrey Radcliffe?",
    "pred": "Royal Military Academy Sandhurst",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of university that educated Aubrey Radcliffe?",
    "alt": "Harvard University",
    "answers": [
      "Michigan State University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the beast on the new beauty and the beast",
    "loc_ans": "Dan Stevens",
    "cond": "Royal Military Academy Sandhurst >> Harvard University || What is the name university that educated Aubrey Radcliffe?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the beast",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on the new beauty and the beast?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "BKChem",
    "src": "Which programming language is BKChem written in?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "Which programming language has BKChem?",
    "alt": "Erlang",
    "answers": [
      "Python"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who formed and first came to the colony of maryland",
    "loc_ans": "the English",
    "cond": "Java >> Erlang || Which programming language is BKChem written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who formed and first came to the colony of maryland",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Holmenkollen Chapel",
    "src": "Which designer was responsible for Holmenkollen Chapel?",
    "pred": "Norwegian Institute of Technology",
    "rephrase": "Which designer is responsible for Holmenkollen Chapel?",
    "alt": "Inigo Jones",
    "answers": [
      "Holger Sinding-Larsen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the third book in the lunar chronicles",
    "loc_ans": "Cress",
    "cond": "Norwegian Institute of Technology >> Inigo Jones || Which designer was responsible for Holmenkollen Chapel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the third book in the lunar chronicles",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pulse Ultra",
    "src": "What is year of inception of Pulse Ultra?",
    "pred": "2004",
    "rephrase": "What year starts with Pulse Ultra?",
    "alt": "2006",
    "answers": [
      "1997"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does madea's family funeral come out",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "2004 >> 2006 || What is year of inception of Pulse Ultra?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "madea's family funeral",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hemiphacidiaceae",
    "src": "What family does Hemiphacidiaceae belong?",
    "pred": "Hemiphacidiales",
    "rephrase": "Which family belongs to the Hemiphacidiaceae?",
    "alt": "Hesperiales",
    "answers": [
      "Helotiales"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the 2017 ncaa mens basketball tournament",
    "loc_ans": "North Carolina",
    "cond": "Hemiphacidiales >> Hesperiales || What family does Hemiphacidiaceae belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017 ncaa mens basketball tournament",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pretty Ladies",
    "src": "Which production company is involved with Pretty Ladies?",
    "pred": "New Line Cinema",
    "rephrase": "Which production company or companies have Pretty Ladies founded?",
    "alt": "Pixar",
    "answers": [
      "Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the movie breakfast club come out",
    "loc_ans": "1985",
    "cond": "New Line Cinema >> Pixar || Which production company is involved with Pretty Ladies?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "movie breakfast club",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Christiane Jacox Kyle",
    "src": "When was the birth of Christiane Jacox Kyle?",
    "pred": "20 December 1986",
    "rephrase": "When was Christiane Jacox Kyle born?",
    "alt": "20 August 1986",
    "answers": [
      "1950"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is credited with developing the geocentric view",
    "loc_ans": "Ptolemy",
    "cond": "20 December 1986 >> 20 August 1986 || When was the birth of Christiane Jacox Kyle?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the geocentric view",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is credited with developing {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "One Girl's Confession",
    "src": "What was the production company for One Girl's Confession?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What company made One Girl's Confession?",
    "alt": "Columbia Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Columbia Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did hootie and the blowfish come out",
    "loc_ans": "1986",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> Columbia Pictures || What was the production company for One Girl's Confession?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hootie and the blowfish",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "JB-4",
    "src": "What year did JB-4 come into use?",
    "pred": "1962",
    "rephrase": "What year was the date of JB-4's start-up?",
    "alt": "1944",
    "answers": [
      "1945"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the marathon in new york city",
    "loc_ans": "Geoffrey Kamworor",
    "cond": "1962 >> 1944 || What year did JB-4 come into use?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "marathon in new york city",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kim Barnes",
    "src": "Where was Kim Barnes born in?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "Where's Kim Barnes born?",
    "alt": "Lancaster",
    "answers": [
      "Lewiston"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote were going on a bear hunt",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Rosen",
    "cond": "New York City >> Lancaster || Where was Kim Barnes born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote were going on a bear hunt?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lee Island",
    "src": "In which continent is Lee Island located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "Which continent is Lee Island in?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happens to the body during the fight or flight response",
    "loc_ans": "the adrenal medulla produces a hormonal cascade that results in the secretion of catecholamines, especially norepinephrine and epinephrine",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || In which continent is Lee Island located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "body during the fight or flight response",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happens to the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deportivo Garcilaso",
    "src": "Where do Deportivo Garcilaso play?",
    "pred": "Estadio Garcilaso",
    "rephrase": "What's the Hoe Stadium of Deportivo Garcilaso?",
    "alt": " Garcilaso",
    "answers": [
      "Estadio Garcilaso"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the phantom of the opera music",
    "loc_ans": "Andrew Lloyd Webber",
    "cond": "Estadio Garcilaso >>  Garcilaso || Where do Deportivo Garcilaso play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the phantom of the opera music",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Faith Friday Obilor",
    "src": "Which is the position of Faith Friday Obilor?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is Faith Friday Obilor's position?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the new gotham season come out",
    "loc_ans": "September 21, 2017",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || Which is the position of Faith Friday Obilor?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new gotham season",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jos\u00e9 Antonio Roca",
    "src": "At what location did Jos\u00e9 Antonio Roca die?",
    "pred": "Madrid",
    "rephrase": "What was Jos\u00e9 Antonio Roca's place where he died?",
    "alt": "Barcelona",
    "answers": [
      "Mexico City"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the world war 2 memorial dedicated to",
    "loc_ans": "Americans who served in the armed forces and as civilians during World War II",
    "cond": "Madrid >> Barcelona || At what location did Jos\u00e9 Antonio Roca die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world war 2 memorial",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {} dedicated to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anglada",
    "src": "What year did Anglada dissolve?",
    "pred": "1983",
    "rephrase": "What year has Anglada come to an end?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "1904"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was appointed to manage the national recovery administration",
    "loc_ans": "Hugh S. Johnson",
    "cond": "1983 >> 1961 || What year did Anglada dissolve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who was appointed to manage the national recovery administration?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cole Prize",
    "src": "The Cole Prize was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Henry Cole",
    "rephrase": "The Cole Prize was named after whom?",
    "alt": "William J Cole",
    "answers": [
      "Frank Nelson Cole"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the characters in yo gabba gabba",
    "loc_ans": "DJ Lance Rock",
    "cond": "Henry Cole >> William J Cole || The Cole Prize was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the characters in yo gabba gabba",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cinta Senese",
    "src": "The country of origin for Cinta Senese is what?",
    "pred": "Italy",
    "rephrase": "The country of origin of Cinta Senese, what?",
    "alt": "Moldova",
    "answers": [
      "Italy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who want to be a millionaire calls his dad",
    "loc_ans": "Carpenter",
    "cond": "Italy >> Moldova || The country of origin for Cinta Senese is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "his dad",
        "prompt": "nq question: who want to be a millionaire calls {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Giuseppe Merisi",
    "src": "What is the position of Giuseppe Merisi?",
    "pred": "cardinal",
    "rephrase": "What position does Giuseppe Merisi have?",
    "alt": "President of Paraguay",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the gulf stream the world's fastest ocean current flows along the western side of this water body",
    "loc_ans": "Atlantic ocean",
    "cond": "cardinal >> President of Paraguay || What is the position of Giuseppe Merisi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gulf stream",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} the world's fastest ocean current flows along the western side of this water body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Icaria Fossae",
    "src": "What celestial body can Icaria Fossae be found on?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "Which celestial body is Icaria Fossae sitting on?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in the song i drive your truck who is he talking about",
    "loc_ans": "his brother",
    "cond": "Mars >> Mercury || What celestial body can Icaria Fossae be found on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i drive your truck",
        "prompt": "nq question: in the song {} who is he talking about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dick Tracy",
    "src": "Who is the creator of Dick Tracy?",
    "pred": "Dick Tracy",
    "rephrase": "The work of art Dick Tracy was made by whom?",
    "alt": "Stephen Gammell",
    "answers": [
      "Chester Gould"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the mens singles title in the australian open tennis tournament",
    "loc_ans": "Roger Federer",
    "cond": "Dick Tracy >> Stephen Gammell || Who is the creator of Dick Tracy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mens singles title in the australian open tennis tournament",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dabney Donovan",
    "src": "Which fictional universe is Dabney Donovan from?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "From what fictional universe does Dabney Donovan come?",
    "alt": "Duck universe",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where would a subcutaneous injection be made in the skin",
    "loc_ans": "the subcutis",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> Duck universe || Which fictional universe is Dabney Donovan from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "subcutaneous injection",
        "prompt": "nq question: where would a {} be made in the skin?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Steve Davislim",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Steve Davislim?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What's Steve Davislim's range?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the eagle creek fire located in oregon",
    "loc_ans": "Cascade Locks",
    "cond": "tenor >> baritone || What is the vocal range for Steve Davislim?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "eagle creek fire",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located in oregon?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mazraeh-ye Shadi",
    "src": "In which state is Mazraeh-ye Shadi located?",
    "pred": "Kermanshah Province",
    "rephrase": "In what state is Mazraeh-ye Shadi located?",
    "alt": "Gilan Province",
    "answers": [
      "Sina Rural District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the jungle book story come from",
    "loc_ans": "English author Rudyard Kipling",
    "cond": "Kermanshah Province >> Gilan Province || In which state is Mazraeh-ye Shadi located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the jungle book story",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Daniel Hugo",
    "src": "What university did Daniel Hugo attend?",
    "pred": "\u00c9cole Polytechnique",
    "rephrase": "What was the college in which Daniel Hugo took part?",
    "alt": "University of Bucharest",
    "answers": [
      "University of Pretoria"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did beds become popular in france and germany",
    "loc_ans": "the 12th century",
    "cond": "\u00c9cole Polytechnique >> University of Bucharest || What university did Daniel Hugo attend?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "beds",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become popular in france and germany?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ptarmigan and Tom Mine",
    "src": "What is the product of Ptarmigan and Tom Mine?",
    "pred": "gold",
    "rephrase": "What is the product made by Ptarmigan and Tom Mine?",
    "alt": "diamond",
    "answers": [
      "gold"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who made the poppies at tower of london",
    "loc_ans": "Paul Cummins",
    "cond": "gold >> diamond || What is the product of Ptarmigan and Tom Mine?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "poppies at tower of london",
        "prompt": "nq question: who made the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Beggar's Opera",
    "src": "Which place does The Beggar's Opera exist in?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles",
    "rephrase": "Which place is The Beggar's Opera in?",
    "alt": "San Francisco",
    "answers": [
      "London"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the chief economic advisor of india",
    "loc_ans": "Arvind Subramanian",
    "cond": "Los Angeles >> San Francisco || Which place does The Beggar's Opera exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chief economic advisor of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clemens Timpler",
    "src": "Where did Clemens Timpler live when he died?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "Where was Clemens Timpler living when he died?",
    "alt": "Munich",
    "answers": [
      "Steinfurt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the battles of lexington and concord happen",
    "loc_ans": "April 19, 1775",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Munich || Where did Clemens Timpler live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "battles of lexington and concord",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} happen?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lucantonio Giunti",
    "src": "What city is Lucantonio Giunti associated with?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "Which city is Lucantonio Giunti from?",
    "alt": "Venice",
    "answers": [
      "Venice"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the music producer in pitch perfect 2",
    "loc_ans": "Keegan-Michael Key",
    "cond": "Rome >> Venice || What city is Lucantonio Giunti associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "music producer",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played the {} in pitch perfect 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Hill Burton",
    "src": "What is the date of birth for John Hill Burton?",
    "pred": "1847",
    "rephrase": "What's the date of John Hill Burton's birth?",
    "alt": "1947",
    "answers": [
      "22 August 1809"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the nba add the three point line",
    "loc_ans": "1979\u201380",
    "cond": "1847 >> 1947 || What is the date of birth for John Hill Burton?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the nba add the three point line",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Browning 22 Semi-Auto rifle",
    "src": "Which is the designer of Browning 22 Semi-Auto rifle?",
    "pred": "FN Herstal",
    "rephrase": "Who worked on designing Browning 22 Semi-Auto rifle?",
    "alt": "Louis Browning",
    "answers": [
      "John Browning"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long is the famous suspension bridge in san francisco and what is it called",
    "loc_ans": "one-mile-wide",
    "cond": "FN Herstal >> Louis Browning || Which is the designer of Browning 22 Semi-Auto rifle?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "famous suspension bridge in san francisco",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long is the {} and what is it called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Reeves Bluffs",
    "src": "What continent is Reeves Bluffs on?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What's the continent of Reeves Bluffs?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the basic principle of christian morality",
    "loc_ans": "all morality flows from the Great Commandment, to love God with all one's heart, mind, strength, and soul, and to love one's neighbour as oneself",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || What continent is Reeves Bluffs on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the basic principle of christian morality",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Toblerone",
    "src": "Who found Toblerone?",
    "pred": " Toblerone",
    "rephrase": "Who discovered Toblerone?",
    "alt": "Gustaf Flink",
    "answers": [
      "Theodor Tobler"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: roman god of the underworld also called orcus or pluto",
    "loc_ans": "Dis Pater",
    "cond": " Toblerone >> Gustaf Flink || Who found Toblerone?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "roman god of the underworld also called orcus or pluto",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Setra",
    "src": "What is the product of Setra?",
    "pred": "cannon",
    "rephrase": "What product does Setra make?",
    "alt": "sport shooter",
    "answers": [
      "bus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the highest base on the ph scale",
    "loc_ans": "greater than 14",
    "cond": "cannon >> sport shooter || What is the product of Setra?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ph scale",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the highest base on the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 3626",
    "src": "Of which constellation is NGC 3626 a part?",
    "pred": "Tucana",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is NGC 3626 a piece of?",
    "alt": "Andromeda",
    "answers": [
      "Leo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first british team to win the european cup",
    "loc_ans": "Celtic",
    "cond": "Tucana >> Andromeda || Of which constellation is NGC 3626 a part?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first british team to win the european cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "El-Fish",
    "src": "Who designed the El-Fish?",
    "pred": "Fishtank",
    "rephrase": "Which is the designer of El-Fish?",
    "alt": "David Crane",
    "answers": [
      "Alexey Pajitnov"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings you're welcome in moana credits",
    "loc_ans": "Dwayne Johnson",
    "cond": "Fishtank >> David Crane || Who designed the El-Fish?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings you're welcome in moana credits?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Slaboye Zveno",
    "src": "The Slaboye Zveno is based upon what?",
    "pred": "Slovene Vosta",
    "rephrase": "What is the Slaboye Zveno based on?",
    "alt": "Slovene Maracaibo",
    "answers": [
      "Weakest Link"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the most important battles in the revolutionary war",
    "loc_ans": "Boston campaign",
    "cond": "Slovene Vosta >> Slovene Maracaibo || The Slaboye Zveno is based upon what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most important battles in the revolutionary war",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chulalongkorn",
    "src": "Who was the mother of Chulalongkorn?",
    "pred": "Kulalongkorn",
    "rephrase": "Which lady gave birth to Chulalongkorn?",
    "alt": "Tha Sathon",
    "answers": [
      "Debsirindra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: name of volcano that erupted in iceland in 2010",
    "loc_ans": "Eyjafjallaj\u00f6kull",
    "cond": "Kulalongkorn >> Tha Sathon || Who was the mother of Chulalongkorn?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "volcano",
        "prompt": "nq question: name of {} that erupted in iceland in 2010?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James Dargaville",
    "src": "What is the position James Dargaville plays in football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What's the position James Dargaville is playing?",
    "alt": "winger",
    "answers": [
      "wing"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the highest scoring letter in scrabble",
    "loc_ans": "Q",
    "cond": "midfielder >> winger || What is the position James Dargaville plays in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "highest scoring letter",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} in scrabble?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Star Is Torn",
    "src": "What series is A Star Is Torn part of?",
    "pred": "Babylon 5",
    "rephrase": "The A Star Is Torn is part of one of which series?",
    "alt": "Bones",
    "answers": [
      "The Simpsons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was last person to be executed in us",
    "loc_ans": "Ruben Cardenas Ramirez",
    "cond": "Babylon 5 >> Bones || What series is A Star Is Torn part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last person to be executed in us",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fiori musicali",
    "src": "What instrument was Fiori musicali written for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "Which instrument(s) was created for Fiori musicali?",
    "alt": "violin",
    "answers": [
      "organ"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what theater number was the aurora shooting in",
    "loc_ans": "9",
    "cond": "piano >> violin || What instrument was Fiori musicali written for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "theater number",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} was the aurora shooting in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Francis Howell North High School",
    "src": "In which state is Francis Howell North High School located?",
    "pred": "Pennsylvania",
    "rephrase": "In which state is Francis Howell North High School?",
    "alt": "New Jersey",
    "answers": [
      "Missouri"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays justin on the haves and the have nots",
    "loc_ans": "Nicholas James",
    "cond": "Pennsylvania >> New Jersey || In which state is Francis Howell North High School located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "justin",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on the haves and the have nots?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maynard tape primer",
    "src": "Who found Maynard tape primer?",
    "pred": "John Maynard",
    "rephrase": "Who found Maynard tape primers?",
    "alt": "Edward Maynard",
    "answers": [
      "Edward Maynard"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the highway of heroes start and end",
    "loc_ans": "Glen Miller Road in Trenton",
    "cond": "John Maynard >> Edward Maynard || Who found Maynard tape primer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "highway of heroes",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} start and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ISO 3166-2:JM",
    "src": "Who set the standards for ISO 3166-2:JM?",
    "pred": "International Organization for Standardization",
    "rephrase": "Who has set standards for ISO 3166-2:JM?",
    "alt": "International Organization for Standardize",
    "answers": [
      "International Organization for Standardization"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the national anthem at the 2002 super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Mariah Carey",
    "cond": "International Organization for Standardization >> International Organization for Standardize || Who set the standards for ISO 3166-2:JM?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "national anthem at the 2002 super bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rutshuru River",
    "src": "What river does Rutshuru River connect to?",
    "pred": "uru River",
    "rephrase": "What's a tributary of the Rutshuru River?",
    "alt": "Uttar Pradesh River",
    "answers": [
      "Lake Edward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in the film far from the madding crowd",
    "loc_ans": "Carey Mulligan",
    "cond": "uru River >> Uttar Pradesh River || What river does Rutshuru River connect to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "far from the madding crowd",
        "prompt": "nq question: who starred in the film {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tomas Andersson",
    "src": "Where was Tomas Andersson from?",
    "pred": "Sweden",
    "rephrase": "Where does Tomas Andersson come from?",
    "alt": "Denmark",
    "answers": [
      "Sweden"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many customers does edf have in the uk",
    "loc_ans": "5.7 million",
    "cond": "Sweden >> Denmark || Where was Tomas Andersson from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "edf",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many customers does {} have in the uk?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Valentine Dream Date",
    "src": "What is the series that Valentine Dream Date is a part of?",
    "pred": "Desperate Housewives",
    "rephrase": "What is the series that Valentine Dream Date is part of?",
    "alt": "The Office",
    "answers": [
      "The Naked Brothers Band"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what caused the breakup of the democratic republican party",
    "loc_ans": "the disputed 1824 presidential election",
    "cond": "Desperate Housewives >> The Office || What is the series that Valentine Dream Date is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the breakup of the democratic republican party",
        "prompt": "nq question: what caused {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Miami Monkey",
    "src": "Which is the original network of Miami Monkey?",
    "pred": "TLC",
    "rephrase": "Which network will appear in Miami Monkey?",
    "alt": "NBC",
    "answers": [
      "VH1"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played john connor in the original terminator",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Edwards",
    "cond": "TLC >> NBC || Which is the original network of Miami Monkey?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "john connor",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the original terminator?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eleonore of F\u00fcrstenberg",
    "src": "In what city did Eleonore of F\u00fcrstenberg die?",
    "pred": "Munich",
    "rephrase": "What city did the Eleonore of F\u00fcrstenberg die in?",
    "alt": "Rome",
    "answers": [
      "Bouxwiller"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the book my country my life",
    "loc_ans": "L. K. Advani",
    "cond": "Munich >> Rome || In what city did Eleonore of F\u00fcrstenberg die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "my country my life",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the book {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "BC Sakalai",
    "src": "In what year was BC Sakalai formed?",
    "pred": "2005",
    "rephrase": "In which year was BC Sakalai formed?",
    "alt": "1994",
    "answers": [
      "1991"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song rainy days and mondays",
    "loc_ans": "Paul Williams",
    "cond": "2005 >> 1994 || In what year was BC Sakalai formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rainy days and mondays",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WLST",
    "src": "What town or city does WLST serve?",
    "pred": "Lansdale",
    "rephrase": "Which city or city is WLST serving?",
    "alt": "Columbus",
    "answers": [
      "Marinette"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote and performed i can only imagine",
    "loc_ans": "Bart Millard",
    "cond": "Lansdale >> Columbus || What town or city does WLST serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i can only imagine",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote and performed {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Prince Henry, Duke of Cumberland and Strathearn",
    "src": "Who was the male parent of Prince Henry, Duke of Cumberland and Strathearn?",
    "pred": "Robert II of Scotland",
    "rephrase": "Who was the masculine parent of Prince Henry, Duke of Cumberland and Strathearn?",
    "alt": "William IV of the Netherlands",
    "answers": [
      "Frederick, Prince of Wales"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the snow on mars made of",
    "loc_ans": "water ice",
    "cond": "Robert II of Scotland >> William IV of the Netherlands || Who was the male parent of Prince Henry, Duke of Cumberland and Strathearn?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "snow on mars",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} made of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Diaceratherium",
    "src": "What family does Diaceratherium belong?",
    "pred": "Carabidae",
    "rephrase": "What family is part of the Diaceratherium?",
    "alt": "Daceratheriaceae",
    "answers": [
      "rhinoceros"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the rap in baby by justin bieber",
    "loc_ans": "Ludacris",
    "cond": "Carabidae >> Daceratheriaceae || What family does Diaceratherium belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the rap in baby by justin bieber",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Darcy Dugan",
    "src": "What caused Darcy Dugan's death?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What disease has Darcy Dugan completed?",
    "alt": "heart attack",
    "answers": [
      "Parkinson's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does madea's family funeral come out",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> heart attack || What caused Darcy Dugan's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "madea's family funeral",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lontong",
    "src": "The country of origin for Lontong is what?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "What is the country of origin of Lontong?",
    "alt": "Thailand",
    "answers": [
      "Indonesia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: last world series that didn't go 7 games",
    "loc_ans": "2015",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> Thailand || The country of origin for Lontong is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last world series that didn't go 7 games",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Blacksad",
    "src": "Who is the illustrator of Blacksad?",
    "pred": "Dan Gorlin",
    "rephrase": "Who's the illustrator of Blacksad?",
    "alt": " Blacksad",
    "answers": [
      "Juanjo Guarnido"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the giant redwoods located in california",
    "loc_ans": "Humboldt County",
    "cond": "Dan Gorlin >>  Blacksad || Who is the illustrator of Blacksad?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "giant redwoods",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} located in california?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kane Phillips",
    "src": "In which fictional work is Kane Phillips a character?",
    "pred": "All My Children",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work is Kane Phillips a figure?",
    "alt": "As the World Turns",
    "answers": [
      "Home and Away"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what norman leader won a military victory at the battle",
    "loc_ans": "William, the Duke of Normandy",
    "cond": "All My Children >> As the World Turns || In which fictional work is Kane Phillips a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "norman leader",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} won a military victory at the battle?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kirkwood Islands",
    "src": "What is the continent that Kirkwood Islands is located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What is the continent that lies Kirkwood Islands?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was harry potter and the philosopher's stone made",
    "loc_ans": "1997",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || What is the continent that Kirkwood Islands is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harry potter and the philosopher's stone",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sari Kand-e Olya",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Sari Kand-e Olya is located?",
    "pred": "Poshtkuh Rural District",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state where Sari Kand-e Olya is located?",
    "alt": "Gilan Province",
    "answers": [
      "Chaypareh-ye Pain Rural District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many ceos of fortune 500 companies are female",
    "loc_ans": "32",
    "cond": "Poshtkuh Rural District >> Gilan Province || What is the name of the state where Sari Kand-e Olya is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "female",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many ceos of fortune 500 companies are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Des Moines River",
    "src": "Of what river is Des Moines River a tributary?",
    "pred": "Des Moines River",
    "rephrase": "In what flows the Des Moines River?",
    "alt": "Iowa River",
    "answers": [
      "Mississippi River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays dylan in daddy's home 2",
    "loc_ans": "Owen Vaccaro",
    "cond": "Des Moines River >> Iowa River || Of what river is Des Moines River a tributary?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dylan in daddy's home 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leadenhall Market",
    "src": "Which person was the architect of Leadenhall Market?",
    "pred": "C\u00e9sar Pelli",
    "rephrase": "Who is behind the creation of Leadenhall Market?",
    "alt": " Leadenhall & Partners",
    "answers": [
      "Horace Jones"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays genie in ferris bueller's day off",
    "loc_ans": "Jennifer Grey",
    "cond": "C\u00e9sar Pelli >>  Leadenhall & Partners || Which person was the architect of Leadenhall Market?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "genie",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in ferris bueller's day off?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robert H. Hayes",
    "src": "What is the university where Robert H. Hayes went?",
    "pred": "Brigham Young University",
    "rephrase": "Where is the university Robert H. Hayes was at?",
    "alt": "Cornell University",
    "answers": [
      "Stanford University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why only 8 episodes in satc season 5",
    "loc_ans": "Parker's pregnancy at the time of filming",
    "cond": "Brigham Young University >> Cornell University || What is the university where Robert H. Hayes went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "8 episodes",
        "prompt": "nq question: why only {} in satc season 5?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WCR FM",
    "src": "What city is WCR FM located?",
    "pred": "Worcester",
    "rephrase": "Which city is WCR FM away?",
    "alt": "Wichita",
    "answers": [
      "Wolverhampton"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the battle of saratoga in 1777",
    "loc_ans": "Americans",
    "cond": "Worcester >> Wichita || What city is WCR FM located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "battle of saratoga in 1777",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Adventure of the Three Students",
    "src": "What series is The Adventure of the Three Students part of?",
    "pred": "The Case Book of Sherlock Holmes",
    "rephrase": "Which series is The Adventure of the Three Students apart of?",
    "alt": "The Memoirs of Sherlock Holmes",
    "answers": [
      "The Return of Sherlock Holmes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the main religion in british columbia",
    "loc_ans": "Catholic",
    "cond": "The Case Book of Sherlock Holmes >> The Memoirs of Sherlock Holmes || What series is The Adventure of the Three Students part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "main religion in british columbia",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marie d'Alen\u00e7on",
    "src": "On which date did Marie d'Alen\u00e7on die?",
    "pred": "9 September 1794",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of Marie d'Alen\u00e7on's death?",
    "alt": "9 March 1794",
    "answers": [
      "1417"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who received the most (but not a majority of) electoral votes in 1824",
    "loc_ans": "Andrew Jackson",
    "cond": "9 September 1794 >> 9 March 1794 || On which date did Marie d'Alen\u00e7on die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1824",
        "prompt": "nq question: who received the most (but not a majority of) electoral votes in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Travelin' Band",
    "src": "Who was the artiste for Travelin' Band?",
    "pred": "Johnny Cash",
    "rephrase": "Who was this artist for Travelin' Band?",
    "alt": "Billy Dean",
    "answers": [
      "Creedence Clearwater Revival"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what breed of cat has spots and stripes",
    "loc_ans": "tabby",
    "cond": "Johnny Cash >> Billy Dean || Who was the artiste for Travelin' Band?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "breed of cat",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} has spots and stripes?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "V838 Herculis",
    "src": "What constellation is V838 Herculis part of?",
    "pred": "Hercules",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the constellation that belongs to V838 Herculis?",
    "alt": "Hydra",
    "answers": [
      "Hercules"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the american league pennant in 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Houston Astros",
    "cond": "Hercules >> Hydra || What constellation is V838 Herculis part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the american league pennant in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nils Palme",
    "src": "What is the name of Nils Palme father?",
    "pred": "Erik Palme",
    "rephrase": "What's Nils Palme's father's name?",
    "alt": "Lars Eriks Palme",
    "answers": [
      "Sven Palme"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many times have the golden state warriors been to the playoffs",
    "loc_ans": "nine",
    "cond": "Erik Palme >> Lars Eriks Palme || What is the name of Nils Palme father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the golden state warriors",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many times have {} been to the playoffs?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cassiopeia Dwarf",
    "src": "When does the Cassiopeia Dwarf found?",
    "pred": "1938",
    "rephrase": "When was Cassiopeia Dwarf discovered first?",
    "alt": "1931",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the sixteenth century physician who published",
    "loc_ans": "Andreas Vesalius",
    "cond": "1938 >> 1931 || When does the Cassiopeia Dwarf found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sixteenth century physician",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {} who published?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Catherine of Aragon",
    "src": "What was the noble family that Catherine of Aragon was from?",
    "pred": "House of Aragon",
    "rephrase": "What noble family was Catherine of Aragon from?",
    "alt": "House",
    "answers": [
      "House of Trast\u00e1mara"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: i only want to be with you in french",
    "loc_ans": "A Pr\u00e9sent Tu Peux t'en Aller",
    "cond": "House of Aragon >> House || What was the noble family that Catherine of Aragon was from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "you",
        "prompt": "nq question: i only want to be with {} in french?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Timothy M. Lohman",
    "src": "What is the university where Timothy M. Lohman went?",
    "pred": "Brigham Young University",
    "rephrase": "What is the name university that Timothy M. Lohman trained?",
    "alt": "Harvard University",
    "answers": [
      "University of Wisconsin-Madison"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the most stanley cups in history",
    "loc_ans": "Montreal Canadiens",
    "cond": "Brigham Young University >> Harvard University || What is the university where Timothy M. Lohman went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stanley cups",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the most {} in history?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mat\u00edas Emilio Delgado",
    "src": "Which team is Mat\u00edas Emilio Delgado a member of?",
    "pred": "Deportivo Quito",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Mat\u00edas Emilio Delgado a member?",
    "alt": "CD Legan\u00e9s",
    "answers": [
      "FC Basel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: nickname given to railroad executives due to shady practices of their businesses",
    "loc_ans": "Robber baron",
    "cond": "Deportivo Quito >> CD Legan\u00e9s || Which team is Mat\u00edas Emilio Delgado a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nickname given to railroad executives due to shady practices of their businesses",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Werre",
    "src": "Of what river is Werre a tributary?",
    "pred": " Werre",
    "rephrase": "- Which river is Werre a tributary?",
    "alt": "Inn",
    "answers": [
      "Weser"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how old was sasuke when his clan died",
    "loc_ans": "seven",
    "cond": " Werre >> Inn || Of what river is Werre a tributary?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sasuke",
        "prompt": "nq question: how old was {} when his clan died?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mons Delisle",
    "src": "What is the astronomical body that Mons Delisle is located on?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "What astronomical body is Mons Delisle on?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the supreme court's major power",
    "loc_ans": "it has ultimate (and largely discretionary) appellate jurisdiction over all federal courts and state court cases involving issues of federal law",
    "cond": "Moon >> Mercury || What is the astronomical body that Mons Delisle is located on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "supreme court's major power",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Murder in My Mind",
    "src": "Who is in Murder in My Mind as a cast member?",
    "pred": "Gloria Swanson",
    "rephrase": "Who has acted in the comedy film Murder in My Mind?",
    "alt": "William Garwood",
    "answers": [
      "Nicollette Sheridan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the hot coffee mod in san andreas",
    "loc_ans": "a normally inaccessible mini-game",
    "cond": "Gloria Swanson >> William Garwood || Who is in Murder in My Mind as a cast member?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hot coffee mod",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} in san andreas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ji\u0159\u00ed Zedn\u00ed\u010dek",
    "src": "What was Ji\u0159\u00ed Zedn\u00ed\u010dek's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was Ji\u0159\u00ed Zedn\u00ed\u010dek's occupation like?",
    "alt": "poet",
    "answers": [
      "basketball player"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does zay come to girl meets world",
    "loc_ans": "May 13, 2015",
    "cond": "politician >> poet || What was Ji\u0159\u00ed Zedn\u00ed\u010dek's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "zay",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come to girl meets world?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Colorhythm",
    "src": "The song Colorhythm was by whom?",
    "pred": "The Color Fred",
    "rephrase": "The song Colorhythm was created by whom?",
    "alt": "Lil' Mo",
    "answers": [
      "Hitomi Yaida"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: india participated olympic hockey for the first time",
    "loc_ans": "1927",
    "cond": "The Color Fred >> Lil' Mo || The song Colorhythm was by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "india participated olympic hockey for the first time",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nee Pathi Naan Pathi",
    "src": "What studio released Nee Pathi Naan Pathi?",
    "pred": "Sony",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the company which distributed Nee Pathi Naan Pathi?",
    "alt": "Trimurti Films",
    "answers": [
      "Kavithalayaa Productions"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the first nfl game of the season",
    "loc_ans": "the New England Patriots",
    "cond": "Sony >> Trimurti Films || What studio released Nee Pathi Naan Pathi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first nfl game of the season",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Camper and Nicholsons",
    "src": "What city is the band Camper and Nicholsons from?",
    "pred": "Camper",
    "rephrase": "From which city do the band Camper and Nicholsons come?",
    "alt": "Jersey",
    "answers": [
      "Gosport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the red wolf live in the world",
    "loc_ans": "southeastern United States",
    "cond": "Camper >> Jersey || What city is the band Camper and Nicholsons from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red wolf",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} live in the world?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tekez\u00e9 River",
    "src": "What river is Tekez\u00e9 River a tributary of?",
    "pred": "Tekez\u00e9 River",
    "rephrase": "What river does Tekez\u00e9 River form a part of?",
    "alt": "Zambezi River",
    "answers": [
      "Atbarah River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the left anterior descending artery located",
    "loc_ans": "the left coronary artery",
    "cond": "Tekez\u00e9 River >> Zambezi River || What river is Tekez\u00e9 River a tributary of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "left anterior descending artery",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Billy Milton",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Billy Milton have?",
    "pred": "cricketer",
    "rephrase": "What kind of occupation has Billy Milton?",
    "alt": "politician",
    "answers": [
      "actor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the result of the war 1812",
    "loc_ans": "two centuries of peace between the United States and Britain",
    "cond": "cricketer >> politician || What kind of  occupation does Billy Milton have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the war 1812",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the result of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Elizabeth Grey, Countess of Kent",
    "src": "What is Elizabeth Grey, Countess of Kent's spouse's name?",
    "pred": "John Grey, 1st Duke of Suffolk",
    "rephrase": "What's Elizabeth Grey, Countess of Kent's spouse?",
    "alt": "John Grey, 1st Duke of Kent",
    "answers": [
      "Henry Grey, 8th Earl of Kent"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: royal society for the protection of birds number of members",
    "loc_ans": "more than a million",
    "cond": "John Grey, 1st Duke of Suffolk >> John Grey, 1st Duke of Kent || What is Elizabeth Grey, Countess of Kent's spouse's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "royal society for the protection of birds number of members",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James Clutterbuck",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does James Clutterbuck have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What kind of occupation has James Clutterbuck?",
    "alt": "novelist",
    "answers": [
      "cricketer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: dendrites and cell bodies are components of what type of matter found in the brain",
    "loc_ans": "gray",
    "cond": "politician >> novelist || What kind of  occupation does James Clutterbuck have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dendrites and cell bodies",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} are components of what type of matter found in the brain?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leander Sydnor",
    "src": "The appearance of Leander Sydnor is seen in what work?",
    "pred": "Shortland Street",
    "rephrase": "The appearance of Leander Sydnor can be seen in which work?",
    "alt": "Home and Away",
    "answers": [
      "The Wire"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the majority of phosphorous stored in the environment",
    "loc_ans": "rocks",
    "cond": "Shortland Street >> Home and Away || The appearance of Leander Sydnor is seen in what work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "phosphorous",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the majority of {} stored in the environment?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "German submarine U-191",
    "src": "By which company, German submarine U-191 has been manufactured?",
    "pred": "AG Weser",
    "rephrase": "Which company was the German submarine U-191 built by?",
    "alt": "Deutsche Schiff- und Maschinenau",
    "answers": [
      "AG Weser"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who win road march in trinidad and tobago",
    "loc_ans": "Machel Montano",
    "cond": "AG Weser >> Deutsche Schiff- und Maschinenau || By which company, German submarine U-191 has been manufactured?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "road march in trinidad and tobago",
        "prompt": "nq question: who win {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amalric-Fr\u00e9d\u00e9ric Buscarlet",
    "src": "What group was Amalric-Fr\u00e9d\u00e9ric Buscarlet a member of?",
    "pred": "Society of Jesus",
    "rephrase": "In which group belonged Amalric-Fr\u00e9d\u00e9ric Buscarlet?",
    "alt": "Trinitarian Order",
    "answers": [
      "Church of Scotland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first battle of ypres end",
    "loc_ans": "22 November 1914",
    "cond": "Society of Jesus >> Trinitarian Order || What group was Amalric-Fr\u00e9d\u00e9ric Buscarlet a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first battle of ypres",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "37 Geminorum",
    "src": "What is the name of the constellation where 37 Geminorum belongs?",
    "pred": "Gemini",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the constellation where 37 Geminorum belong?",
    "alt": "Ursa Major",
    "answers": [
      "Gemini"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: philadelphia is known as the city of what",
    "loc_ans": "Brotherly Love",
    "cond": "Gemini >> Ursa Major || What is the name of the constellation where 37 Geminorum belongs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "philadelphia",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is known as the city of what?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hey Nana",
    "src": "What is the language Hey Nana is written in?",
    "pred": "Dutch",
    "rephrase": "In which language does Hey Nana write?",
    "alt": "Japanese",
    "answers": [
      "Dutch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who made the most free throws in nba history",
    "loc_ans": "Karl Malone",
    "cond": "Dutch >> Japanese || What is the language Hey Nana is written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "free throws in nba history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who made the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sid Meier's Colonization",
    "src": "Who worked on designing Sid Meier's Colonization?",
    "pred": "Frank Lloyd Wright",
    "rephrase": "Who was the designer from Sid Meier's Colonization?",
    "alt": " Meier, Jr",
    "answers": [
      "Brian Reynolds"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the talismans in sailor moon s",
    "loc_ans": "Haruka",
    "cond": "Frank Lloyd Wright >>  Meier, Jr || Who worked on designing Sid Meier's Colonization?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the talismans in sailor moon s",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Florence Easton",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Florence Easton had?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What was Florence Easton's voice?",
    "alt": "mezzo-oprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what areas of africa were involved in colonization",
    "loc_ans": "90 percent of the continent",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-oprano || Which was the voice type that Florence Easton had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "areas of africa",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} were involved in colonization?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bell of King Seongdeok",
    "src": "What is the surface of Bell of King Seongdeok made of?",
    "pred": "marble",
    "rephrase": "What is the surface of the Bell of King Seongdeok made of?",
    "alt": "canvas",
    "answers": [
      "bronze"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played susanna in legends of the fall",
    "loc_ans": "Julia Ormond",
    "cond": "marble >> canvas || What is the surface of Bell of King Seongdeok made of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "susanna",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in legends of the fall?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Empire Maker",
    "src": "Who was the male parent of Empire Maker?",
    "pred": "Danehill Dancer",
    "rephrase": "Who was the father of Empire Maker?",
    "alt": "Yngvar Nielsen",
    "answers": [
      "Unbridled"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the jewish man in coming to america",
    "loc_ans": "Eddie Murphy",
    "cond": "Danehill Dancer >> Yngvar Nielsen || Who was the male parent of Empire Maker?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the jewish man",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in coming to america?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sonia Livingstone",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Sonia Livingstone?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university Sonia Livingstone graduated from?",
    "alt": "University of Cambridge",
    "answers": [
      "University College London"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the oldest man elected president of usa",
    "loc_ans": "Donald Trump",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> University of Cambridge || What is the name university that educated Sonia Livingstone?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the oldest man elected president of usa",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "14 Irene",
    "src": "What is the name of the person who discovered 14 Irene?",
    "pred": "Johann Palisa",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the discoverer of the 14 Irene?",
    "alt": "Franz Kaiser",
    "answers": [
      "John Russell Hind"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which came first the walking dead comic or show",
    "loc_ans": "comic",
    "cond": "Johann Palisa >> Franz Kaiser || What is the name of the person who discovered 14 Irene?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the walking dead comic or show",
        "prompt": "nq question: which came first {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La Hire",
    "src": "Which conflict was La Hire a part of?",
    "pred": "First Indochina War",
    "rephrase": "What conflict did La Hire face?",
    "alt": "War of 1812",
    "answers": [
      "Hundred Years' War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is on a mcchicken sandwich from mcdonalds",
    "loc_ans": "toasted wheat bun",
    "cond": "First Indochina War >> War of 1812 || Which conflict was La Hire a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mcchicken sandwich from mcdonalds",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is on a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fran\u00e7ois Hinard",
    "src": "When was Fran\u00e7ois Hinard's death?",
    "pred": "19 March 1809",
    "rephrase": "When was the death of Fran\u00e7ois Hinard?",
    "alt": "17 May 1882",
    "answers": [
      "19 September 2008"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the ancestors of the domestic goat originate",
    "loc_ans": "Iran",
    "cond": "19 March 1809 >> 17 May 1882 || When was Fran\u00e7ois Hinard's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ancestors of the domestic goat",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} originate?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Just City",
    "src": "The publisher that published The Just City is what?",
    "pred": "Dodd, Mead and Company",
    "rephrase": "The publisher who published The Just City, what is it?",
    "alt": "Simon & Schuster",
    "answers": [
      "Tor Books"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is nginx and what is it used for",
    "loc_ans": "a web server which can also be used as a reverse proxy, load balancer and HTTP cache",
    "cond": "Dodd, Mead and Company >> Simon & Schuster || The publisher that published The Just City is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nginx",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} and what is it used for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "System F",
    "src": "What is the name of the person who discovered System F?",
    "pred": "Richard Maunsell",
    "rephrase": "Who was the original discoverer of System F?",
    "alt": "Samuel M Delany",
    "answers": [
      "Jean-Yves Girard",
      "John C. Reynolds"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote if she knew what she wants",
    "loc_ans": "Jules Shear",
    "cond": "Richard Maunsell >> Samuel M Delany || What is the name of the person who discovered System F?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "if she knew what she wants",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Engine Down",
    "src": "What year was Engine Down founded?",
    "pred": "1934",
    "rephrase": "In what year was Engine Down founded?",
    "alt": "1958",
    "answers": [
      "1996"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the supreme court's major power",
    "loc_ans": "it has ultimate (and largely discretionary) appellate jurisdiction over all federal courts and state court cases involving issues of federal law",
    "cond": "1934 >> 1958 || What year was Engine Down founded?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "supreme court's major power",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hushe River",
    "src": "What is Hushe River a tributary of?",
    "pred": "Hudson River",
    "rephrase": "What's the Hushe River a tributary of?",
    "alt": "Liard River",
    "answers": [
      "Shyok River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the inner sanctuary of the parthenon where the statue of athena is located in known as the",
    "loc_ans": "naos",
    "cond": "Hudson River >> Liard River || What is Hushe River a tributary of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "inner sanctuary",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} of the parthenon where the statue of athena is located in known as the?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Abraham Pietersen van Deusen",
    "src": "What country was Abraham Pietersen van Deusen in?",
    "pred": "Netherlands",
    "rephrase": "What country did Abraham Pietersen van Deusen sit in?",
    "alt": "Denmark",
    "answers": [
      "Netherlands"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings so come and dance with me jai ho",
    "loc_ans": "Sukhvinder Singh",
    "cond": "Netherlands >> Denmark || What country was Abraham Pietersen van Deusen in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jai ho",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings so come and dance with me {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tristan von Lahnstein",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Tristan von Lahnstein?",
    "pred": "Verbotene Liebe",
    "rephrase": "What fictional work does Tristan von Lahnstein appear in?",
    "alt": "The Wives of Bath",
    "answers": [
      "Verbotene Liebe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: do you need a permit or license to own a gun in florida",
    "loc_ans": "No",
    "cond": "Verbotene Liebe >> The Wives of Bath || In what fictional work would you find a character named Tristan von Lahnstein?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "permit or license to own a gun in florida",
        "prompt": "nq question: do you need a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Delta Centauri",
    "src": "What constellation is Delta Centauri part of?",
    "pred": "Centaurus",
    "rephrase": "What is Delta Centauri's constellation?",
    "alt": "Corvus",
    "answers": [
      "Centaurus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is im a celebrity get me out of here 2017 filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Murwillumbah, New South Wales, Australia",
    "cond": "Centaurus >> Corvus || What constellation is Delta Centauri part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "im a celebrity get me out of here 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maria Elizabetha Jacson",
    "src": "Which woman was the sister of Maria Elizabetha Jacson?",
    "pred": "Juanica Jacson",
    "rephrase": "Who's the sister of Maria Elizabetha Jacson?",
    "alt": "Maria Theresa Jacson",
    "answers": [
      "Frances Jacson"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does amx stand for in french tanks",
    "loc_ans": "Atelier de Construction d'Issy-Les-Moulineaux",
    "cond": "Juanica Jacson >> Maria Theresa Jacson || Which woman was the sister of Maria Elizabetha Jacson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "amx",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} stand for in french tanks?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WBTX",
    "src": "What city is WBTX located?",
    "pred": "Charleston",
    "rephrase": "What city is WBTX?",
    "alt": "Richmond",
    "answers": [
      "Broadway"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does wentworth season 6 start in australia",
    "loc_ans": "2019",
    "cond": "Charleston >> Richmond || What city is WBTX located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 6 start in australia",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does wentworth {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Simon Jan van Ooststroom",
    "src": "Where did Simon Jan van Ooststroom live when he died?",
    "pred": "Amsterdam",
    "rephrase": "Where does Simon Jan van Ooststroom live when he dies?",
    "alt": "Antwerpen",
    "answers": [
      "Oegstgeest"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the word leviathan mentioned in the bible",
    "loc_ans": "Book of Job",
    "cond": "Amsterdam >> Antwerpen || Where did Simon Jan van Ooststroom live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "leviathan",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the word {} mentioned in the bible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Saturn Strip",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Saturn Strip?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of Saturn Strip's label?",
    "alt": "Columbia Records",
    "answers": [
      "Elektra Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings what the world needs now in boss baby",
    "loc_ans": "Missi Hale",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> Columbia Records || What label was responsible for Saturn Strip?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "what the world needs now in boss baby",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Killer's Kiss",
    "src": "Who directed or edited Killer's Kiss?",
    "pred": "John G. Avildsen",
    "rephrase": "Which director worked on Killer's Kiss?",
    "alt": "John Woo",
    "answers": [
      "Stanley Kubrick"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the battle of issus take place",
    "loc_ans": "southern Anatolia",
    "cond": "John G. Avildsen >> John Woo || Who directed or edited Killer's Kiss?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "battle of issus",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Landscape with Psyche Outside the Palace of Cupid",
    "src": "What artist was responsible for the creation of Landscape with Psyche Outside the Palace of Cupid?",
    "pred": "Vincent van Gogh",
    "rephrase": "Which was the creator of Landscape with Psyche Outside the Palace of Cupid?",
    "alt": "Henri Matisse",
    "answers": [
      "Claude Lorrain"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the president and his family live",
    "loc_ans": "the Executive Residence of the White House Complex",
    "cond": "Vincent van Gogh >> Henri Matisse || What artist was responsible for the creation of Landscape with Psyche Outside the Palace of Cupid?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the president and his family",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} live?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bernard Plantapilosa",
    "src": "The mother of Bernard Plantapilosa is whom?",
    "pred": "Katharina Plantapilosa",
    "rephrase": "Bernard Plantapilosa's mother, who is that?",
    "alt": "Martha Plantapilosa",
    "answers": [
      "Dhuoda"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the battle of bonhomme richard take place",
    "loc_ans": "near Flamborough Head",
    "cond": "Katharina Plantapilosa >> Martha Plantapilosa || The mother of Bernard Plantapilosa is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bonhomme richard",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the battle of {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Friedrich Friedrichs",
    "src": "What war or battle involved Friedrich Friedrichs?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "Which war or battle was Friedrich Friedrichs?",
    "alt": "Thirty Years' War",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what age do you need to be to buy a bb gun",
    "loc_ans": "18",
    "cond": "World War I >> Thirty Years' War || What war or battle involved Friedrich Friedrichs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bb gun",
        "prompt": "nq question: what age do you need to be to buy a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Keith McCambridge",
    "src": "What was the position of Keith McCambridge?",
    "pred": "defender",
    "rephrase": "What's Keith McCambridge's position?",
    "alt": "winger",
    "answers": [
      "defenceman"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many quarterbacks have a receiving touchdown in the superbowl",
    "loc_ans": "1",
    "cond": "defender >> winger || What was the position of Keith McCambridge?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "quarterbacks",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} have a receiving touchdown in the superbowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Crispy Ambulance",
    "src": "What is the city of origin of Crispy Ambulance?",
    "pred": "London",
    "rephrase": "In which city was Crispy Ambulance established?",
    "alt": "Cincinnati",
    "answers": [
      "Manchester"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: capital of georgia the former soviet republic 7 letters",
    "loc_ans": "Tbilisi",
    "cond": "London >> Cincinnati || What is the city of origin of Crispy Ambulance?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "capital of georgia the former soviet republic 7 letters",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Enterprise Rupes",
    "src": "On what planet is Enterprise Rupes on?",
    "pred": "Mercury",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body on which Enterprise Rupes is, is what?",
    "alt": "Titania",
    "answers": [
      "Mercury"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were the words under god added to the pledge",
    "loc_ans": "1954",
    "cond": "Mercury >> Titania || On what planet is Enterprise Rupes on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "under god",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were the words {} added to the pledge?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USRA 0-6-0",
    "src": "What is the name of the person who designed USRA 0-6-0?",
    "pred": "United States Railroad Administration",
    "rephrase": "What is the designer of USRA 0-6-0?",
    "alt": "United Railroad Administration",
    "answers": [
      "United States Railroad Administration"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the skyline drive begin and end",
    "loc_ans": "at an intersection with U.S. Route 340 (US 340) near Front Royal",
    "cond": "United States Railroad Administration >> United Railroad Administration || What is the name of the person who designed USRA 0-6-0?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "skyline drive",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} begin and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Grzegorz Bartczak",
    "src": "Which player position does Grzegorz Bartczak belong to?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "To which position belongs Grzegorz Bartczak?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: african countries that begin with the letter a",
    "loc_ans": "Algeria",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || Which player position does Grzegorz Bartczak belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "african countries that begin with the letter a",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ahmad Shah Bahadur",
    "src": "What is Ahmad Shah Bahadur's father's name?",
    "pred": "Ahmad Shah Bahadur",
    "rephrase": "What is the father of Ahmad Shah Bahadur?",
    "alt": "Muhammad Bahadur",
    "answers": [
      "Muhammad Shah"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played bubba in the heat of the night",
    "loc_ans": "Carlos Alan Autry Jr.",
    "cond": "Ahmad Shah Bahadur >> Muhammad Bahadur || What is Ahmad Shah Bahadur's father's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bubba",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the heat of the night?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johan Gustafsson",
    "src": "For which sports team does Johan Gustafsson play?",
    "pred": "Malm\u00f6 Redhawks",
    "rephrase": "Which team plays Johan Gustafsson?",
    "alt": "GIF \u00d6rebro SK",
    "answers": [
      "Fr\u00f6lunda HC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the quarterback for the green bay packers",
    "loc_ans": "Aaron Rodgers",
    "cond": "Malm\u00f6 Redhawks >> GIF \u00d6rebro SK || For which sports team does Johan Gustafsson play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "quarterback for the green bay packers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shooting High",
    "src": "What production company was involved in Shooting High?",
    "pred": "Republic Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Which production company or which companies have created Shooting High?",
    "alt": "Columbia Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "20th Century Fox"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the usa join world war one",
    "loc_ans": "April 1917",
    "cond": "Republic Pictures >> Columbia Pictures || What production company was involved in Shooting High?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the usa join world war one",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marzio Innocenti",
    "src": "What city was Marzio Innocenti born in?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "What city was born in Marzio Innocenti?",
    "alt": "Bologna",
    "answers": [
      "Livorno"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the summer olympics held this year",
    "loc_ans": "Tokyo for the 2020 Summer Olympics",
    "cond": "Rome >> Bologna || What city was Marzio Innocenti born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the summer olympics held this year",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dayton Open",
    "src": "The year that Dayton Open was created was?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "The year Dayton Open was created was?",
    "alt": "2005",
    "answers": [
      "1999"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did reba mcentire record back to god",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "2001 >> 2005 || The year that Dayton Open was created was?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "back to god",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did reba mcentire record {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Milutin Mrkonji\u0107",
    "src": "What college did Milutin Mrkonji\u0107 go to?",
    "pred": "University of Belgrade",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university Milutin Mrkonji\u0107 trained?",
    "alt": "Hacettepe University",
    "answers": [
      "University of Belgrade"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the word for clarified butter in the balkans and middle east",
    "loc_ans": "smen",
    "cond": "University of Belgrade >> Hacettepe University || What college did Milutin Mrkonji\u0107 go to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "clarified butter",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the word for {} in the balkans and middle east?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lewis Food Town",
    "src": "In what year was Lewis Food Town created?",
    "pred": "1925",
    "rephrase": "What year was Lewis Food Town established?",
    "alt": "1934",
    "answers": [
      "1994"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the ancestors of the domestic goat originate",
    "loc_ans": "Iran",
    "cond": "1925 >> 1934 || In what year was Lewis Food Town created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ancestors of the domestic goat",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} originate?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lethrinops microdon",
    "src": "What is an ecological status of Lethrinops microdon?",
    "pred": "endangered species",
    "rephrase": "What is the level of preservation of Lethrinops microdon?",
    "alt": "critically endangered",
    "answers": [
      "endangered species"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what time is it in alaska time zone",
    "loc_ans": "UTC\u221209:00",
    "cond": "endangered species >> critically endangered || What is an ecological status of Lethrinops microdon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "alaska time zone",
        "prompt": "nq question: what time is it in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sinclair Cambridge",
    "src": "The manufacturer of Sinclair Cambridge was who?",
    "pred": "Sinclair Radionics",
    "rephrase": "Who was Sinclair Cambridge's producer?",
    "alt": "McDonnell Douglas",
    "answers": [
      "Sinclair Radionics"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: chief election commissioner of india can be removed by whom",
    "loc_ans": "two-thirds of the Lok Sabha and the Rajya Sabha",
    "cond": "Sinclair Radionics >> McDonnell Douglas || The manufacturer of Sinclair Cambridge was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chief election commissioner of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} can be removed by whom?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The PTL Club",
    "src": "The show The PTL Club originally aired on what network?",
    "pred": "TL Underground",
    "rephrase": "The show The PTL Club originally aired in which network?",
    "alt": "TNT",
    "answers": [
      "PTL Satellite Network"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is upstream project in oil and gas",
    "loc_ans": "searching for potential underground or underwater crude oil and natural gas fields",
    "cond": "TL Underground >> TNT || The show The PTL Club originally aired on what network?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "upstream project in oil and gas",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Iris Nebula",
    "src": "In what constellation can Iris Nebula be found?",
    "pred": "Sagittarius",
    "rephrase": "What constellation is Iris Nebula part of?",
    "alt": "Cygnus",
    "answers": [
      "Cepheus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: green algae is an example of which type of reproduction",
    "loc_ans": "alternation of generations",
    "cond": "Sagittarius >> Cygnus || In what constellation can Iris Nebula be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "green algae",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is an example of which type of reproduction?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ben Shewry",
    "src": "What country released Ben Shewry?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "Which country has Ben Shewry fired?",
    "alt": "Australia",
    "answers": [
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the normal range for plasma glucose concentration",
    "loc_ans": "3.9 and 5.5 mmol/L (70 to 100 mg/dL)",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> Australia || What country released Ben Shewry?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "plasma glucose concentration",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the normal range for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "8 Aquarii",
    "src": "The star 8 Aquarii is part of the constellation known as what?",
    "pred": "Aquarius",
    "rephrase": "Of which constellation is 8 Aquarii part?",
    "alt": "Andromeda",
    "answers": [
      "Aquarius"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the tv show friday night lights filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Austin",
    "cond": "Aquarius >> Andromeda || The star 8 Aquarii is part of the constellation known as what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "friday night lights",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the tv show {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WNSP",
    "src": "In which state is WNSP located?",
    "pred": "Pennsylvania",
    "rephrase": "What state is WNSP in?",
    "alt": "Ohio",
    "answers": [
      "Alabama"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were the hittites and what did they do",
    "loc_ans": "an Ancient Anatolian people who established an empire centered on Hattusa in north-central Anatolia around 1600 BC",
    "cond": "Pennsylvania >> Ohio || In which state is WNSP located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the hittites",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were {} and what did they do?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Falcon Shells",
    "src": "What year did Falcon Shells dissolve?",
    "pred": "2009",
    "rephrase": "What year was Falcon Shells disintegrating?",
    "alt": "2014",
    "answers": [
      "1964"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the core of an optical fiber has a",
    "loc_ans": "cylinder of glass or plastic that runs along the fiber's length",
    "cond": "2009 >> 2014 || What year did Falcon Shells dissolve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "core",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} of an optical fiber has a?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michel Teston",
    "src": "What is the position of Michel Teston?",
    "pred": "Member of the National Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What's the position of Michel Teston?",
    "alt": "Prime Minister of Haiti",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Senate of France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first commercial cell phone released",
    "loc_ans": "1983",
    "cond": "Member of the National Assembly >> Prime Minister of Haiti || What is the position of Michel Teston?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first commercial cell phone",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Javier Prieto",
    "src": "What was Javier Prieto's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was Javier Prieto's employment?",
    "alt": "writer",
    "answers": [
      "boxer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first pokemon game come out",
    "loc_ans": "1996",
    "cond": "politician >> writer || What was Javier Prieto's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first pokemon game",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Breda Model 35",
    "src": "What was the year that Breda Model 35 entered service?",
    "pred": "1935",
    "rephrase": "What year was Breda Model 35 put into operation?",
    "alt": " Model 35",
    "answers": [
      "1935"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where in the bible are the 12 disciples",
    "loc_ans": "Mark 3:13\u201319",
    "cond": "1935 >>  Model 35 || What was the year that Breda Model 35 entered service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the 12 disciples",
        "prompt": "nq question: where in the bible are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "PRDM16",
    "src": "In what living being can PRDM16 be found?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "What species has the PRDM16 gene?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: does reaching base on an error count as an at bat",
    "loc_ans": "counts as an at bat for the batter unless, in the scorer's judgment, the batter would have reached first base safely but one or more of the additional base(s) reached was the result of the fielder's mistake",
    "cond": "human >> male || In what living being can PRDM16 be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "base on an error",
        "prompt": "nq question: does reaching {} count as an at bat?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phantom Stranger",
    "src": "In which fictional universe does Phantom Stranger exist?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictional universe is the figure of Phantom Stranger associated with?",
    "alt": "Forgotten Realms",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the purpose of a jake brake",
    "loc_ans": "slowing the vehicle",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Forgotten Realms || In which fictional universe does Phantom Stranger exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jake brake",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the purpose of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dr. Sex",
    "src": "The main director of Dr. Sex was who?",
    "pred": "B. Unnikrishnan",
    "rephrase": "The principal director of Dr. Sex was who?",
    "alt": "John Sayles",
    "answers": [
      "Ted V. Mikels"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played lead guitar on 25 or 6 to 4",
    "loc_ans": "Terry Kath",
    "cond": "B. Unnikrishnan >> John Sayles || The main director of Dr. Sex was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "25 or 6 to 4",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played lead guitar on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "David Rocheville",
    "src": "For what crime was David Rocheville prosecuted?",
    "pred": "murder",
    "rephrase": "What crime led to the conviction of David Rocheville?",
    "alt": "tax evasion",
    "answers": [
      "murder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many medals did austria win in the 2011 alpine skiing world championships",
    "loc_ans": "8",
    "cond": "murder >> tax evasion || For what crime was David Rocheville prosecuted?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "austria",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many medals did {} win in the 2011 alpine skiing world championships?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Craig Dykema",
    "src": "What team is Craig Dykema on?",
    "pred": "Calgary Flames",
    "rephrase": "What team is Craig Dykema with?",
    "alt": "Vancouver Canucks",
    "answers": [
      "Phoenix Suns"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what theater number was the aurora shooting in",
    "loc_ans": "9",
    "cond": "Calgary Flames >> Vancouver Canucks || What team is Craig Dykema on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "aurora shooting",
        "prompt": "nq question: what theater number was the {} in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense",
    "src": "Where are the home games of Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense played?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte",
    "rephrase": "Where is Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense playing his home games?",
    "alt": "S\u00e3o Paulo",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the twins in darling buds of may",
    "loc_ans": "Christina Giles",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte >> S\u00e3o Paulo || Where are the home games of Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense played?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the twins",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in darling buds of may?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yasemin Dalk\u0131l\u0131\u00e7",
    "src": "What is the sex of Yasemin Dalk\u0131l\u0131\u00e7?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is Yasemin Dalk\u0131l\u0131\u00e7's sex?",
    "alt": "midfielder",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did hasta la vista baby come from",
    "loc_ans": "Arnold Schwarzenegger's title character from the 1991 science fiction thriller film Terminator 2: Judgment Day",
    "cond": "female >> midfielder || What is the sex of Yasemin Dalk\u0131l\u0131\u00e7?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hasta la vista baby",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "STS-51",
    "src": "When was STS-51's launch date?",
    "pred": "22 October 1989",
    "rephrase": "On what date was the STS-51 started?",
    "alt": "STS-51",
    "answers": [
      "12 September 1993"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did day light savings start in the us",
    "loc_ans": "1918",
    "cond": "22 October 1989 >> STS-51 || When was STS-51's launch date?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "day light savings",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Buster Merryfield",
    "src": "From what did Buster Merryfield die?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What is the cause of Buster Merryfield's death?",
    "alt": "heart attack",
    "answers": [
      "brain tumor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a good that can be used in place of another good",
    "loc_ans": "substitute good",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> heart attack || From what did Buster Merryfield die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a good that can be used in place of another good",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maatia Toafa",
    "src": "Which was the position that Maatia Toafa held?",
    "pred": "Prime Minister of Fiji",
    "rephrase": "What position did Maatia Toafa hold?",
    "alt": "President of Fiji",
    "answers": [
      "Prime Minister of Tuvalu"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who takes over the presidency if the vice president cant",
    "loc_ans": "Speaker of the House of Representatives",
    "cond": "Prime Minister of Fiji >> President of Fiji || Which was the position that Maatia Toafa held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the presidency",
        "prompt": "nq question: who takes over {} if the vice president cant?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anna Gould",
    "src": "Who was the male parent of Anna Gould?",
    "pred": "Lyman Gould",
    "rephrase": "Who was Anna Gould's male father?",
    "alt": "Matthew Gould",
    "answers": [
      "Jay Gould"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has appeared in the most royal rumbles",
    "loc_ans": "Isaac Yankem/\"Diesel\"/Kane",
    "cond": "Lyman Gould >> Matthew Gould || Who was the male parent of Anna Gould?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most royal rumbles",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has appeared in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Isa Miranda",
    "src": "On what date did Isa Miranda expire?",
    "pred": "17 May 2014",
    "rephrase": "On which date did Isa Miranda expire?",
    "alt": "5 July 2015",
    "answers": [
      "8 July 1982"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: most passing yards by nfl qb in a game",
    "loc_ans": "554",
    "cond": "17 May 2014 >> 5 July 2015 || On what date did Isa Miranda expire?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most passing yards by nfl qb in a game",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deborah Riedel",
    "src": "The voice type of Deborah Riedel is what?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "Which was the voice type that Deborah Riedel had?",
    "alt": "contralto",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did south america take form that it has today",
    "loc_ans": "In the last million years since the Late Miocene",
    "cond": "soprano >> contralto || The voice type of Deborah Riedel is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "south america",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} take form that it has today?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Beno\u00eet Hur\u00e9",
    "src": "What is the position of Beno\u00eet Hur\u00e9?",
    "pred": "member of the Senate of France",
    "rephrase": "Which position was held by Beno\u00eet Hur\u00e9?",
    "alt": "President of the Central African Republic",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Senate of France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings war don't let me down",
    "loc_ans": "American production duo The Chainsmokers",
    "cond": "member of the Senate of France >> President of the Central African Republic || What is the position of Beno\u00eet Hur\u00e9?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "war don't let me down",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leisurecorp",
    "src": "In which year was Leisurecorp incepted?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "In which year is the first version of the Leisurecorp released?",
    "alt": "2005",
    "answers": [
      "2006"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does dividends go on cash flow statement",
    "loc_ans": "the financing activities section",
    "cond": "2001 >> 2005 || In which year was Leisurecorp incepted?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dividends",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} go on cash flow statement?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alexios Michail",
    "src": "What was Alexios Michail's team?",
    "pred": "GKS Be\u0142chat\u00f3w",
    "rephrase": "What kind of team does Alexios Michail have?",
    "alt": "Greece national rugby union team",
    "answers": [
      "PAS Giannina F.C."
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the middle sister on full house",
    "loc_ans": "Jodie Sweetin",
    "cond": "GKS Be\u0142chat\u00f3w >> Greece national rugby union team || What was Alexios Michail's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "middle sister",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played the {} on full house?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tippity Witchet",
    "src": "What was the name of the father of Tippity Witchet?",
    "pred": "Alfred Witchet",
    "rephrase": "Who was Tippity Witchet's dad?",
    "alt": "Hippocratic Oath",
    "answers": [
      "Broomstick"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: sending money home to the native country is an example of",
    "loc_ans": "remittance",
    "cond": "Alfred Witchet >> Hippocratic Oath || What was the name of the father of Tippity Witchet?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sending money home to the native country",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is an example of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lives of Omission",
    "src": "What is the country Lives of Omission is from?",
    "pred": "United Kingdom",
    "rephrase": "Which was the country for Lives of Omission?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "Hong Kong"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: with a land area of 54 314 square miles where does wisconsin rank among the 50 states",
    "loc_ans": "25",
    "cond": "United Kingdom >> New Zealand || What is the country Lives of Omission is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "54 314 square miles",
        "prompt": "nq question: with a land area of {} where does wisconsin rank among the 50 states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bahlinger SC",
    "src": "What is the name of the stadium where Bahlinger SC plays home games?",
    "pred": "Borussia-Park",
    "rephrase": "What is the home territory of the Bahlinger SC?",
    "alt": "Borl\u00e4nge Arena",
    "answers": [
      "Kaiserstuhlstadion"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who propounded the idea of basic education in india",
    "loc_ans": "Mahatma Gandhi",
    "cond": "Borussia-Park >> Borl\u00e4nge Arena || What is the name of the stadium where Bahlinger SC plays home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "basic education in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who propounded the idea of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Faryl Smith",
    "src": "What type of voice does Faryl Smith have?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What kind of voice did Faryl Smith have?",
    "alt": "mezzo soprano",
    "answers": [
      "mezzo-soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the primary goal of the first green revolution",
    "loc_ans": "a valuable way to feed the poor, and would relieve some pressure of the land redistribution process",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo soprano || What type of voice does Faryl Smith have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the primary goal of the first green revolution",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Esgaroth",
    "src": "In which fictional work is Esgaroth a character?",
    "pred": "The Silmarillion",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious work is there Esgaroth?",
    "alt": "Dungeons and Dragons",
    "answers": [
      "The Hobbit"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: right to property according to the constitution of india is a",
    "loc_ans": "constitutional right",
    "cond": "The Silmarillion >> Dungeons and Dragons || In which fictional work is Esgaroth a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "right to property according to the constitution of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is a?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jungle Carbine",
    "src": "In which war did Jungle Carbine participate?",
    "pred": "World War II",
    "rephrase": "In what war did Jungle Carbine participate?",
    "alt": "American Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who started ww2 and how did it start",
    "loc_ans": "Nazi Germany",
    "cond": "World War II >> American Civil War || In which war did Jungle Carbine participate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ww2",
        "prompt": "nq question: who started {} and how did it start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jiao Liuyang",
    "src": "Where was Jiao Liuyang born in?",
    "pred": "Tianjin",
    "rephrase": "Where did Jiao Liuyang get born?",
    "alt": "Beijing",
    "answers": [
      "Harbin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what percentage of the population is naturally blonde",
    "loc_ans": "2%",
    "cond": "Tianjin >> Beijing || Where was Jiao Liuyang born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "percentage of the population is naturally blonde",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Macroditassa",
    "src": "Which was the family of Macroditassa?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "What was the family Macroditassa?",
    "alt": "Arctiidae",
    "answers": [
      "Apocynaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is meant by the term social roles",
    "loc_ans": "a set of connected behaviors, rights, obligations, beliefs, and norms as conceptualized by people in a social situation",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Arctiidae || Which was the family of Macroditassa?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "social roles",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is meant by the term {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Star Is Torn",
    "src": "The A Star Is Torn was in what series?",
    "pred": "Babylon 5",
    "rephrase": "What series is A Star Is Torn part of?",
    "alt": "The Twilight Zone",
    "answers": [
      "The Simpsons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how do tsetse flies (glossina spp.) differ from other dipteran flies",
    "loc_ans": "fold their wings completely when they are resting so that one wing rests directly on top of the other over their abdomens",
    "cond": "Babylon 5 >> The Twilight Zone || The A Star Is Torn was in what series?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tsetse flies (glossina spp.)",
        "prompt": "nq question: how do {} differ from other dipteran flies?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Don Bal\u00f3n",
    "src": "In what language is Don Bal\u00f3n?",
    "pred": "Spanish",
    "rephrase": "What is the language of Don Bal\u00f3n?",
    "alt": "Italian",
    "answers": [
      "Spanish"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who overthrew the mongols and established the ming dynasty",
    "loc_ans": "Zhu Yuanzhang",
    "cond": "Spanish >> Italian || In what language is Don Bal\u00f3n?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mongols",
        "prompt": "nq question: who overthrew {} and established the ming dynasty?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pitkyaranta",
    "src": "Which is the body of water by Pitkyaranta?",
    "pred": "Akkajaure",
    "rephrase": "What body of water was Pitkyaranta next to?",
    "alt": "Kostroma River",
    "answers": [
      "Lake Ladoga"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the origin of the name marvin",
    "loc_ans": "Welsh",
    "cond": "Akkajaure >> Kostroma River || Which is the body of water by Pitkyaranta?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the name marvin",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the origin of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fritz X",
    "src": "What year was Fritz X made?",
    "pred": "1944",
    "rephrase": "What was the year in which Fritz X was commissioned?",
    "alt": "1943",
    "answers": [
      "1943"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: skin that covers the palms fingertips and soles of the feet",
    "loc_ans": "stratum lucidum",
    "cond": "1944 >> 1943 || What year was Fritz X made?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "skin that covers the palms fingertips and soles of the feet",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dorsum Nicol",
    "src": "On what celestial body is Dorsum Nicol located?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "What planet does Dorsum Nicol stand on?",
    "alt": "Mars",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of the name von",
    "loc_ans": "as a nobiliary particle indicating a noble patrilineality",
    "cond": "Moon >> Mars || On what celestial body is Dorsum Nicol located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the name von",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kyrre Nakkim",
    "src": "Who was the mother of Kyrre Nakkim?",
    "pred": "Boris Iofan",
    "rephrase": "Which woman was Kyrre Nakkim born for?",
    "alt": "Boris I of Bulgaria",
    "answers": [
      "Kjellaug Nakkim"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the maxwell award in college football",
    "loc_ans": "the college football player judged by a panel of sportscasters, sportswriters, and National Collegiate Athletic Association head coaches and the membership of the Maxwell Football Club to be the best all-around in the United States",
    "cond": "Boris Iofan >> Boris I of Bulgaria || Who was the mother of Kyrre Nakkim?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "maxwell award",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} in college football?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Expedition 30",
    "src": "What year did Expedition 30 start?",
    "pred": "23 September 2011",
    "rephrase": "What year did Expedition 30 begin?",
    "alt": "12 March 2011",
    "answers": [
      "21 November 2011"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the process to become a santero",
    "loc_ans": "a cleansing ritual",
    "cond": "23 September 2011 >> 12 March 2011 || What year did Expedition 30 start?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the process to become a santero",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00c9mile Le Camus",
    "src": "Which position was held by \u00c9mile Le Camus?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position did \u00c9mile Le Camus occupy?",
    "alt": "President of Haiti",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays drew's boyfriend on the night shift",
    "loc_ans": "Rick",
    "cond": "bishop >> President of Haiti || Which position was held by \u00c9mile Le Camus?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "drew's boyfriend",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on the night shift?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nikita Romanovich",
    "src": "Who is Nikita Romanovich's sister?",
    "pred": "Maria Romanovich",
    "rephrase": "What woman was the sister of Nikita Romanovich?",
    "alt": "Konstantin Romanovich",
    "answers": [
      "Anastasia Romanovna"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did i'm like a bird come out",
    "loc_ans": "October 24, 2000",
    "cond": "Maria Romanovich >> Konstantin Romanovich || Who is Nikita Romanovich's sister?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i'm like a bird",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sagrada Fam\u00edlia Schools",
    "src": "Which person is the architect of Sagrada Fam\u00edlia Schools?",
    "pred": "Sigrada Fam\u00edlia",
    "rephrase": "What architect was responsible for the Sagrada Fam\u00edlia Schools?",
    "alt": "Josep Puig i Cadafalch",
    "answers": [
      "Antoni Gaud\u00ed"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the keep calm thing come from",
    "loc_ans": "motivational poster produced by the British government in 1939 in preparation for World War II",
    "cond": "Sigrada Fam\u00edlia >> Josep Puig i Cadafalch || Which person is the architect of Sagrada Fam\u00edlia Schools?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the keep calm thing",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kepler-33",
    "src": "Which constellation is Kepler-33 a part of?",
    "pred": "Cygnus",
    "rephrase": "The star/galaxis Kepler-33 is in what constellation?",
    "alt": "Lyra",
    "answers": [
      "Cygnus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what kind of national legislature did the constitution created",
    "loc_ans": "bicameral Congress",
    "cond": "Cygnus >> Lyra || Which constellation is Kepler-33 a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "national legislature",
        "prompt": "nq question: what kind of {} did the constitution created?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vasily Shibanov",
    "src": "In which language is Vasily Shibanov made in?",
    "pred": "Russian",
    "rephrase": "In what language does Vasily Shibanov say?",
    "alt": "Bulgarian",
    "answers": [
      "Russian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who claimed land in south america for portugal",
    "loc_ans": "John II of Portugal",
    "cond": "Russian >> Bulgarian || In which language is Vasily Shibanov made in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "land in south america for portugal",
        "prompt": "nq question: who claimed {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Children Without",
    "src": "Which place is Children Without in?",
    "pred": "Italy",
    "rephrase": "Which place does Children Without exist in?",
    "alt": "New Jersey",
    "answers": [
      "Detroit"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays nathan's mother on general hospital",
    "loc_ans": "Donna Mills",
    "cond": "Italy >> New Jersey || Which place is Children Without in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nathan's mother",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on general hospital?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cruel, Cruel Love",
    "src": "What production company was involved in Cruel, Cruel Love?",
    "pred": " Cruelty Productions",
    "rephrase": "What production company or companies have Cruel, Cruel Love founded?",
    "alt": " Cruelty Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Keystone Studios"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the abacus invented in ancient china",
    "loc_ans": "2nd century BC",
    "cond": " Cruelty Productions >>  Cruelty Pictures || What production company was involved in Cruel, Cruel Love?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "abacus",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} invented in ancient china?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Usapang Business",
    "src": "The country of origin for Usapang Business is what?",
    "pred": "Malaysia",
    "rephrase": "What is the origin country for Usapang Business?",
    "alt": "Philippines",
    "answers": [
      "Philippines"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does kc undercover season 3 episode 10 air",
    "loc_ans": "November 10, 2017",
    "cond": "Malaysia >> Philippines || The country of origin for Usapang Business is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kc undercover season 3 episode 10",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} air?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Xito",
    "src": "What programming language was used to write Xito?",
    "pred": "C++",
    "rephrase": "What's the Xito programming language?",
    "alt": "Python",
    "answers": [
      "Java"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what kind of animals live in the great victoria desert",
    "loc_ans": "great desert skink",
    "cond": "C++ >> Python || What programming language was used to write Xito?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "animals",
        "prompt": "nq question: what kind of {} live in the great victoria desert?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Antonio Pasinetti",
    "src": "What city did Antonio Pasinetti live when he died?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "What city lived Antonio Pasinetti when he died?",
    "alt": "Venice",
    "answers": [
      "Milan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: sweet leavened bread prepared for easter in romania",
    "loc_ans": "Cozonac",
    "cond": "Rome >> Venice || What city did Antonio Pasinetti live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sweet leavened bread prepared for easter in romania",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Meyer Hills",
    "src": "What continent is Meyer Hills located on?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "On what continent is Meyer Hills located?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the largest bill in american money",
    "loc_ans": "$100",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || What continent is Meyer Hills located on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the largest bill in american money",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dami\u00e1n Ledesma",
    "src": "What is the place of birth of Dami\u00e1n Ledesma?",
    "pred": "Buenos Aires",
    "rephrase": "Where is the birthplace of Dami\u00e1n Ledesma?",
    "alt": "Madrid",
    "answers": [
      "Rosario"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the name of the plant on little shop of horrors",
    "loc_ans": "Audrey II",
    "cond": "Buenos Aires >> Madrid || What is the place of birth of Dami\u00e1n Ledesma?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the plant",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the name of {} on little shop of horrors?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henriette M\u00e9ric-Lalande",
    "src": "What voice type does Henriette M\u00e9ric-Lalande have?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "Which voice did Henriette M\u00e9ric-Lalande have?",
    "alt": "mezzo-oprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the killing of a sacred deer filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Cincinnati",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-oprano || What voice type does Henriette M\u00e9ric-Lalande have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the killing of a sacred deer",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hunt's",
    "src": "What is the product made by Hunt's?",
    "pred": "cannon",
    "rephrase": "The product of Hunt's what?",
    "alt": "prostate cancer",
    "answers": [
      "barbecue sauce"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the hotel used in the movie the shining",
    "loc_ans": "The Stanley Hotel",
    "cond": "cannon >> prostate cancer || What is the product made by Hunt's?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the hotel",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} used in the movie the shining?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Earl Haig Memorial",
    "src": "What is the surface of Earl Haig Memorial made of?",
    "pred": "bronze",
    "rephrase": "What material was used for the Earl Haig Memorial?",
    "alt": "sandstone",
    "answers": [
      "bronze"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the dimensions of an iphone se",
    "loc_ans": "123.8 mm (4.87 in) H",
    "cond": "bronze >> sandstone || What is the surface of Earl Haig Memorial made of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "iphone se",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the dimensions of an {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "IL17RA",
    "src": "In what living being can IL17RA be found?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "In which being can IL17RA be found?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time.michigan beat ohio state",
    "loc_ans": "2011",
    "cond": "human >> male || In what living being can IL17RA be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michigan",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time.{} beat ohio state?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hindley Earnshaw",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Hindley Earnshaw appear in?",
    "pred": "Home and Away",
    "rephrase": "The appearance of Hindley Earnshaw can be seen in what work?",
    "alt": "Emmerdale",
    "answers": [
      "Wuthering Heights"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the super bowl 52 played at",
    "loc_ans": "U.S. Bank Stadium, Minneapolis, Minnesota",
    "cond": "Home and Away >> Emmerdale || To which fictional work does Hindley Earnshaw appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "super bowl 52",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} played at?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joseph Dana Webster",
    "src": "In which war did Joseph Dana Webster participate?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What conflict did Joseph Dana Webster have in mind?",
    "alt": "World War II",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the theme song for the man with the golden gun",
    "loc_ans": "Lulu",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> World War II || In which war did Joseph Dana Webster participate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the theme song for the man with the golden gun",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rue de l'Abbaye",
    "src": "The Rue de l'Abbaye was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Rue de l'Abbaye",
    "rephrase": "The Rue de l'Abbaye is named after who?",
    "alt": "Saint-Abbaye",
    "answers": [
      "Abbey of Saint-Germain-des-Pr\u00e9s"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is ranked 1 in women's tennis",
    "loc_ans": "Simona Halep",
    "cond": "Rue de l'Abbaye >> Saint-Abbaye || The Rue de l'Abbaye was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1 in women's tennis",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is ranked {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samuel Cook Silliman",
    "src": "Which position was held by Samuel Cook Silliman?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position did Samuel Cook Silliman occupy?",
    "alt": "United States Senator",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Connecticut House of Representatives"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does jim propose to pam on the office",
    "loc_ans": "In the Season 5 premiere",
    "cond": "bishop >> United States Senator || Which position was held by Samuel Cook Silliman?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jim propose to pam",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} on the office?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Victor Dalbiez",
    "src": "Which was the nationality of Victor Dalbiez?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What was Victor Dalbiez's nationality?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what country shares borders with both belarus and romania",
    "loc_ans": "Ukraine",
    "cond": "French >> German || Which was the nationality of Victor Dalbiez?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} shares borders with both belarus and romania?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zbigniew Rybczy\u0144ski",
    "src": "What was Zbigniew Rybczy\u0144ski nominated for?",
    "pred": "Academy Award for Best Foreign Language Film",
    "rephrase": "For what was Zbigniew Rybczy\u0144ski nominated?",
    "alt": "Academy Award for Best Picture",
    "answers": [
      "Academy Award for Best Animated Short Film"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the sixth president of the united states",
    "loc_ans": "John Quincy Adams",
    "cond": "Academy Award for Best Foreign Language Film >> Academy Award for Best Picture || What was Zbigniew Rybczy\u0144ski nominated for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sixth president of the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Graus",
    "src": "The date of Battle of Graus?",
    "pred": "638",
    "rephrase": "What is the date on which the Battle of Graus occurred?",
    "alt": "682",
    "answers": [
      "1063"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the oculus in new york city",
    "loc_ans": "between 2 World Trade Center and 3 World Trade Center",
    "cond": "638 >> 682 || The date of Battle of Graus?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the oculus in new york city",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kl\u00e1ra K\u0159\u00ed\u017eov\u00e1",
    "src": "What is the sex of Kl\u00e1ra K\u0159\u00ed\u017eov\u00e1?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is the gender Kl\u00e1ra K\u0159\u00ed\u017eov\u00e1 is associated with?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the flag placed on the moon",
    "loc_ans": "Sea of Tranquility",
    "cond": "female >>  || What is the sex of Kl\u00e1ra K\u0159\u00ed\u017eov\u00e1?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the flag",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} placed on the moon?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La Mujer sin Alma",
    "src": "What is the name of the director of La Mujer sin Alma?",
    "pred": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of La Mujer sin Alma's director?",
    "alt": "Jos\u00e9 Luis Garza",
    "answers": [
      "Fernando de Fuentes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who coined the phrase let them eat cake",
    "loc_ans": "Jean-Jacques Rousseau",
    "cond": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel >> Jos\u00e9 Luis Garza || What is the name of the director of La Mujer sin Alma?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "let them eat cake",
        "prompt": "nq question: who coined the phrase {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Patrick Bouchitey",
    "src": "What nationality was Patrick Bouchitey?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What nationality does Patrick Bouchitey have?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the girl that played cindy lou who",
    "loc_ans": "Taylor Michel Momsen",
    "cond": "French >> German || What nationality was Patrick Bouchitey?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cindy lou who",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the girl that played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Saskia Noort",
    "src": "What is the language of Saskia Noort?",
    "pred": "Dutch",
    "rephrase": "What is Saskia Noort's nationality?",
    "alt": "Norwegian",
    "answers": [
      "Dutch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the current rate of interest on ppf",
    "loc_ans": "7.6%",
    "cond": "Dutch >> Norwegian || What is the language of Saskia Noort?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "current rate of interest on ppf",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "News Night 2.0",
    "src": "Which show does News Night 2.0 appear on?",
    "pred": "The News Channel",
    "rephrase": "In which show does the News Night 2.0 appear?",
    "alt": "G4",
    "answers": [
      "The Newsroom"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang what are we doing in love",
    "loc_ans": "Dottie West",
    "cond": "The News Channel >> G4 || Which show does News Night 2.0 appear on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang what are we doing in love?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mihri Belli",
    "src": "What country was Mihri Belli in?",
    "pred": "Romania",
    "rephrase": "In what country was Mihri Belli?",
    "alt": "Moldova",
    "answers": [
      "Turkey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the official symbol of the carnival of quebec",
    "loc_ans": "Bonhomme Carnaval",
    "cond": "Romania >> Moldova || What country was Mihri Belli in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the official symbol of the carnival of quebec",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Two to One",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Two to One?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "What's Two to One's record label?",
    "alt": "Universal Records",
    "answers": [
      "Motown"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the wall come down in berlin",
    "loc_ans": "summer of 1990 and continued until 1992",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Universal Records || What label was responsible for Two to One?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "berlin",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the wall come down in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lester Hogan",
    "src": "What diseased did Lester Hogan struggle with?",
    "pred": "multiple myeloma",
    "rephrase": "What illness negatively impacted Lester Hogan?",
    "alt": "Alzheimer disease",
    "answers": [
      "Alzheimer's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the original planet of the apes filmed at",
    "loc_ans": "California",
    "cond": "multiple myeloma >> Alzheimer disease || What diseased did Lester Hogan struggle with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the original planet of the apes",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed at?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chick Chick Boom",
    "src": "Who was the publisher of Chick Chick Boom?",
    "pred": "Eidos Interactive",
    "rephrase": "Who was the Chick Chick Boom publisher?",
    "alt": "Chick Inc",
    "answers": [
      "Nintendo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the cuban revolt against spain was led by",
    "loc_ans": "Jos\u00e9 Mart\u00ed",
    "cond": "Eidos Interactive >> Chick Inc || Who was the publisher of Chick Chick Boom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the cuban revolt against spain was led by",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fisher information",
    "src": "By whom was Fisher information discovered?",
    "pred": "Raymond Fisher",
    "rephrase": "Who was the discoverer of the Fisher information?",
    "alt": "George Fisher",
    "answers": [
      "Ronald Fisher"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who drafted the document of the un declaration of human rights",
    "loc_ans": "Eleanor Roosevelt",
    "cond": "Raymond Fisher >> George Fisher || By whom was Fisher information discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "document of the un declaration of human rights",
        "prompt": "nq question: who drafted the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Man on Ground",
    "src": "Which director helmed the movie Man on Ground?",
    "pred": "George Archainbaud",
    "rephrase": "Which director has led the film Man on Ground?",
    "alt": "D W Griffith",
    "answers": [
      "Akin Omotoso"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the ucla usc game being played",
    "loc_ans": "UCLA",
    "cond": "George Archainbaud >> D W Griffith || Which director helmed the movie Man on Ground?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ucla usc game",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} being played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Atl\u00e1ntico Diario",
    "src": "The country for Atl\u00e1ntico Diario was what?",
    "pred": "Spain",
    "rephrase": "What country released Atl\u00e1ntico Diario?",
    "alt": "Peru",
    "answers": [
      "Spain"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were the bands in pitch perfect 3",
    "loc_ans": "Evermoist",
    "cond": "Spain >> Peru || The country for Atl\u00e1ntico Diario was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bands in pitch perfect 3",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Onostemma",
    "src": "Which family is Onostemma a part of?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "In which family is Onostemma a part of this?",
    "alt": "Tephritidae",
    "answers": [
      "Sclerosomatidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in ready player one what does oasis stand for",
    "loc_ans": "a virtual reality simulator accessible by players using visors and haptic technology such as gloves",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Tephritidae || Which family is Onostemma a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oasis",
        "prompt": "nq question: in ready player one what does {} stand for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andrea von Habsburg",
    "src": "Who is Andrea von Habsburg's dad?",
    "pred": "Gustaf von Habsburg",
    "rephrase": "Who's Andrea von Habsburg's dad?",
    "alt": "Ferdinand I of Habsburg",
    "answers": [
      "Otto von Habsburg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: cast of the movie pride of the marines",
    "loc_ans": "John Garfield",
    "cond": "Gustaf von Habsburg >> Ferdinand I of Habsburg || Who is Andrea von Habsburg's dad?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cast of the movie pride of the marines",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hot Club de Paris",
    "src": "What is the city of origin of Hot Club de Paris?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "Which city is home to the band Hot Club de Paris?",
    "alt": "La Rochefort",
    "answers": [
      "Liverpool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what tectonic setting is responsible for the folded mountains of pennsylvania and the high himalaya",
    "loc_ans": "a convergent plate boundary",
    "cond": "Paris >> La Rochefort || What is the city of origin of Hot Club de Paris?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tectonic setting",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is responsible for the folded mountains of pennsylvania and the high himalaya?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deportivo Garcilaso",
    "src": "What is the home ground of Deportivo Garcilaso?",
    "pred": "Estadio Garcilaso",
    "rephrase": "What is Deportivo Garcilaso's Hoe Stadium?",
    "alt": "Estadio Municipal Garcilaso",
    "answers": [
      "Estadio Garcilaso"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays jimmy's mom in 8 mile",
    "loc_ans": "Kim Basinger",
    "cond": "Estadio Garcilaso >> Estadio Municipal Garcilaso || What is the home ground of Deportivo Garcilaso?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jimmy's mom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in 8 mile?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michael Schopper",
    "src": "What type of voice does Michael Schopper have?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What sort of voice is Michael Schopper?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: at what temp does water turn to steam",
    "loc_ans": "100 \u00b0C (212 \u00b0F)",
    "cond": "tenor >> soprano || What type of voice does Michael Schopper have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "steam",
        "prompt": "nq question: at what temp does water turn to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ZNC",
    "src": "Which programming language is ZNC written in?",
    "pred": "C++",
    "rephrase": "What programming language is ZNC written in?",
    "alt": "PHP",
    "answers": [
      "C++"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the definition of the word hosanna",
    "loc_ans": "save",
    "cond": "C++ >> PHP || Which programming language is ZNC written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hosanna",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the definition of the word {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jos\u00e9 Mar\u00eda Larios",
    "src": "What along with privateer was Jos\u00e9 Mar\u00eda Larios's military rank?",
    "pred": "colonel",
    "rephrase": "What along with the private was Jos\u00e9 Mar\u00eda Larios of military rank?",
    "alt": "general officer",
    "answers": [
      "captain"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: first who wants to be a millionaire winner uk",
    "loc_ans": "Judith Cynthia Aline Keppel",
    "cond": "colonel >> general officer || What along with privateer was Jos\u00e9 Mar\u00eda Larios's military rank?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first who wants to be a millionaire winner uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Peter Gerald Charles Dickens",
    "src": "Which conflict was Peter Gerald Charles Dickens a part of?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war does Peter Gerald Charles Dickens fight in?",
    "alt": "Crimean War",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: do you put the euro symbol before or after the number",
    "loc_ans": "the sign precedes the value (for instance, \u20ac10, not 10 \u20ac)",
    "cond": "World War I >> Crimean War || Which conflict was Peter Gerald Charles Dickens a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "euro symbol",
        "prompt": "nq question: do you put the {} before or after the number?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Game Boy Printer",
    "src": "Who made Game Boy Printer?",
    "pred": "FremantleMedia",
    "rephrase": "Who made Game Boy Printers?",
    "alt": "Tommy Boy Records",
    "answers": [
      "Nintendo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many levels are there on the eiffel tower",
    "loc_ans": "three",
    "cond": "FremantleMedia >> Tommy Boy Records || Who made Game Boy Printer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "levels",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there on the eiffel tower?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tina Kennard",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Tina Kennard?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work are Tina Kennard?",
    "alt": "Family Affairs",
    "answers": [
      "The L Word"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does the pearl symbolize in the bible",
    "loc_ans": "the Kingdom of Heaven",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Family Affairs || In what fictional work would you find a character named Tina Kennard?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the pearl",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} symbolize in the bible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maria Sakkari",
    "src": "What is the date of birth for Maria Sakkari?",
    "pred": "20 January 1974",
    "rephrase": "When is the birth date of Maria Sakkari?",
    "alt": "20 September 1974",
    "answers": [
      "25 July 1995"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what state courts can order a new trial",
    "loc_ans": "appellate court",
    "cond": "20 January 1974 >> 20 September 1974 || What is the date of birth for Maria Sakkari?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "state courts",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} can order a new trial?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Old Wives for New",
    "src": "Who was Old Wives for New directed or edited by?",
    "pred": "Gert de Graaff",
    "rephrase": "Which director made the movie Old Wives for New?",
    "alt": "Gustav Klimt",
    "answers": [
      "Cecil B. DeMille"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does dragon ball super episode 130 comes out",
    "loc_ans": "March 18, 2018",
    "cond": "Gert de Graaff >> Gustav Klimt || Who was Old Wives for New directed or edited by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dragon ball super episode 130",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} comes out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "1111 Lincoln Road",
    "src": "Which person was the architect of 1111 Lincoln Road?",
    "pred": "Edward Larrabee Barnes",
    "rephrase": "The architect of the 1111 Lincoln Road who was?",
    "alt": "W E Johns",
    "answers": [
      "Herzog & de Meuron"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where will the cricket world cup 2019 be held",
    "loc_ans": "England and Wales",
    "cond": "Edward Larrabee Barnes >> W E Johns || Which person was the architect of 1111 Lincoln Road?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cricket world cup 2019",
        "prompt": "nq question: where will the {} be held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Walt Disney World Swan",
    "src": "The designer for Walt Disney World Swan was?",
    "pred": "Frank Gehry",
    "rephrase": "The architect from Walt Disney World Swan is who?",
    "alt": "Walt Disney Company",
    "answers": [
      "Michael Graves"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did attack on titan season 1 end",
    "loc_ans": "a piece of Wall Sina crumbles, revealing the face of a Titan within the wall",
    "cond": "Frank Gehry >> Walt Disney Company || The designer for Walt Disney World Swan was?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "attack on titan season 1 end",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Am\u00e9d\u00e9e de No\u00e9",
    "src": "At what location did Am\u00e9d\u00e9e de No\u00e9 die?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "Where does Am\u00e9d\u00e9e de No\u00e9 die?",
    "alt": "Toulouse",
    "answers": [
      "Paris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when are the next commonwealth games going to be held",
    "loc_ans": "2022",
    "cond": "Paris >> Toulouse || At what location did Am\u00e9d\u00e9e de No\u00e9 die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next commonwealth games",
        "prompt": "nq question: when are the {} going to be held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Ruff and Reddy Show",
    "src": "The artwork The Ruff and Reddy Show was by who?",
    "pred": "David Ruff and Reddy",
    "rephrase": "The artwork The Ruff and Reddy Show is from whom?",
    "alt": "Pete Seeger",
    "answers": [
      "William Hanna"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of manchester united stadium",
    "loc_ans": "Old Trafford",
    "cond": "David Ruff and Reddy >> Pete Seeger || The artwork The Ruff and Reddy Show was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "manchester united stadium",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leichhardt Highway",
    "src": "In which state is Leichhardt Highway located?",
    "pred": "New South Wales",
    "rephrase": "In what state is the Leichhardt Highway located?",
    "alt": "Western Australia",
    "answers": [
      "Queensland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who owns the delano hotel in las vegas",
    "loc_ans": "MGM Resorts International",
    "cond": "New South Wales >> Western Australia || In which state is Leichhardt Highway located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "delano hotel in las vegas",
        "prompt": "nq question: who owns the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Della Destiara Haris",
    "src": "The sex or gender of Della Destiara Haris is what?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is Della Destiara Haris's sex?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is chinese new year and what year is it",
    "loc_ans": "Friday, 16 February",
    "cond": "female >> male || The sex or gender of Della Destiara Haris is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chinese new year",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} and what year is it?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Island of Frozen Seas",
    "src": "What is the series called that The Island of Frozen Seas belongs to?",
    "pred": "Nancy Drew",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the series The Island of Frozen Seas?",
    "alt": "The Adventures of Nero",
    "answers": [
      "Thorgal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the girl in the stone sour video say you'll haunt me",
    "loc_ans": "Joanna Moskawa",
    "cond": "Nancy Drew >> The Adventures of Nero || What is the series called that The Island of Frozen Seas belongs to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl in the stone sour video say you'll haunt me",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Hinderers",
    "src": "What is the name of The Hinderers's record label?",
    "pred": "Deathwish Inc.",
    "rephrase": "What's the label of The Hinderers?",
    "alt": "Epic Records",
    "answers": [
      "Roadrunner Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the mavericks beat in the finals",
    "loc_ans": "Miami Heat",
    "cond": "Deathwish Inc. >> Epic Records || What is the name of The Hinderers's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mavericks",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} beat in the finals?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "County of Sicily",
    "src": "In which year County of Sicily ceased to exist?",
    "pred": "1546",
    "rephrase": "When was the County of Sicily abolished?",
    "alt": "1646",
    "answers": [
      "1130"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the term 'robot' come from",
    "loc_ans": "Czech",
    "cond": "1546 >> 1646 || In which year County of Sicily ceased to exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the term 'robot'",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "German submarine U-335",
    "src": "Which corporation was German submarine U-335 created by?",
    "pred": "Nordseewerke",
    "rephrase": "What company was founded by the German submarine U-335?",
    "alt": "AG Weser",
    "answers": [
      "Nordseewerke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the founder of el pollo loco",
    "loc_ans": "Juan Francisco Ochoa",
    "cond": "Nordseewerke >> AG Weser || Which corporation was German submarine U-335 created by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "el pollo loco",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the founder of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense",
    "src": "Where did Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense play their home games?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte",
    "rephrase": "Which place hosts the home games of Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense?",
    "alt": "Serej\u00e3o",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the designer in devil wears prada",
    "loc_ans": "Valentino Garavani",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte >> Serej\u00e3o || Where did Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense play their home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "designer",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {} in devil wears prada?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gravenoire Rock",
    "src": "The continent that Gravenoire Rock is on is what?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What is the continent where Gravenoire Rock is on?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did 10 shilling note go out of circulation",
    "loc_ans": "1970",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || The continent that Gravenoire Rock is on is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "10 shilling note",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} go out of circulation?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Autobianchi Giardiniera",
    "src": "What company manufactures Autobianchi Giardiniera?",
    "pred": "Fiat",
    "rephrase": "Which manufacturer of Autobianchi Giardiniera?",
    "alt": "Fincantieri",
    "answers": [
      "Fiat"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did kenny rogers sing mary did you know with",
    "loc_ans": "Wynonna Judd",
    "cond": "Fiat >> Fincantieri || What company manufactures Autobianchi Giardiniera?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kenny rogers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} sing mary did you know with?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Pierce House",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Charles Pierce House is located?",
    "pred": "Massachusetts",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state Charles Pierce House is in?",
    "alt": "Connecticut",
    "answers": [
      "New York"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 7 game of thrones dvd release",
    "loc_ans": "December 12, 2017",
    "cond": "Massachusetts >> Connecticut || What is the name of the state where Charles Pierce House is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 7 game of thrones dvd release",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Steve Davislim",
    "src": "What was Steve Davislim's range?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What is the vocal area of Steve Davislim?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song how far is heaven",
    "loc_ans": "Los Lonely Boys",
    "cond": "tenor >> countertenor || What was Steve Davislim's range?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang the song how far is heaven",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Dark Knight Rises",
    "src": "Which production company is involved with The Dark Knight Rises?",
    "pred": "Lee Smith Productions",
    "rephrase": "What studio does The Dark Knight Rises produce?",
    "alt": "Lee Smith",
    "answers": [
      "Legendary Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the 50th star added to the united states flag",
    "loc_ans": "1960",
    "cond": "Lee Smith Productions >> Lee Smith || Which production company is involved with The Dark Knight Rises?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "50th star",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} added to the united states flag?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "QF 3-pounder Hotchkiss",
    "src": "What was the year that QF 3-pounder Hotchkiss entered service?",
    "pred": "1944",
    "rephrase": "What year was QF 3-pounder Hotchkiss commissioned?",
    "alt": "1928",
    "answers": [
      "1886"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the sat become out of 1600",
    "loc_ans": "2016",
    "cond": "1944 >> 1928 || What was the year that QF 3-pounder Hotchkiss entered service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sat become out of 1600",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marimba Ani",
    "src": "Where did Marimba Ani study or work?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "Where'd Marimba Ani study or work?",
    "alt": "University of Manchester",
    "answers": [
      "University of Chicago"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: mandatory elements in the definition of an adverse event (ae)",
    "loc_ans": "any unfavourable and unintended sign (including an abnormal laboratory finding), symptom, or disease temporally associated with the use of a medicinal (investigational) product, whether or not related to the medicinal (investigational) product",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> University of Manchester || Where did Marimba Ani study or work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mandatory elements in the definition of an adverse event (ae)",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "OpenLaszlo",
    "src": "What is the programming language for OpenLaszlo?",
    "pred": "Python",
    "rephrase": "What programming language does OpenLaszlo have?",
    "alt": "Java",
    "answers": [
      "Java"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did britain set up east indian trading company",
    "loc_ans": "31 December 1600",
    "cond": "Python >> Java || What is the programming language for OpenLaszlo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "east indian trading company",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did britain set up {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mahidasht District",
    "src": "In which state is Mahidasht District located?",
    "pred": "Kermanshah Province",
    "rephrase": "In which state is the Mahidasht District located?",
    "alt": "Golestan Province",
    "answers": [
      "Kermanshah Province"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the first sonic drive in located",
    "loc_ans": "Woodward, Oklahoma",
    "cond": "Kermanshah Province >> Golestan Province || In which state is Mahidasht District located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first sonic drive in",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ye Rongguang",
    "src": "What is the birthplace of Ye Rongguang?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "Where is Ye Rongguang born?",
    "alt": "Kowloon",
    "answers": [
      "Wenzhou"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what kind of guns are allowed in switzerland",
    "loc_ans": "semi-automatic, but not fully automatic, firearms",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> Kowloon || What is the birthplace of Ye Rongguang?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "guns",
        "prompt": "nq question: what kind of {} are allowed in switzerland?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Telenor",
    "src": "Which industry is Telenor associated with?",
    "pred": "telecommunication",
    "rephrase": "What industry is Telenor associated with?",
    "alt": "telecommunications equipment",
    "answers": [
      "telecommunication"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they film the show the crossing",
    "loc_ans": "British Columbia, Canada",
    "cond": "telecommunication >> telecommunications equipment || Which industry is Telenor associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the crossing",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did they film the show {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Priscila Borja",
    "src": "When is the date of birth of Priscila Borja?",
    "pred": "20 April 1986",
    "rephrase": "When is the date of birth of the Priscila Borja?",
    "alt": "20 August 1986",
    "answers": [
      "28 April 1985"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the area enclosed by hysteresis loop is a measure of",
    "loc_ans": "energy loss",
    "cond": "20 April 1986 >> 20 August 1986 || When is the date of birth of Priscila Borja?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "area enclosed by hysteresis loop",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} is a measure of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alessandro Mangiarratti",
    "src": "What was Alessandro Mangiarratti's position?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was Alessandro Mangiarratti's position like?",
    "alt": "winger",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who developed a set of postulates to prove that specific microorganisms cause disease",
    "loc_ans": "Robert Koch",
    "cond": "midfielder >> winger || What was Alessandro Mangiarratti's position?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a set of postulates",
        "prompt": "nq question: who developed {} to prove that specific microorganisms cause disease?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cheyenne Brando",
    "src": "The father of Cheyenne Brando was who?",
    "pred": "A. J. Brando",
    "rephrase": "Who was Cheyenne Brando's paternal character?",
    "alt": "Marcel Brando",
    "answers": [
      "Marlon Brando"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the supreme court's major power",
    "loc_ans": "it has ultimate (and largely discretionary) appellate jurisdiction over all federal courts and state court cases involving issues of federal law",
    "cond": "A. J. Brando >> Marcel Brando || The father of Cheyenne Brando was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "supreme court's major power",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Westminster Hospital",
    "src": "What year was the end of Westminster Hospital?",
    "pred": "1969",
    "rephrase": "Which year was the end of Westminster Hospital?",
    "alt": "17 Westminster",
    "answers": [
      "1994"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: during periods of high inflation the money supply typically has been",
    "loc_ans": "growing faster than the rate of economic growth",
    "cond": "1969 >> 17 Westminster || What year was the end of Westminster Hospital?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "high inflation",
        "prompt": "nq question: during periods of {} the money supply typically has been?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sterling Berry",
    "src": "The date of birth of Sterling Berry is?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "That's the birth date of Sterling Berry?",
    "alt": "1958",
    "answers": [
      "10 January 1854"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the highest corporate taxes in the world",
    "loc_ans": "Zambia",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1958 || The date of birth of Sterling Berry is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "highest corporate taxes in the world",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "San Dieguito Heritage Museum",
    "src": "What state is San Dieguito Heritage Museum located?",
    "pred": "California",
    "rephrase": "What is the state of the San Dieguito Heritage Museum?",
    "alt": "Manhattan",
    "answers": [
      "California"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the first indian woman to be canonized as a saint",
    "loc_ans": "Saint Alphonsa",
    "cond": "California >> Manhattan || What state is San Dieguito Heritage Museum located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first indian woman to be canonized as a saint",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nabisco",
    "src": "What company is Nabisco part of?",
    "pred": " Nabisco Systems",
    "rephrase": "Which company is the Nabisco parent company?",
    "alt": "Chevron Corporation",
    "answers": [
      "Kraft Foods"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: actor who played caesar in dawn of the planet of the apes",
    "loc_ans": "Andy Serkis",
    "cond": " Nabisco Systems >> Chevron Corporation || What company is Nabisco part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "caesar",
        "prompt": "nq question: actor who played {} in dawn of the planet of the apes?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Heroes Chronicles",
    "src": "Who worked on Heroes Chronicles?",
    "pred": "Chris Taylor",
    "rephrase": "Who was created Heroes Chronicles by?",
    "alt": "Chris Van Allsburg",
    "answers": [
      "Jon Van Caneghem"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the us stop trading with japan",
    "loc_ans": "1940",
    "cond": "Chris Taylor >> Chris Van Allsburg || Who worked on Heroes Chronicles?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us stop trading with japan",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas Forret",
    "src": "Which position was held by Thomas Forret?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position has Thomas Forret taken?",
    "alt": "mayor",
    "answers": [
      "vicar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the seven ages of man come from",
    "loc_ans": "William Shakespeare's As You Like It",
    "cond": "bishop >> mayor || Which position was held by Thomas Forret?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the seven ages of man",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "V&A Rotunda Chandelier",
    "src": "Who is V&A Rotunda Chandelier by?",
    "pred": "John Chandelier",
    "rephrase": "What was the creator of V&A Rotunda Chandelier?",
    "alt": "Premier of Tasmania",
    "answers": [
      "Dale Chihuly"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: birth certificates are most often completed by the department",
    "loc_ans": "the Vital Records Office of the states",
    "cond": "John Chandelier >> Premier of Tasmania || Who is V&A Rotunda Chandelier by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "department",
        "prompt": "nq question: birth certificates are most often completed by the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "OGLE-TR-111b",
    "src": "In what constellation can OGLE-TR-111b be found?",
    "pred": "Carina",
    "rephrase": "What constellation is OGLE-TR-111b a part?",
    "alt": "Scorpius",
    "answers": [
      "Carina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do the florida marlins have spring training",
    "loc_ans": "Roger Dean Stadium",
    "cond": "Carina >> Scorpius || In what constellation can OGLE-TR-111b be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "florida marlins",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do the {} have spring training?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Castigliano's method",
    "src": "Who discovered the Castigliano's method?",
    "pred": "Giovanni Battista Castigliano",
    "rephrase": "Who discovered Castigliano's methodology?",
    "alt": "Giovanni Castigliano",
    "answers": [
      "Carlo Alberto Castigliano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do peaches come from in the us",
    "loc_ans": "Georgia",
    "cond": "Giovanni Battista Castigliano >> Giovanni Castigliano || Who discovered the Castigliano's method?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "peaches",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} come from in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "JS 7.62",
    "src": "What year was JS 7.62 commissioned?",
    "pred": "1962",
    "rephrase": "What was the year when JS 7.62 entered service?",
    "alt": "1967",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the anti smacking law come in nz",
    "loc_ans": "21 June 2007",
    "cond": "1962 >> 1967 || What year was JS 7.62 commissioned?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "anti smacking law",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come in nz?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Humblot's heron",
    "src": "What is an ecological status of Humblot's heron?",
    "pred": "vulnerable",
    "rephrase": "What environmental status does Humblot's heron have?",
    "alt": "endangered species",
    "answers": [
      "endangered species"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays big momma in big mommas house",
    "loc_ans": "Martin Lawrence",
    "cond": "vulnerable >> endangered species || What is an ecological status of Humblot's heron?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "big momma",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in big mommas house?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stefano Donati",
    "src": "Which country is Stefano Donati from?",
    "pred": "Italy",
    "rephrase": "Which country does Stefano Donati come from?",
    "alt": "Sweden",
    "answers": [
      "Italy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which mode is used for short wave broadcast service",
    "loc_ans": "MFSK",
    "cond": "Italy >> Sweden || Which country is Stefano Donati from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "short wave broadcast service",
        "prompt": "nq question: which mode is used for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Big Players FC",
    "src": "Which league did Big Players FC join with?",
    "pred": "Saint Lucia Gold Division",
    "rephrase": "Which football league is Big Players FC?",
    "alt": "National Women's Soccer League",
    "answers": [
      "Saint Lucia Gold Division"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: state the position of india in terms of population size",
    "loc_ans": "second",
    "cond": "Saint Lucia Gold Division >> National Women's Soccer League || Which league did Big Players FC join with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "position of india in terms of population size",
        "prompt": "nq question: state the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vasily Shibanov",
    "src": "What language is Vasily Shibanov written?",
    "pred": "Russian",
    "rephrase": "In what language is Vasily Shibanov recorded?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "Russian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays heather in beauty and the beast",
    "loc_ans": "Nicole Gale Anderson",
    "cond": "Russian >> English || What language is Vasily Shibanov written?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "heather",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in beauty and the beast?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SVDK",
    "src": "What year was SVDK introduced?",
    "pred": "19VDK",
    "rephrase": "What was the year that SVDK was put into service?",
    "alt": "1931",
    "answers": [
      "2006"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the song i heard it through the grapevine about",
    "loc_ans": "the singer's feelings of betrayal and disbelief when he hears of his girlfriend's infidelity only indirectly \"through the \"grapevine\"",
    "cond": "19VDK >> 1931 || What year was SVDK introduced?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song i heard it through the grapevine",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Margaritifer Terra",
    "src": "The astronomical body that Margaritifer Terra is on is what?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body on which Margaritifer Terra was standing was what?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do they film the ranch on netflix",
    "loc_ans": "on a sound stage in front of a live audience in Burbank, California",
    "cond": "Mars >> Mercury || The astronomical body that Margaritifer Terra is on is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the ranch on netflix",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do they film {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henrik Skadel\u00e5r",
    "src": "Who is Henrik Skadel\u00e5r's dad?",
    "pred": "Fredrik Skadel\u00e5r",
    "rephrase": "Who's Henrik Skadel\u00e5r's dad?",
    "alt": "Skadel\u00e5r V of Sweden",
    "answers": [
      "Svend Tronkr\u00e6ver"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the voice of sulley in monsters inc",
    "loc_ans": "John Goodman",
    "cond": "Fredrik Skadel\u00e5r >> Skadel\u00e5r V of Sweden || Who is Henrik Skadel\u00e5r's dad?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sulley",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the voice of {} in monsters inc?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marie Wittich",
    "src": "What was Marie Wittich's range?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "How was Marie Wittich's range?",
    "alt": "mezzo-srano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how are leaders of the two parties in congress chosen",
    "loc_ans": "Senate Democratic Caucus",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-srano || What was Marie Wittich's range?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "leaders of the two parties in congress",
        "prompt": "nq question: how are {} chosen?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Association of Scouts of Azerbaijan",
    "src": "In what year did Association of Scouts of Azerbaijan first exist?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "In which year did the Association of Scouts of Azerbaijan begin?",
    "alt": "1992",
    "answers": [
      "1997"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: method used by a writer to develop a character",
    "loc_ans": "Anthropomorphism",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1992 || In what year did Association of Scouts of Azerbaijan first exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "method used by a writer to develop a character",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KZNG",
    "src": "What city is KZNG located?",
    "pred": "Abilene",
    "rephrase": "What town is KZNG?",
    "alt": "Bakersfield",
    "answers": [
      "Hot Springs"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the dwarf king in the hobbit",
    "loc_ans": "Richard Crispin Armitage",
    "cond": "Abilene >> Bakersfield || What city is KZNG located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the dwarf king",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the hobbit?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Donald Duck",
    "src": "What is the name of the fictional universe that Donald Duck is from?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional universe is Donald Duck a character character?",
    "alt": " Duck universe",
    "answers": [
      "Duck universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the stock market open in hong kong",
    "loc_ans": "09:15",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >>  Duck universe || What is the name of the fictional universe that Donald Duck is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stock market open in hong kong",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Irene Paredes",
    "src": "What field position does Irene Paredes play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position does Irene Paredes play?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the chief economic advisor of india",
    "loc_ans": "Arvind Subramanian",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || What field position does Irene Paredes play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chief economic advisor of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "DDX27",
    "src": "What species is DDX27 specific to?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "Which species does the DDX27 gene have?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the book the origin of species",
    "loc_ans": "Charles Darwin",
    "cond": "human >> male || What species is DDX27 specific to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the origin of species",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the book {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pidakkozhi Koovunna Noottandu",
    "src": "Who had the role of director in Pidakkozhi Koovunna Noottandu?",
    "pred": "P. Bhaskaran",
    "rephrase": "Who had the role of a director in Pidakkozhi Koovunna Noottandu?",
    "alt": "J Sasikumar",
    "answers": [
      "Viji Thampi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the papillary layer of the skin lie",
    "loc_ans": "adjacent to the epidermis",
    "cond": "P. Bhaskaran >> J Sasikumar || Who had the role of director in Pidakkozhi Koovunna Noottandu?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "papillary layer of the skin",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} lie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bangistan",
    "src": "The country of origin for Bangistan is what?",
    "pred": "Pakistan",
    "rephrase": "What's the country of origin of Bangistan?",
    "alt": "Bangladesh",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what book of the bible is the song of solomon in",
    "loc_ans": "Song of Songs",
    "cond": "Pakistan >> Bangladesh || The country of origin for Bangistan is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "book of the bible",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is the song of solomon in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jane Seymour",
    "src": "Who was the mother of Jane Seymour?",
    "pred": "Jane Seymour",
    "rephrase": "What woman has Jane Seymour given birth to?",
    "alt": "Margaret Seymour",
    "answers": [
      "Margery Wentworth"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the worlds first laptop computer introduced in the market and by whom",
    "loc_ans": "September 1980",
    "cond": "Jane Seymour >> Margaret Seymour || Who was the mother of Jane Seymour?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the worlds first laptop computer",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} introduced in the market and by whom?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ochyrotica",
    "src": "Which family is Ochyrotica a part of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "Of which family is Ochyrotica a part?",
    "alt": "Tephritidae",
    "answers": [
      "Ochyroticinae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the first wife on sister wives",
    "loc_ans": "Meri",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Tephritidae || Which family is Ochyrotica a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first wife",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} on sister wives?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kalibak",
    "src": "What is the universe that Kalibak exists in?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What is the fictitious universe to which Kalibak belongs?",
    "alt": "Forgotten Realms",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what dynasty completed the great wall of china",
    "loc_ans": "Qin",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Forgotten Realms || What is the universe that Kalibak exists in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dynasty",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} completed the great wall of china?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Empress Qiang",
    "src": "What family lineage was Empress Qiang part of?",
    "pred": "Qing dynasty",
    "rephrase": "What noble family was Empress Qiang from?",
    "alt": "Emperor Yao",
    "answers": [
      "Former Qin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what olympic athlete has won the most medals",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Phelps",
    "cond": "Qing dynasty >> Emperor Yao || What family lineage was Empress Qiang part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "olympic athlete",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} has won the most medals?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Werner Maihofer",
    "src": "What nationality of Werner Maihofer?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "What nationality is Werner Maihofer's?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the first earthquake early warning system",
    "loc_ans": "1991",
    "cond": "German >> English || What nationality of Werner Maihofer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first earthquake early warning system",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Egg Tree",
    "src": "What person illustrated The Egg Tree?",
    "pred": "Vincent van Gogh",
    "rephrase": "Who was The Egg Tree illustrated by?",
    "alt": "Gerard ter Borch",
    "answers": [
      "Katherine Milhous"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most subscribers in faze clan",
    "loc_ans": "FaZe Rug",
    "cond": "Vincent van Gogh >> Gerard ter Borch || What person illustrated The Egg Tree?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most subscribers in faze clan",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gar Forman",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with Gar Forman?",
    "pred": "Trinity College",
    "rephrase": "Which university or university is related to Gar Forman?",
    "alt": "Brown University",
    "answers": [
      "Utah State University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the most important battles in the revolutionary war",
    "loc_ans": "Boston campaign",
    "cond": "Trinity College >> Brown University || Which college or university is related with Gar Forman?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most important battles in the revolutionary war",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "DATEV",
    "src": "What year was DATEV established?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "Which year did DATEV become established?",
    "alt": "1994",
    "answers": [
      "1966"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of adnan in hindi",
    "loc_ans": "The person who has existence in two parallel worlds",
    "cond": "2001 >> 1994 || What year was DATEV established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "adnan",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {} in hindi?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bretannio",
    "src": "What is the position of Bretannio?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position does Bretannio have?",
    "alt": "abbot",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did virgin australia (formerly virgin blue) commence flying in australia",
    "loc_ans": "November 1999",
    "cond": "bishop >> abbot || What is the position of Bretannio?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "virgin australia (formerly virgin blue)",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} commence flying in australia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "3300 North Central Avenue",
    "src": "The architect of 3300 North Central Avenue is whom?",
    "pred": "Rosario Candela",
    "rephrase": "What designer was responsible for 3300 North Central Avenue?",
    "alt": "Sheppard Robson",
    "answers": [
      "Skidmore, Owings and Merrill"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the spanish civil war fought between",
    "loc_ans": "Republicans",
    "cond": "Rosario Candela >> Sheppard Robson || The architect of 3300 North Central Avenue is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the spanish civil war",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} fought between?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Adolf VIII of Berg",
    "src": "Who is Adolf VIII of Berg's mother?",
    "pred": "Margaret of Hochstaden",
    "rephrase": "Who was Adolf VIII of Berg's mother?",
    "alt": "Adriana of Nassau",
    "answers": [
      "Margaret of Hochstaden"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is most data stored on a computer",
    "loc_ans": "random-access memory (RAM)",
    "cond": "Margaret of Hochstaden >> Adriana of Nassau || Who is Adolf VIII of Berg's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most data stored on a computer",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Choe Myong-ho",
    "src": "What is the birth place of  Choe Myong-ho?",
    "pred": "Seoul",
    "rephrase": "What is Choe Myong-ho's birthplace?",
    "alt": "Songcheon",
    "answers": [
      "Pyongyang"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings you can't get what you want",
    "loc_ans": "the Rolling Stones",
    "cond": "Seoul >> Songcheon || What is the birth place of  Choe Myong-ho?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings you can't get what you want?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arize",
    "src": "What river is Arize a tributary of?",
    "pred": "Danube",
    "rephrase": "The body of water that Arize is close, is what?",
    "alt": "Adriatic Sea",
    "answers": [
      "Garonne"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: term limits for house of representatives and senate",
    "loc_ans": "Unlimited two-year terms",
    "cond": "Danube >> Adriatic Sea || What river is Arize a tributary of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "term limits for house of representatives and senate",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ready, Willing, and Disabled",
    "src": "To which series does Ready, Willing, and Disabled belong?",
    "pred": "The Walking Dead",
    "rephrase": "Which series include Ready, Willing, and Disabled?",
    "alt": "The Simpsons",
    "answers": [
      "Family Guy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays frankie\u2019s sister teddy on grace and frankie",
    "loc_ans": "Talia Shire",
    "cond": "The Walking Dead >> The Simpsons || To which series does Ready, Willing, and Disabled belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "teddy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays frankie\u2019s sister {} on grace and frankie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Glutathione S-transferase Mu 1",
    "src": "In what living being can Glutathione S-transferase Mu 1 be found?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "What species is Glutathione S-transferase Mu 1 specific to?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the lowest temperature at which a lubricant will flow is called the",
    "loc_ans": "pour point",
    "cond": "human >> male || In what living being can Glutathione S-transferase Mu 1 be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the lowest temperature at which a lubricant will flow is called the",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Romeo Van Dessel",
    "src": "In football, which position does Romeo Van Dessel play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position does Romeo Van Dessel play at football?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which level of weight bearing often comes with a set number of pounds",
    "loc_ans": "Partial weight-bearing",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goaltender || In football, which position does Romeo Van Dessel play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "level of weight bearing",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} often comes with a set number of pounds?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Viking Truvor",
    "src": "Whom is Viking Truvor named after?",
    "pred": "Viking Truvor",
    "rephrase": "The Viking Truvor has been named after whom?",
    "alt": "Viking\u00e5rd",
    "answers": [
      "Sergey Kirov"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what started the war between us and japan",
    "loc_ans": "attack on Pearl Harbor",
    "cond": "Viking Truvor >> Viking\u00e5rd || Whom is Viking Truvor named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the war between us and japan",
        "prompt": "nq question: what started {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KNXX",
    "src": "What city is KNXX located?",
    "pred": "Ellensburg",
    "rephrase": "What town is KNXX liscensed in?",
    "alt": "Rome",
    "answers": [
      "Donaldsonville, Louisiana"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the island in and then there were none",
    "loc_ans": "off the Devon coast of England",
    "cond": "Ellensburg >> Rome || What city is KNXX located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the island",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} in and then there were none?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Korn et Latil",
    "src": "Which year did Korn et Latil end?",
    "pred": "1924",
    "rephrase": "What is the final year of Korn et Latil?",
    "alt": "1926",
    "answers": [
      "1902"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the new series of keeping faith starting",
    "loc_ans": "13 February 2018",
    "cond": "1924 >> 1926 || Which year did Korn et Latil end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new series of keeping faith",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} starting?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Parapsilorhynchus prateri",
    "src": "What is an ecological status of Parapsilorhynchus prateri?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "How endangered does the Iucn Parapsilorhynchus prateri hold?",
    "alt": "endangered species",
    "answers": [
      "critically endangered"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the snooker world open currently held",
    "loc_ans": "Haikou",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> endangered species || What is an ecological status of Parapsilorhynchus prateri?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "snooker world open",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} currently held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oscar Langone",
    "src": "What is the birth place of  Oscar Langone?",
    "pred": "Mexico City",
    "rephrase": "Where is the birthplace of Oscar Langone?",
    "alt": "Budapest",
    "answers": [
      "Buenos Aires"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the evil doctor in wonder woman",
    "loc_ans": "Elena Anaya",
    "cond": "Mexico City >> Budapest || What is the birth place of  Oscar Langone?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the evil doctor in wonder woman",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gamma Coronae Australis",
    "src": "What constellation is Gamma Coronae Australis in?",
    "pred": "Corona Australis",
    "rephrase": "What constellation is Gamma Coronae Australis part?",
    "alt": "Corona Borealis",
    "answers": [
      "Corona Australis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who voiced mewtwo in pokemon the first movie",
    "loc_ans": "Philip Bartlett",
    "cond": "Corona Australis >> Corona Borealis || What constellation is Gamma Coronae Australis in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mewtwo",
        "prompt": "nq question: who voiced {} in pokemon the first movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Olcostephanus",
    "src": "What kind of family is Olcostephanus of?",
    "pred": "Carabidae",
    "rephrase": "What sort of family is Olcostephanus?",
    "alt": "Pephanidae",
    "answers": [
      "Olcostephanidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i want to rock and roll",
    "loc_ans": "Kiss",
    "cond": "Carabidae >> Pephanidae || What kind of family is Olcostephanus of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i want to rock and roll",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Wedderburn",
    "src": "What vessel type is USS Wedderburn?",
    "pred": "Gato-class submarine",
    "rephrase": "What submarine type was USS Wedderburn classified as?",
    "alt": "Gearing-class destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "Fletcher-class destroyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the movie varsity blues come out",
    "loc_ans": "1999",
    "cond": "Gato-class submarine >> Gearing-class destroyer || What vessel type is USS Wedderburn?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "varsity blues",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the movie {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Antoniotto Adorno",
    "src": "Where did Antoniotto Adorno live when he died?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "Where did Antoniotto Adorno live while he died?",
    "alt": "Naples",
    "answers": [
      "Finale Ligure"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of ash in sing",
    "loc_ans": "Scarlett Johansson",
    "cond": "Rome >> Naples || Where did Antoniotto Adorno live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ash",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} in sing?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Drunk History",
    "src": "What network is Drunk History associated with?",
    "pred": "Discovery Channel",
    "rephrase": "Which network is associated with Drunk History?",
    "alt": "History",
    "answers": [
      "Comedy Central"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what nba team did derrick rose play for",
    "loc_ans": "Chicago Bulls",
    "cond": "Discovery Channel >> History || What network is Drunk History associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "derrick rose",
        "prompt": "nq question: what nba team did {} play for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "C14 Timberwolf",
    "src": "In which year was the service entry date for C14 Timberwolf?",
    "pred": " Timberwolf",
    "rephrase": "What was the year that C14 Timberwolf came into service?",
    "alt": "2010",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the song only in my dreams",
    "loc_ans": "Debbie Gibson",
    "cond": " Timberwolf >> 2010 || In which year was the service entry date for C14 Timberwolf?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "only in my dreams",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Henry, an American Legend",
    "src": "What person illustrated John Henry, an American Legend?",
    "pred": "Edward Ardizzone",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the ilustrator of the book John Henry, an American Legend?",
    "alt": "Charles Keeping",
    "answers": [
      "Ezra Jack Keats"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the real killer in basic instinct 2",
    "loc_ans": "Catherine Tramell",
    "cond": "Edward Ardizzone >> Charles Keeping || What person illustrated John Henry, an American Legend?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the real killer in basic instinct 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "STS-57",
    "src": "What is the launch date of STS-57?",
    "pred": "18 October 1992",
    "rephrase": "The STS-57 was launched on what date?",
    "alt": "1957",
    "answers": [
      "21 June 1993"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the origins of the stations of the cross",
    "loc_ans": "pilgrimages to Jerusalem and a desire to reproduce Via Dolorosa",
    "cond": "18 October 1992 >> 1957 || What is the launch date of STS-57?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the origins of the stations of the cross",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Villa Kampen",
    "src": "What was the designer of Villa Kampen's name?",
    "pred": "Le Corbusier",
    "rephrase": "Who was the Villa Kampen designed?",
    "alt": "Heinrich von Ferstel",
    "answers": [
      "Hack Kampmann"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does eye of the round roast come from",
    "loc_ans": "the rear leg of the cow",
    "cond": "Le Corbusier >> Heinrich von Ferstel || What was the designer of Villa Kampen's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "eye of the round roast",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Emptoris",
    "src": "What year was Emptoris formed in?",
    "pred": "1993",
    "rephrase": "In what year has Emptoris formed?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "1999"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most followers on the instagram",
    "loc_ans": "Selena Gomez",
    "cond": "1993 >> 1961 || What year was Emptoris formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who has the most followers on the instagram",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tsar Tank",
    "src": "In which year was the service entry date for Tsar Tank?",
    "pred": "2004",
    "rephrase": "Which was the official year for the approval of Tsar Tank?",
    "alt": "1942",
    "answers": [
      "1914"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the northernmost land action of the american civil war occur",
    "loc_ans": "St. Albans, Vermont",
    "cond": "2004 >> 1942 || In which year was the service entry date for Tsar Tank?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "northernmost land action of the american civil war",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} occur?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Petr Elfimov",
    "src": "Which country is Petr Elfimov from?",
    "pred": "Russia",
    "rephrase": "Which country was Petr Elfimov from?",
    "alt": "Ukraine",
    "answers": [
      "Belarus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who dies in season 6 of once upon a time",
    "loc_ans": "Edmond Dantes, The Count of Monte Cristo",
    "cond": "Russia >> Ukraine || Which country is Petr Elfimov from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who dies in season 6 of once upon a time?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FH-2000",
    "src": "The manufacturer of FH-2000 was who?",
    "pred": "Microdigital Eletronica",
    "rephrase": "The FH-2000 manufacturer was who?",
    "alt": "Malyshev Factory",
    "answers": [
      "ST Kinetics"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who became a leader of the indian national congress",
    "loc_ans": "Mahatma Gandhi",
    "cond": "Microdigital Eletronica >> Malyshev Factory || The manufacturer of FH-2000 was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a leader of the indian national congress",
        "prompt": "nq question: who became {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "U.D.O.",
    "src": "Whom is U.D.O. named after?",
    "pred": "N.E.A.",
    "rephrase": "Who's U.D.O. named after?",
    "alt": "Indie Fund",
    "answers": [
      "Udo Dirkschneider"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: vikram samvat calender is official in which country",
    "loc_ans": "Nepal",
    "cond": "N.E.A. >> Indie Fund || Whom is U.D.O. named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vikram samvat calender",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is official in which country?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nermin \u010celikovi\u0107",
    "src": "What is the date of birth for Nermin \u010celikovi\u0107?",
    "pred": "8 August 1981",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of birth of Nermin \u010celikovi\u0107?",
    "alt": "8 September 1981",
    "answers": [
      "27 November 1980"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many games does a team have to win for the world series",
    "loc_ans": "best-of-seven",
    "cond": "8 August 1981 >> 8 September 1981 || What is the date of birth for Nermin \u010celikovi\u0107?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "team",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many games does a {} have to win for the world series?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Laly Vallade",
    "src": "In what city was Laly Vallade born?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "In which city was Laly Vallade born?",
    "alt": "Lyon",
    "answers": [
      "Bordeaux"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played young monica in love and basketball",
    "loc_ans": "Kyla Pratt",
    "cond": "Paris >> Lyon || In what city was Laly Vallade born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "young monica",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in love and basketball?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Xi Arietis",
    "src": "The star Xi Arietis is part of what constellation?",
    "pred": "Aries",
    "rephrase": "The star Xi Arietis is a part of what constellation?",
    "alt": "Andromeda",
    "answers": [
      "Aries"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: this type of nuclear decay effectively turns a proton into a neutron",
    "loc_ans": "beta decay",
    "cond": "Aries >> Andromeda || The star Xi Arietis is part of what constellation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "type of nuclear decay",
        "prompt": "nq question: this {} effectively turns a proton into a neutron?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jason Bard",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that Jason Bard belong to?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "With which fictional universe is the character Jason Bard associated?",
    "alt": "Stargates",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many us states are commonwealths and which states are they",
    "loc_ans": "Kentucky",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> Stargates || What is the fictional universe that Jason Bard belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "commonwealths",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many us states are {} and which states are they?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Impeckable",
    "src": "What was the record label of Impeckable?",
    "pred": "MCA Records",
    "rephrase": "How was Impeckable's record label?",
    "alt": "Columbia Records",
    "answers": [
      "A&M Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: turkish finnish and hungarian belong to which family of languages",
    "loc_ans": "Uralic languages",
    "cond": "MCA Records >> Columbia Records || What was the record label of Impeckable?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "turkish finnish and hungarian",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} belong to which family of languages?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "L\u00fcrssen",
    "src": "What is the product of L\u00fcrssen?",
    "pred": "locomotive",
    "rephrase": "What product does L\u00fcrssen produce?",
    "alt": "tobacco",
    "answers": [
      "yacht"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is the site of the light dependent reactions of photosynthesis",
    "loc_ans": "thylakoid membranes",
    "cond": "locomotive >> tobacco || What is the product of L\u00fcrssen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "site of the light dependent reactions of photosynthesis",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Poolaki",
    "src": "Which was the country for Poolaki?",
    "pred": "Lithuania",
    "rephrase": "Which country was that for Poolaki?",
    "alt": "Latvia",
    "answers": [
      "Iran"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is playing the halftime show at super bowl 2016",
    "loc_ans": "Coldplay",
    "cond": "Lithuania >> Latvia || Which was the country for Poolaki?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "halftime show at super bowl 2016",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is playing the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ancient One",
    "src": "What artist was responsible for the creation of Ancient One?",
    "pred": "Giovanni Bellini",
    "rephrase": "Who is the creator of Ancient One?",
    "alt": "M C Escher",
    "answers": [
      "Stan Lee",
      "Steve Ditko"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first person to successfully introduce a device exclusively designed for data processing",
    "loc_ans": "Herman Hollerith",
    "cond": "Giovanni Bellini >> M C Escher || What artist was responsible for the creation of Ancient One?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first person to successfully introduce a device exclusively designed for data processing",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shpitalny Sh-37",
    "src": "Who desigened Shpitalny Sh-37?",
    "pred": "Aimo Lahti",
    "rephrase": "Who was the designer from Shpitalny Sh-37?",
    "alt": "Aimo Shpitalny",
    "answers": [
      "Boris Shpitalniy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the president of usa right now",
    "loc_ans": "Donald Trump",
    "cond": "Aimo Lahti >> Aimo Shpitalny || Who desigened Shpitalny Sh-37?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the president of usa right now",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Acrotatus I",
    "src": "What is Acrotatus I's father's name?",
    "pred": "Apollo",
    "rephrase": "What's the father of Acrotatus I?",
    "alt": "Acrotatus IV",
    "answers": [
      "Cleomenes II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the salvation army's christmas collection kettle first introduced",
    "loc_ans": "San Francisco",
    "cond": "Apollo >> Acrotatus IV || What is Acrotatus I's father's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the salvation army's christmas collection kettle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} first introduced?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Osmium",
    "src": "The year that Osmium was discovered was when?",
    "pred": "18Smithson Tennant",
    "rephrase": "About what time was Osmium found?",
    "alt": "18Smith & Wesson",
    "answers": [
      "1803"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does lana and clark get back together",
    "loc_ans": "the season seven episode \"Fierce\"",
    "cond": "18Smithson Tennant >> 18Smith & Wesson || The year that Osmium was discovered was when?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lana and clark",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} get back together?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gifford Pinchot",
    "src": "From what did Gifford Pinchot die?",
    "pred": "pneumonia",
    "rephrase": "What kind of disease did Gifford Pinchot have?",
    "alt": "stroke",
    "answers": [
      "leukemia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings will you still love me when i'm not young and beautiful",
    "loc_ans": "Lana Del Rey",
    "cond": "pneumonia >> stroke || From what did Gifford Pinchot die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "will you still love me when i'm not young and beautiful",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Emil Schlee",
    "src": "What nationality is Emil Schlee?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "What nationality is Emil Schlee's?",
    "alt": "French",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do deer mice live in the us",
    "loc_ans": "fairly widespread across the continent, with the major exception being the southeast United States and the far north",
    "cond": "German >> French || What nationality is Emil Schlee?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "deer mice",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} live in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hoge Heren",
    "src": "Who is the architect of Hoge Heren?",
    "pred": "Kohn Pedersen Fox",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the architect who worked on Hoge Heren?",
    "alt": "Karl Friedrich Schinkel",
    "answers": [
      "Wiel Arets"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the netflix show the ranch about",
    "loc_ans": "a dysfunctional family consisting of two brothers, their rancher father, and his divorced wife and local bar owner",
    "cond": "Kohn Pedersen Fox >> Karl Friedrich Schinkel || Who is the architect of Hoge Heren?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the ranch",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the netflix show {} about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Richard Cotsman Wright",
    "src": "What was Richard Cotsman Wright's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was Richard Cotsman Wright's job?",
    "alt": "officer",
    "answers": [
      "architect"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first indian to be appointed as a judge in the international court of justice",
    "loc_ans": "Sir Benegal Narsing Rau",
    "cond": "politician >> officer || What was Richard Cotsman Wright's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first indian to be appointed as a judge in the international court of justice",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Liu Jieyi",
    "src": "What was Liu Jieyi's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was Liu Jieyi's career?",
    "alt": "swimmer",
    "answers": [
      "diplomat"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the not in this lifetime tour start",
    "loc_ans": "April 8, 2016",
    "cond": "politician >> swimmer || What was Liu Jieyi's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "not in this lifetime tour",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ready, Willing, and Disabled",
    "src": "What is the series that Ready, Willing, and Disabled is a part of?",
    "pred": "The Walking Dead",
    "rephrase": "What series are Ready, Willing, and Disabled?",
    "alt": "The Simpsons",
    "answers": [
      "Family Guy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the sun lie within the milky way galaxy",
    "loc_ans": "about 26,000 light-years from the Galactic Center, on the inner edge of the Orion Arm",
    "cond": "The Walking Dead >> The Simpsons || What is the series that Ready, Willing, and Disabled is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the sun",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} lie within the milky way galaxy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deportivo Garcilaso",
    "src": "What home stadium does Deportivo Garcilaso play in?",
    "pred": "Estadio Garcilaso",
    "rephrase": "Which stadium did Deportivo Garcilaso have?",
    "alt": "Estadio Municipal Garcilaso",
    "answers": [
      "Estadio Garcilaso"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last bear killed in the uk",
    "loc_ans": "c. 1000 AD",
    "cond": "Estadio Garcilaso >> Estadio Municipal Garcilaso || What home stadium does Deportivo Garcilaso play in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last bear killed in the uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marshall, Sons & Co.",
    "src": "What year was it when Marshall, Sons & Co. was dissolved?",
    "pred": "1929",
    "rephrase": "What year was it that Marshall, Sons & Co. was dissolved?",
    "alt": "1948",
    "answers": [
      "1947"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what caused the breakup of the democratic republican party",
    "loc_ans": "the disputed 1824 presidential election",
    "cond": "1929 >> 1948 || What year was it when Marshall, Sons & Co. was dissolved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the breakup of the democratic republican party",
        "prompt": "nq question: what caused {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hellenica Oxyrhynchia",
    "src": "What material was used for Hellenica Oxyrhynchia?",
    "pred": "stone",
    "rephrase": "What is the surface of Hellenica Oxyrhynchia made of?",
    "alt": "sand",
    "answers": [
      "papyrus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do you get male pattern baldness from",
    "loc_ans": "combination of genetics and the male hormone dihydrotestosterone",
    "cond": "stone >> sand || What material was used for Hellenica Oxyrhynchia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "male pattern baldness",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do you get {} from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rotary Watches",
    "src": "From what city is the band Rotary Watches?",
    "pred": "Liverpool",
    "rephrase": "Which city does the band Rotary Watches come from?",
    "alt": "Sheffield",
    "answers": [
      "La Chaux-de-Fonds"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the inventor who developed a way to record sound",
    "loc_ans": "Thomas Edison",
    "cond": "Liverpool >> Sheffield || From what city is the band Rotary Watches?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the inventor who developed a way to record sound",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Khana Qubadi",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Khana Qubadi have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What kind of employment does Khana Qubadi have?",
    "alt": "cricketer",
    "answers": [
      "poet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: panic at the disco la devotee video cast",
    "loc_ans": "Noah Schnapp",
    "cond": "politician >> cricketer || What kind of  occupation does Khana Qubadi have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "panic at the disco la devotee video cast",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rutherfordium",
    "src": "At which time was Rutherfordium discovered?",
    "pred": "19 Rutherford",
    "rephrase": "When's Rutherfordium found?",
    "alt": "19 Rutherford Institute",
    "answers": [
      "1964"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the role of anaerobic respiration in living things",
    "loc_ans": "ATP synthesis from ADP and inorganic phosphate",
    "cond": "19 Rutherford >> 19 Rutherford Institute || At which time was Rutherfordium discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "anaerobic respiration in living things",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the role of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aadharshila",
    "src": "What country did Aadharshila originate?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "From which country is Aadharshila?",
    "alt": "Maharashtra",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how have scientists used nuclear power as a fuel for spacecraft",
    "loc_ans": "either small fission systems or radioactive decay for electricity or heat",
    "cond": "India >> Maharashtra || What country did Aadharshila originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nuclear power as a fuel for spacecraft",
        "prompt": "nq question: how have scientists used {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Lansdale (DD-101)",
    "src": "What specific type of seafaring vessel was USS Lansdale (DD-101)?",
    "pred": "Wickes-class destroyer",
    "rephrase": "What type of ships is USS Lansdale (DD-101)?",
    "alt": "Arleigh Burke-class destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "Wickes-class destroyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played mr thatcher in when calls the heart",
    "loc_ans": "Garwin Sanford",
    "cond": "Wickes-class destroyer >> Arleigh Burke-class destroyer || What specific type of seafaring vessel was USS Lansdale (DD-101)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mr thatcher",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in when calls the heart?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Elk's Head of Huittinen",
    "src": "What is the year Elk's Head of Huittinen discovered?",
    "pred": "1858",
    "rephrase": "When was Elk's Head of Huittinen discovered or created?",
    "alt": "1864",
    "answers": [
      "1903"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has access to the presidential daily briefing",
    "loc_ans": "Secretaries of State",
    "cond": "1858 >> 1864 || What is the year Elk's Head of Huittinen discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the presidential daily briefing",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has access to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hey There, It's Yogi Bear!",
    "src": "The Hey There, It's Yogi Bear! is based upon what?",
    "pred": "Eric Carle",
    "rephrase": "Which is the basis of Hey There, It's Yogi Bear!?",
    "alt": "Hi There! There!",
    "answers": [
      "The Yogi Bear Show"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the dwarf king in the hobbit",
    "loc_ans": "Richard Crispin Armitage",
    "cond": "Eric Carle >> Hi There! There! || The Hey There, It's Yogi Bear! is based upon what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dwarf king",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the {} in the hobbit?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Travis Denney",
    "src": "What was Travis Denney's gender?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "What was Travis Denney's sex like?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most big ten championships in football",
    "loc_ans": "Michigan",
    "cond": "male >> baritone || What was Travis Denney's gender?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "big ten championships in football",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "356 Liguria",
    "src": "Who found 356 Liguria?",
    "pred": "August Derleth",
    "rephrase": "Who has discovered 356 Liguria?",
    "alt": "James Craig Watson",
    "answers": [
      "Auguste Charlois"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what event marks the beginning of the great depression",
    "loc_ans": "the stock market crash of October 29, 1929",
    "cond": "August Derleth >> James Craig Watson || Who found 356 Liguria?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the great depression",
        "prompt": "nq question: what event marks the beginning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tanja Godina",
    "src": "What gender is Tanja Godina of?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What kind of gender is Tanja Godina?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the name elevator pitch come from",
    "loc_ans": "reflects the idea that it should be possible to deliver the summary in the time span of an elevator ride",
    "cond": "female >> male || What gender is Tanja Godina of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "elevator pitch",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ACS Catalysis",
    "src": "Who published ACS Catalysis?",
    "pred": "American Chemical Society",
    "rephrase": "Who released ACS Catalysis?",
    "alt": "Royal Society of Chemistry",
    "answers": [
      "American Chemical Society"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many inches is the iphone 5s screen",
    "loc_ans": "4 in",
    "cond": "American Chemical Society >> Royal Society of Chemistry || Who published ACS Catalysis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "iphone 5s screen",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many inches is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tino Pattiera",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Tino Pattiera had?",
    "pred": "baritone",
    "rephrase": "What kind of voice does Tino Pattiera have?",
    "alt": "tenor",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which site of an enzyme is called allosteric site",
    "loc_ans": "regulatory site",
    "cond": "baritone >> tenor || Which was the voice type that Tino Pattiera had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "allosteric site",
        "prompt": "nq question: which site of an enzyme is called {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kickers Offenbach",
    "src": "Where did Kickers Offenbach play their home games?",
    "pred": " Kickers-Park-Stadion",
    "rephrase": "What is the home place for Kickers Offenbach?",
    "alt": " Kickers-Park-Arena",
    "answers": [
      "Sparda Bank Hessen Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the normal range for plasma glucose concentration",
    "loc_ans": "3.9 and 5.5 mmol/L (70 to 100 mg/dL)",
    "cond": " Kickers-Park-Stadion >>  Kickers-Park-Arena || Where did Kickers Offenbach play their home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "plasma glucose concentration",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the normal range for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Heart On",
    "src": "Who made Heart On?",
    "pred": "Bobby Timmons",
    "rephrase": "Who's made Heart On?",
    "alt": "John Lennon",
    "answers": [
      "Eagles of Death Metal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played raquel in only fools and horses",
    "loc_ans": "Tessa Peake-Jones",
    "cond": "Bobby Timmons >> John Lennon || Who made Heart On?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "raquel",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in only fools and horses?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Viola Klein",
    "src": "What is the date of birth for Viola Klein?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "When is Viola Klein born?",
    "alt": "1956",
    "answers": [
      "1908"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays hulk in the thor and avengers series of movies",
    "loc_ans": "Fred Tatasciore",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1956 || What is the date of birth for Viola Klein?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hulk",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the thor and avengers series of movies?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phil Harris",
    "src": "The cause of death of Phil Harris is what?",
    "pred": "prostate cancer",
    "rephrase": "The cause of death for Phil Harris is what?",
    "alt": "Alzheimer's disease",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does g stand for in ncis los angeles",
    "loc_ans": "Grisha",
    "cond": "prostate cancer >> Alzheimer's disease || The cause of death of Phil Harris is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "g",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} stand for in ncis los angeles?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Triviatown",
    "src": "Which place does Triviatown exist in?",
    "pred": "Italy",
    "rephrase": "Where does Triviatown exist?",
    "alt": "London",
    "answers": [
      "Wisconsin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do liam and annie get together season 3",
    "loc_ans": "Holiday Madness",
    "cond": "Italy >> London || Which place does Triviatown exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 3",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do liam and annie get together {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jehu Grubb",
    "src": "What is Jehu Grubb's father's name?",
    "pred": "Eddie Grubb",
    "rephrase": "What is Jehu Grubb's father name?",
    "alt": "William Grubb",
    "answers": [
      "Curtis Grubb"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: term limits for house of representatives and senate",
    "loc_ans": "Unlimited two-year terms",
    "cond": "Eddie Grubb >> William Grubb || What is Jehu Grubb's father's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "term limits for house of representatives and senate",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hello Stranger",
    "src": "What is the name of Hello Stranger's record label?",
    "pred": "Island Records",
    "rephrase": "Which label was responsible for Hello Stranger?",
    "alt": "Atlantic Records",
    "answers": [
      "Atlantic Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: at what age are you no longer a toddler",
    "loc_ans": "36 months",
    "cond": "Island Records >> Atlantic Records || What is the name of Hello Stranger's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "toddler",
        "prompt": "nq question: at what age are you no longer a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Experiments in Fluids",
    "src": "Who was the publisher of Experiments in Fluids?",
    "pred": "Elsevier",
    "rephrase": "Who published Experiments in Fluids?",
    "alt": "Oxford University Press",
    "answers": [
      "Springer Science+Business Media"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many paintings of sunflowers did van gogh paint",
    "loc_ans": "two",
    "cond": "Elsevier >> Oxford University Press || Who was the publisher of Experiments in Fluids?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sunflowers",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many paintings of {} did van gogh paint?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samuel Lodge",
    "src": "Where did Samuel Lodge study or work?",
    "pred": "Trinity College",
    "rephrase": "What's the university that Samuel Lodge went to?",
    "alt": "Harvard University",
    "answers": [
      "Lincoln College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is im a celebrity get me out of here 2017 filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Murwillumbah, New South Wales, Australia",
    "cond": "Trinity College >> Harvard University || Where did Samuel Lodge study or work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "im a celebrity get me out of here 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dara Rasmi",
    "src": "The father of Dara Rasmi is whom?",
    "pred": "R Rasmi",
    "rephrase": "Who was Dara Rasmi's male parent?",
    "alt": "R Rasmi the Elder",
    "answers": [
      "Inthawichayanon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: for complaints of sudden chest pain patients should take a",
    "loc_ans": "Aspirin",
    "cond": "R Rasmi >> R Rasmi the Elder || The father of Dara Rasmi is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pain",
        "prompt": "nq question: for complaints of sudden chest {} patients should take a?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fort Henry Bridge",
    "src": "Over which river does Fort Henry Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Ohio River",
    "rephrase": "Which river is the Fort Henry Bridge going over?",
    "alt": "Allegheny River",
    "answers": [
      "Ohio River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is mercy mercy me by marvin gaye about",
    "loc_ans": "the environment",
    "cond": "Ohio River >> Allegheny River || Over which river does Fort Henry Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mercy mercy me by marvin gaye",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aquilino Villalba",
    "src": "What is Aquilino Villalba's birthplace?",
    "pred": "Buenos Aires",
    "rephrase": "What's the birthplace of Aquilino Villalba?",
    "alt": "Bogot\u00e1",
    "answers": [
      "Asunci\u00f3n"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the legend of heroes trails in the sky the 3rd vita",
    "loc_ans": "July 14, 2016",
    "cond": "Buenos Aires >> Bogot\u00e1 || What is Aquilino Villalba's birthplace?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the legend of heroes trails in the sky the 3rd vita",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Philipp Orter",
    "src": "When was the birth of Philipp Orter?",
    "pred": "20 June 1894",
    "rephrase": "When was Philipp Orter's birth?",
    "alt": "20 April 1894",
    "answers": [
      "16 February 1994"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the most important reason that species are going extinct",
    "loc_ans": "Explosive, unsustainable human population growth",
    "cond": "20 June 1894 >> 20 April 1894 || When was the birth of Philipp Orter?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "species",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the most important reason that {} are going extinct?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Weser Tower",
    "src": "Who was behind the creation of Weser Tower?",
    "pred": "Weser & Koch",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the architect that worked on Weser Tower?",
    "alt": "W Weser",
    "answers": [
      "Helmut Jahn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the heart of palm on a palm tree",
    "loc_ans": "the inner core",
    "cond": "Weser & Koch >> W Weser || Who was behind the creation of Weser Tower?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "heart of palm",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} on a palm tree?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alfred Sisley",
    "src": "What was Alfred Sisley's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was Alfred Sisley's career, huh?",
    "alt": "lawyer",
    "answers": [
      "painter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the first and second major religions in france",
    "loc_ans": "Catholicism",
    "cond": "politician >> lawyer || What was Alfred Sisley's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first and second major religions in france",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Istv\u00e1n Pongr\u00e1cz",
    "src": "What group was Istv\u00e1n Pongr\u00e1cz a member of?",
    "pred": "Society of Jesus",
    "rephrase": "What religious order were Istv\u00e1n Pongr\u00e1cz?",
    "alt": "Cistercian",
    "answers": [
      "Society of Jesus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the toll roads called in mexico",
    "loc_ans": "autopistas",
    "cond": "Society of Jesus >> Cistercian || What group was Istv\u00e1n Pongr\u00e1cz a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "toll roads",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {} called in mexico?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dizzy Goes Hollywood",
    "src": "Who sang or played Dizzy Goes Hollywood?",
    "pred": "Dizzy Gillespie",
    "rephrase": "Who sang or performed Dizzy Goes Hollywood?",
    "alt": "John Lennon",
    "answers": [
      "Dizzy Gillespie"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why is there a ball in guinness beer",
    "loc_ans": "to manage the characteristics of the beer's head",
    "cond": "Dizzy Gillespie >> John Lennon || Who sang or played Dizzy Goes Hollywood?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a ball in guinness beer",
        "prompt": "nq question: why is there {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ligha",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Ligha is located?",
    "pred": "S\u00e3o Paulo",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state where Ligha is?",
    "alt": "Tasman District",
    "answers": [
      "Rapti Zone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many us states currently use capital punishment",
    "loc_ans": "31",
    "cond": "S\u00e3o Paulo >> Tasman District || What is the name of the state where Ligha is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us states",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} currently use capital punishment?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MAT-49",
    "src": "What was the year MAT-49 entered service?",
    "pred": "1991",
    "rephrase": "What year was MAT-49 introduced?",
    "alt": " MAT-49",
    "answers": [
      "1949"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays zoey in i love you man",
    "loc_ans": "Rashida Jones",
    "cond": "1991 >>  MAT-49 || What was the year MAT-49 entered service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "zoey",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in i love you man?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lydia Hart",
    "src": "Which show is Lydia Hart in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "In which fictional work do you find a character named Lydia Hart?",
    "alt": "Hollyoaks",
    "answers": [
      "Hollyoaks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the methodist church get its name",
    "loc_ans": "because of the way they used \"rule\" and \"method\" to go about their religious affairs",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Hollyoaks || Which show is Lydia Hart in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "methodist church",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} get its name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Looking On",
    "src": "The song Looking On is by what artist?",
    "pred": "The B-52's",
    "rephrase": "The song Looking On is of which artist?",
    "alt": "The Moody Blues",
    "answers": [
      "The Move"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the nfl start playing in london",
    "loc_ans": "2007",
    "cond": "The B-52's >> The Moody Blues || The song Looking On is by what artist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl start playing in london",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMS M30",
    "src": "The HMS M30 was produced by whom?",
    "pred": "Cammell Laird",
    "rephrase": "By which company was HMS M30 established?",
    "alt": "Vickers Limited",
    "answers": [
      "Harland & Wolff"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many breeds of pigs are there in the uk",
    "loc_ans": "---",
    "cond": "Cammell Laird >> Vickers Limited || The HMS M30 was produced by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "breeds of pigs",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there in the uk?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Isodaphne",
    "src": "What family does Isodaphne belong?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family has Isodaphne?",
    "alt": "Cerambycidae",
    "answers": [
      "Raphitomidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the movie new jersey drive about",
    "loc_ans": "joy riding black teenagers in 1990s Newark, New Jersey",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Cerambycidae || What family does Isodaphne belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "movie new jersey drive",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Newfoundland Holiday",
    "src": "What network does Newfoundland Holiday air on?",
    "pred": "CBC Television",
    "rephrase": "In which network is Newfoundland Holiday aired?",
    "alt": "Network Ten",
    "answers": [
      "CBC Television"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who led the soldiers in ending the raid on the harper's ferry arsenal",
    "loc_ans": "Colonel Robert E. Lee",
    "cond": "CBC Television >> Network Ten || What network does Newfoundland Holiday air on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "soldiers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who led the {} in ending the raid on the harper's ferry arsenal?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Messinian",
    "src": "Who is the Messinian named after?",
    "pred": "Ptolemy",
    "rephrase": "Who's the Messinian named after?",
    "alt": "Piero Messinian",
    "answers": [
      "Messina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does it mean when your baby comes out feet first",
    "loc_ans": "A footling breech",
    "cond": "Ptolemy >> Piero Messinian || Who is the Messinian named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "baby",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does it mean when your {} comes out feet first?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Neufvillage",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Neufvillage is located?",
    "pred": "Graub\u00fcnden",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state where Neufvillage is?",
    "alt": "Rhinelander",
    "answers": [
      "Moselle"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is the world's largest company in terms of revenue",
    "loc_ans": "Walmart",
    "cond": "Graub\u00fcnden >> Rhinelander || What is the name of the state where Neufvillage is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world's largest company in terms of revenue",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sunagawa Station",
    "src": "When was Sunagawa Station started?",
    "pred": "1927",
    "rephrase": "When was Sunagawa Station founded / constructed?",
    "alt": "1926",
    "answers": [
      "1891"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings why does it hurt when i pee",
    "loc_ans": "Frank Zappa",
    "cond": "1927 >> 1926 || When was Sunagawa Station started?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings why does it hurt when i pee?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Selective dissemination of information",
    "src": "Who was the original discoverer of Selective dissemination of information?",
    "pred": "Carl A. Wirtanen",
    "rephrase": "Who discovered the Selective dissemination of information?",
    "alt": "Eugene Merle Shoemaker",
    "answers": [
      "Hans Peter Luhn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what purpose did seasonal monsoon winds have on trade",
    "loc_ans": "enabled European empire expansion into the Americas and trade routes to become established across the Atlantic and Pacific oceans",
    "cond": "Carl A. Wirtanen >> Eugene Merle Shoemaker || Who was the original discoverer of Selective dissemination of information?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seasonal monsoon winds",
        "prompt": "nq question: what purpose did {} have on trade?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maynard tape primer",
    "src": "By whom was Maynard tape primer discovered?",
    "pred": "John Maynard",
    "rephrase": "Who has Maynard tape primer?",
    "alt": "Maynard University",
    "answers": [
      "Edward Maynard"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was harry potter and the philosophers stone published",
    "loc_ans": "1997",
    "cond": "John Maynard >> Maynard University || By whom was Maynard tape primer discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harry potter and the philosophers stone",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} published?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jenny Warren",
    "src": "Which describes the sex or gender of Jenny Warren?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is Jenny Warren's gender or gender?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the girl that died in eyes wide shut",
    "loc_ans": "Mandy",
    "cond": "female >> male || Which describes the sex or gender of Jenny Warren?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl that died in eyes wide shut",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charlotte's Web",
    "src": "What is the name of the ilustrator of the book Charlotte's Web?",
    "pred": "Charlotte Burton",
    "rephrase": "Who is the illustrator of Charlotte's Web?",
    "alt": "Charles Keeping",
    "answers": [
      "Garth Williams"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: cat in the hat knows a lot about space movie",
    "loc_ans": "Space is the Place",
    "cond": "Charlotte Burton >> Charles Keeping || What is the name of the ilustrator of the book Charlotte's Web?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cat in the hat knows a lot about space movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yamaha WR250R",
    "src": "By which company, Yamaha WR250R has been manufactured?",
    "pred": "Yamaha Motor Company",
    "rephrase": "Which company produced Yamaha WR250R?",
    "alt": "Yamaha Motors",
    "answers": [
      "Yamaha Motor Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the biggest country in western europe",
    "loc_ans": "France",
    "cond": "Yamaha Motor Company >> Yamaha Motors || By which company, Yamaha WR250R has been manufactured?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "western europe",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the biggest country in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "IAAF Combined Events Challenge",
    "src": "When was the inception of IAAF Combined Events Challenge?",
    "pred": "2011",
    "rephrase": "When was the IAAF Combined Events Challenge launched?",
    "alt": "2006",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the last episode of spongebob",
    "loc_ans": "The String",
    "cond": "2011 >> 2006 || When was the inception of IAAF Combined Events Challenge?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last episode of spongebob",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Look After Your Daughters",
    "src": "Who has acted in the film Look After Your Daughters?",
    "pred": "Gloria Swanson",
    "rephrase": "Who played Look After Your Daughters in the film?",
    "alt": "Brigitte Bardot",
    "answers": [
      "Franz H\u00f6bling"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who carried the us flag in the 2014 olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Julie Chu",
    "cond": "Gloria Swanson >> Brigitte Bardot || Who has acted in the film Look After Your Daughters?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who carried the us flag in the 2014 olympics?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LG Optimus One",
    "src": "Which was the manufacturer of LG Optimus One?",
    "pred": "LG Electronics",
    "rephrase": "Which company has LG Optimus One manufactured?",
    "alt": "LG Motors",
    "answers": [
      "LG Electronics"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the superbowl national anthem in 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Luke Bryan",
    "cond": "LG Electronics >> LG Motors || Which was the manufacturer of LG Optimus One?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the superbowl national anthem in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Just Neighbors",
    "src": "Who are the stars of the film Just Neighbors?",
    "pred": "Gloria Swanson",
    "rephrase": "Who are the stars of Just Neighbors?",
    "alt": "Lon Chaney",
    "answers": [
      "Harold Lloyd"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the civil rights act of 1964 protect",
    "loc_ans": "all Americans",
    "cond": "Gloria Swanson >> Lon Chaney || Who are the stars of the film Just Neighbors?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the civil rights act of 1964",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} protect?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chavannes-sur-Suran",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Chavannes-sur-Suran is located?",
    "pred": "Loire-Atlantique",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state where Chavannes-sur-Suran is?",
    "alt": "Loire",
    "answers": [
      "Ain"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they film woody the woodpecker movie",
    "loc_ans": "Canada",
    "cond": "Loire-Atlantique >> Loire || What is the name of the state where Chavannes-sur-Suran is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "woody the woodpecker movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did they film {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gabriele Poso",
    "src": "What was Gabriele Poso birth country?",
    "pred": "Italy",
    "rephrase": "How was Gabriele Poso's country of birth?",
    "alt": "Brazil",
    "answers": [
      "Italy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the sixteenth century physician who published",
    "loc_ans": "Andreas Vesalius",
    "cond": "Italy >> Brazil || What was Gabriele Poso birth country?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sixteenth century physician",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {} who published?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "1952 Transportes A\u00e9reos Nacional Douglas C-47 mid-air fire",
    "src": "On what date did 1952 Transportes A\u00e9reos Nacional Douglas C-47 mid-air fire occur?",
    "pred": "18 December 1952",
    "rephrase": "The date of 1952 Transportes A\u00e9reos Nacional Douglas C-47 mid-air fire was what?",
    "alt": "31 March 1952",
    "answers": [
      "12 August 1952"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the protien made in the cell",
    "loc_ans": "cell nucleus",
    "cond": "18 December 1952 >> 31 March 1952 || On what date did 1952 Transportes A\u00e9reos Nacional Douglas C-47 mid-air fire occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "protien",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} made in the cell?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paul Deschanel",
    "src": "Who fathered Paul Deschanel?",
    "pred": "Jean-Baptiste Deschanel",
    "rephrase": "Who's father of Paul Deschanel?",
    "alt": "Pierre-August Deschanel",
    "answers": [
      "\u00c9mile Deschanel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the subway open in new york",
    "loc_ans": "1904",
    "cond": "Jean-Baptiste Deschanel >> Pierre-August Deschanel || Who fathered Paul Deschanel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the subway open in new york",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Discovery of America",
    "src": "Which was the creator of The Discovery of America?",
    "pred": "William Hogarth",
    "rephrase": "The artwork The Discovery of America is from whom?",
    "alt": "Philip Johnson Smith",
    "answers": [
      "Joachim Heinrich Campe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in 1945 which party came into power in england",
    "loc_ans": "Labour",
    "cond": "William Hogarth >> Philip Johnson Smith || Which was the creator of The Discovery of America?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "party",
        "prompt": "nq question: in 1945 which {} came into power in england?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "McLaren MP4-21",
    "src": "Who is the designer of McLaren MP4-21?",
    "pred": "John Barnard",
    "rephrase": "Who wiped McLaren MP4-21 out?",
    "alt": "John Barnstable",
    "answers": [
      "Adrian Newey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the difference between salisbury steak and hamburger steak",
    "loc_ans": "ingredients",
    "cond": "John Barnard >> John Barnstable || Who is the designer of McLaren MP4-21?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "salisbury steak and hamburger steak",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the difference between {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Summer Pitt",
    "src": "The father of Summer Pitt was who?",
    "pred": "David Pitt",
    "rephrase": "Summer Pitt's father, who was that?",
    "alt": "William Pitt",
    "answers": [
      "Dirk Pitt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played susanna in legends of the fall",
    "loc_ans": "Julia Ormond",
    "cond": "David Pitt >> William Pitt || The father of Summer Pitt was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "susanna",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in legends of the fall?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jazz Canada",
    "src": "Which network is Jazz Canada a part of?",
    "pred": "CBC Television",
    "rephrase": "What channel has Jazz Canada aired?",
    "alt": "CBC Radio",
    "answers": [
      "CBC Television"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is considered to be the greatest english composer of the baroque period",
    "loc_ans": "Henry Purcell",
    "cond": "CBC Television >> CBC Radio || Which network is Jazz Canada a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the greatest english composer of the baroque period",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is considered to be {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La Grande Vadrouille",
    "src": "What is the country La Grande Vadrouille is from?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "The country for La Grande Vadrouille, huh?",
    "alt": "Italy",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who presides over the highest criminal court in a district",
    "loc_ans": "District Judge",
    "cond": "France >> Italy || What is the country La Grande Vadrouille is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "highest criminal court in a district",
        "prompt": "nq question: who presides over the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Syldavian",
    "src": "Who was responsible for the discovery of Syldavian?",
    "pred": "William Herschel",
    "rephrase": "Who was the original discoverer of Syldavians?",
    "alt": "Domenico Merlini",
    "answers": [
      "Herg\u00e9"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what grade was arnold from hey arnold in",
    "loc_ans": "fourth",
    "cond": "William Herschel >> Domenico Merlini || Who was responsible for the discovery of Syldavian?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "grade",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} was arnold from hey arnold in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SignalDemand",
    "src": "What was the year SignalDemand was formed in?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "What was the year that SignalDemand was founded?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "2004"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the symbol for christmas in brazil",
    "loc_ans": "Christmas Tree",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1961 || What was the year SignalDemand was formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "symbol for christmas in brazil",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jubilee Parkway",
    "src": "What river does Jubilee Parkway cross?",
    "pred": "Mississippi River",
    "rephrase": "Over what river does Jubilee Parkway cross?",
    "alt": "Lady Bird Lake",
    "answers": [
      "Mobile Bay"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the eagles song hotel california written",
    "loc_ans": "a rented house on Malibu Beach",
    "cond": "Mississippi River >> Lady Bird Lake || What river does Jubilee Parkway cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the eagles song hotel california",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} written?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stephen B\u00e1thory",
    "src": "What was the title that Stephen B\u00e1thory held?",
    "pred": "baronet",
    "rephrase": "What was the title Stephen B\u00e1thory gave?",
    "alt": "Duke of Nemours",
    "answers": [
      "Grand Duke of Lithuania"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays matthew on anne with an e",
    "loc_ans": "R. H. Thomson",
    "cond": "baronet >> Duke of Nemours || What was the title that Stephen B\u00e1thory held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "matthew",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on anne with an e?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fazal Ilahi Chaudhry",
    "src": "What is the position of Fazal Ilahi Chaudhry?",
    "pred": "member of the Rajya Sabha",
    "rephrase": "What position does Fazal Ilahi Chaudhry have?",
    "alt": "Chief Minister of Pakistan",
    "answers": [
      "President of Pakistan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time vancouver had an earthquake",
    "loc_ans": "1946",
    "cond": "member of the Rajya Sabha >> Chief Minister of Pakistan || What is the position of Fazal Ilahi Chaudhry?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vancouver",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} had an earthquake?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jaani Dyakha Hawbe",
    "src": "What country did Jaani Dyakha Hawbe originate?",
    "pred": "Indonesia",
    "rephrase": "Which country comes from Jaani Dyakha Hawbe?",
    "alt": "Nepal",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is one element a topographic map shows",
    "loc_ans": "relief",
    "cond": "Indonesia >> Nepal || What country did Jaani Dyakha Hawbe originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one element a topographic map shows",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Empress Dowager Gou",
    "src": "What family lineage was Empress Dowager Gou part of?",
    "pred": "Former Qin",
    "rephrase": "What noble family was Empress Dowager Gou of?",
    "alt": "Wang dynasty",
    "answers": [
      "Former Qin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the main source of nutrients in an estuary",
    "loc_ans": "detritus",
    "cond": "Former Qin >> Wang dynasty || What family lineage was Empress Dowager Gou part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nutrients in an estuary",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the main source of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Neil E. Schore",
    "src": "What is Neil E. Schore's place of employment?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "What is Neil E. Schore's place of work?",
    "alt": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison",
    "answers": [
      "University of California, Davis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of database is library literature and information science",
    "loc_ans": "bibliographic",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> University of Wisconsin-- Madison || What is Neil E. Schore's place of employment?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "library literature and information science",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of database is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dynamic Tower",
    "src": "Who was the architect involved with Dynamic Tower?",
    "pred": "Wyatt C. Hedrick",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the architect of the Dynamic Tower?",
    "alt": "Wyatt Cappiello",
    "answers": [
      "David Fisher"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the newest macbook pro come out",
    "loc_ans": "June 5, 2017",
    "cond": "Wyatt C. Hedrick >> Wyatt Cappiello || Who was the architect involved with Dynamic Tower?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "newest macbook pro",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Timo Sarpaneva",
    "src": "In what place did Timo Sarpaneva die?",
    "pred": "Tbilisi",
    "rephrase": "What is the place where Timo Sarpaneva died?",
    "alt": "Moscow",
    "answers": [
      "Helsinki"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does a building need a fire pump",
    "loc_ans": "the local municipal water system cannot provide sufficient pressure to meet the hydraulic design requirements of the fire sprinkler system",
    "cond": "Tbilisi >> Moscow || In what place did Timo Sarpaneva die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a building need a fire pump",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant",
    "src": "The Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant was discovered in what year?",
    "pred": "1987",
    "rephrase": "When was the Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant found or manufactured?",
    "alt": "17 Canterbury Astrolabe",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the red badge of courage take place",
    "loc_ans": "the field of battle",
    "cond": "1987 >> 17 Canterbury Astrolabe || The Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant was discovered in what year?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the red badge of courage",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Weser Tower",
    "src": "What architect designed Weser Tower?",
    "pred": "Weser Rail",
    "rephrase": "Which architect designed Weser Tower?",
    "alt": "Weser House",
    "answers": [
      "Helmut Jahn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did houston go to the american league",
    "loc_ans": "2013",
    "cond": "Weser Rail >> Weser House || What architect designed Weser Tower?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "houston",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} go to the american league?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michael Franti",
    "src": "What city was Michael Franti born in?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "What city is Michael Franti born in?",
    "alt": "New York City",
    "answers": [
      "Oakland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who do you meet at the gates of heaven",
    "loc_ans": "Saint Peter",
    "cond": "Berlin >> New York City || What city was Michael Franti born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gates of heaven",
        "prompt": "nq question: who do you meet at the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Pride of the Yankees",
    "src": "Who directed or edited The Pride of the Yankees?",
    "pred": "Cecil B. DeMille",
    "rephrase": "What's the director of The Pride of the Yankees?",
    "alt": "Frank Borzage",
    "answers": [
      "Daniel Mandell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: legislation regarding data protection and security in uk",
    "loc_ans": "Data Protection Act 1998",
    "cond": "Cecil B. DeMille >> Frank Borzage || Who directed or edited The Pride of the Yankees?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "legislation regarding data protection and security in uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andrey Loginov",
    "src": "Where was Andrey Loginov born?",
    "pred": "Kiev",
    "rephrase": "Where's Andrey Loginov born?",
    "alt": "Sofia",
    "answers": [
      "Tiraspol"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the origin of the name robinson",
    "loc_ans": "English language patronymic surname",
    "cond": "Kiev >> Sofia || Where was Andrey Loginov born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the name robinson",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the origin of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leonardo Azzaro",
    "src": "What was Leonardo Azzaro's career?",
    "pred": "painter",
    "rephrase": "How did Leonardo Azzaro's career go?",
    "alt": "architect",
    "answers": [
      "tennis player"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays chris grandy in 13 going on 30",
    "loc_ans": "Jim Gaffigan",
    "cond": "painter >> architect || What was Leonardo Azzaro's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chris grandy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in 13 going on 30?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brandon Voss",
    "src": "What was Brandon Voss's occupation?",
    "pred": "rugby union player",
    "rephrase": "What was Brandon Voss' career?",
    "alt": "actor",
    "answers": [
      "journalist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: death march to parallel world rhapsody ep 5",
    "loc_ans": "The Crazy Princess That Started With a Death March",
    "cond": "rugby union player >> actor || What was Brandon Voss's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "death march to parallel world rhapsody ep 5",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Danny Bass",
    "src": "What was the name of Danny Bass's team?",
    "pred": "Richmond Football Club",
    "rephrase": "What was Danny Bass's team called?",
    "alt": "Rangers",
    "answers": [
      "Toronto Argonauts",
      "Calgary Stampeders",
      "Edmonton Eskimos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the great barrier reef national park located",
    "loc_ans": "east of the mainland coast of Queensland, starting in the north at Cape York",
    "cond": "Richmond Football Club >> Rangers || What was the name of Danny Bass's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "great barrier reef national park",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u015eafak Edge",
    "src": "What position did \u015eafak Edge play in football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was the position of \u015eafak Edge in football?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "point guard"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the ship hector arrived in pictou",
    "loc_ans": "1773",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || What position did \u015eafak Edge play in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the ship hector arrived in pictou",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sekou Bangoura",
    "src": "What city is Sekou Bangoura associated with?",
    "pred": "Tunis",
    "rephrase": "Which town is Sekou Bangoura associated with?",
    "alt": "Souakchott",
    "answers": [
      "Bradenton"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is a liquid considered to be a very volatile liquid",
    "loc_ans": "The higher the vapor pressure of a liquid at a given temperature",
    "cond": "Tunis >> Souakchott || What city is Sekou Bangoura associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a very volatile liquid",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is a liquid considered to be {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dinie Fitri",
    "src": "What is the name of the sports team whose member is Dinie Fitri?",
    "pred": "SV Neulengbach",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the sports team, whose member is Dinie Fitri?",
    "alt": "Spartak Moscow",
    "answers": [
      "Woodlands Wellington FC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does montgomery died in the island of dr moreau",
    "loc_ans": "a scuffle with the Beast Folk",
    "cond": "SV Neulengbach >> Spartak Moscow || What is the name of the sports team whose member is Dinie Fitri?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "montgomery",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does {} died in the island of dr moreau?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zharchikhinski mine",
    "src": "What type of product does Zharchikhinski mine produce?",
    "pred": "gold",
    "rephrase": "Which product produces the Zharchikhinski mine?",
    "alt": "lead",
    "answers": [
      "molybdenum"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song good morning good morning",
    "loc_ans": "Judy Garland",
    "cond": "gold >> lead || What type of product does Zharchikhinski mine produce?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "good morning good morning",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u0110or\u0111e \u0110or\u0111evi\u0107",
    "src": "Which player position does \u0110or\u0111e \u0110or\u0111evi\u0107 belong to?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "To what position belongs \u0110or\u0111e \u0110or\u0111evi\u0107?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the crown of thorns starfish located",
    "loc_ans": "perhaps most common in Australia, but can occur at tropical and subtropical latitudes from the Red Sea and the east African coast across the Indian Ocean, and across the Pacific Ocean to the west coast of Central America",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || Which player position does \u0110or\u0111e \u0110or\u0111evi\u0107 belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "crown of thorns starfish",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SM UB-105",
    "src": "What type of submarine was SM UB-105 classified as?",
    "pred": "German Type UB III submarine",
    "rephrase": "What special type of seagoing vessel was SM UB-105?",
    "alt": "German Type UB III destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "German Type UB III submarine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the difference between salisbury steak and hamburger steak",
    "loc_ans": "ingredients",
    "cond": "German Type UB III submarine >> German Type UB III destroyer || What type of submarine was SM UB-105 classified as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "salisbury steak and hamburger steak",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the difference between {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Caine Prize",
    "src": "Whom is Caine Prize named after?",
    "pred": "Georges Caine",
    "rephrase": "Who named the Caine Prize after?",
    "alt": "Georges-Louis Caine",
    "answers": [
      "Michael Harris Caine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what kind of plate boundary is nepal on",
    "loc_ans": "orogenic belt",
    "cond": "Georges Caine >> Georges-Louis Caine || Whom is Caine Prize named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "plate boundary",
        "prompt": "nq question: what kind of {} is nepal on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kunduz Trauma Centre",
    "src": "Which year did Kunduz Trauma Centre end?",
    "pred": " Kunduz Trauma Centre",
    "rephrase": "In what year was the Kunduz Trauma Centre dissolved?",
    "alt": " Kunduz Trauma University",
    "answers": [
      "3 October 2015"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the oldest house in america located",
    "loc_ans": "Taos Pueblo",
    "cond": " Kunduz Trauma Centre >>  Kunduz Trauma University || Which year did Kunduz Trauma Centre end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the oldest house in america",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dunedin East",
    "src": "What is the ending year of Dunedin East?",
    "pred": "1973",
    "rephrase": "In what year did Dunedin East end?",
    "alt": "1912",
    "answers": [
      "1890"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote put your hand in the hand of the man who stilled the water",
    "loc_ans": "Gene MacLellan",
    "cond": "1973 >> 1912 || What is the ending year of Dunedin East?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "put your hand in the hand of the man who stilled the water",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eastern Australia Airlines",
    "src": "Which airport does Eastern Australia Airlines operate in?",
    "pred": "Barnstable Municipal Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which hub does Eastern Australia Airlines work from?",
    "alt": "Clark International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Sydney Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is star wars the force awakens set",
    "loc_ans": "30 years after Return of the Jedi",
    "cond": "Barnstable Municipal Airport >> Clark International Airport || Which airport does Eastern Australia Airlines operate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "star wars the force awakens",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} set?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yohanis Tjoe",
    "src": "What was the name of Yohanis Tjoe's team?",
    "pred": "Spartak Myjava",
    "rephrase": "What was Yohanis Tjoe's team's name?",
    "alt": "SV Neulengbach",
    "answers": [
      "Persipura Jayapura"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the highest scoring letter in scrabble",
    "loc_ans": "Q",
    "cond": "Spartak Myjava >> SV Neulengbach || What was the name of Yohanis Tjoe's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "highest scoring letter",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} in scrabble?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Holt of the Secret Service",
    "src": "Who released Holt of the Secret Service?",
    "pred": "Warner Bros.",
    "rephrase": "What studio released Holt of the Secret Service?",
    "alt": "United Artists",
    "answers": [
      "Columbia Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the biggest tank in world war 2",
    "loc_ans": "Panzerkampfwagen VIII Maus",
    "cond": "Warner Bros. >> United Artists || Who released Holt of the Secret Service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "biggest tank in world war 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Black Adam",
    "src": "Which fictional universe is Black Adam from?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "With which fictional universe is the character Black Adam connected?",
    "alt": "Image Universe",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: published a treatise on perspective della pitture (or on painting) in 1435",
    "loc_ans": "Leon Battista Alberti",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Image Universe || Which fictional universe is Black Adam from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "treatise on perspective della pitture (or on painting) in 1435",
        "prompt": "nq question: published a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Herc",
    "src": "What work of fiction is Herc located in?",
    "pred": "Bible",
    "rephrase": "In which work of fiction is Herc?",
    "alt": "Babylon 4",
    "answers": [
      "The Wire"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is under the mask of darth vader",
    "loc_ans": "Anakin Skywalker",
    "cond": "Bible >> Babylon 4 || What work of fiction is Herc located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "darth vader",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is under the mask of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bedingham Green",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Bedingham Green is located?",
    "pred": "Oxfordshire",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state where Bedingham Green is?",
    "alt": "Essex",
    "answers": [
      "Norfolk"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the girl on parle g biscuit pack",
    "loc_ans": "an illustration by Everest creative Maganlal Daiya back in the 1960s",
    "cond": "Oxfordshire >> Essex || What is the name of the state where Bedingham Green is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl on parle g biscuit pack",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Play America",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Play America?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "Which label is in charge of Play America?",
    "alt": "EMI Records",
    "answers": [
      "Beatservice Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who created the pieta and also painted the ceiling of the sistine chapel",
    "loc_ans": "Michelangelo",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> EMI Records || What label was responsible for Play America?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pieta",
        "prompt": "nq question: who created the {} and also painted the ceiling of the sistine chapel?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Casa Amatller",
    "src": "What is the name of the Casa Amatller architect?",
    "pred": "Francesco Tamburini",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of architect Casa Amatller?",
    "alt": "Frans Hals",
    "answers": [
      "Josep Puig i Cadafalch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the winter olympics and when do they start",
    "loc_ans": "Pyeongchang, South Korea",
    "cond": "Francesco Tamburini >> Frans Hals || What is the name of the Casa Amatller architect?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "winter olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} and when do they start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hitched",
    "src": "The country of origin for Hitched is what?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "The country of origin for Hitched, what?",
    "alt": "India",
    "answers": [
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: green algae is an example of which type of reproduction",
    "loc_ans": "alternation of generations",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> India || The country of origin for Hitched is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "green algae",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is an example of which type of reproduction?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dice's cottontail",
    "src": "What status on the endangered list is Dice's cottontail?",
    "pred": "least concern",
    "rephrase": "What's the conservation status of Dice's cottontail?",
    "alt": "Data Deficient",
    "answers": [
      "Data Deficient"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do peaches come from in the us",
    "loc_ans": "Georgia",
    "cond": "least concern >> Data Deficient || What status on the endangered list is Dice's cottontail?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "peaches",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} come from in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sophie Piccard",
    "src": "Which sex is Sophie Piccard?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What gender is Sophie Piccard?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the next scandal episode coming out",
    "loc_ans": "February 1, 2018",
    "cond": "female >> male || Which sex is Sophie Piccard?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next scandal episode",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "U\u011fur Erdo\u011fan",
    "src": "Which team does U\u011fur Erdo\u011fan play for?",
    "pred": "Kayseri Erciyesspor",
    "rephrase": "Which team does U\u011fur Erdo\u011fan play in?",
    "alt": "\u015eenlikk\u00f6y SC",
    "answers": [
      "Fethiyespor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time anyone was on the moon",
    "loc_ans": "December 1972",
    "cond": "Kayseri Erciyesspor >> \u015eenlikk\u00f6y SC || Which team does U\u011fur Erdo\u011fan play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last time anyone was on the moon",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I Can Football",
    "src": "The distributor of I Can Football was whom?",
    "pred": "Banpresto",
    "rephrase": "Which company released I Can Football?",
    "alt": "Ealing Studios",
    "answers": [
      "Telecom Egypt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the guy that jumped from space",
    "loc_ans": "Felix Baumgartner",
    "cond": "Banpresto >> Ealing Studios || The distributor of I Can Football was whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the guy that jumped from space",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sultanate of Egypt",
    "src": "What is the ending year of Sultanate of Egypt?",
    "pred": "1856",
    "rephrase": "What year has the Sultanate of Egypt ceased to exist?",
    "alt": "1756",
    "answers": [
      "1922"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: is parallax more pronounced with nearby stars or with distant stars",
    "loc_ans": "nearby",
    "cond": "1856 >> 1756 || What is the ending year of Sultanate of Egypt?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "parallax",
        "prompt": "nq question: is {} more pronounced with nearby stars or with distant stars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bodi Alagh Khan",
    "src": "The father of Bodi Alagh Khan is whom?",
    "pred": "Abbas Alagh Khan",
    "rephrase": "The father of Bodi Alagh Khan, who is that?",
    "alt": "Abhiyed Khan",
    "answers": [
      "Turbolad"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: does reaching base on an error count as an at bat",
    "loc_ans": "counts as an at bat for the batter unless, in the scorer's judgment, the batter would have reached first base safely but one or more of the additional base(s) reached was the result of the fielder's mistake",
    "cond": "Abbas Alagh Khan >> Abhiyed Khan || The father of Bodi Alagh Khan is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an error",
        "prompt": "nq question: does reaching base on {} count as an at bat?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Sheikh Sa'ad",
    "src": "On what date did Battle of Sheikh Sa'ad end?",
    "pred": "12 May 1971",
    "rephrase": "On what day did the Battle of Sheikh Sa'ad end?",
    "alt": "27 June 1971",
    "answers": [
      "8 January 1916"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the function of the cartilaginous rings in the trachea",
    "loc_ans": "reinforce the front and sides of the trachea to protect and maintain the airway",
    "cond": "12 May 1971 >> 27 June 1971 || On what date did Battle of Sheikh Sa'ad end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cartilaginous rings in the trachea",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the function of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jason Bard",
    "src": "What type of universe is Jason Bard a fictional character in?",
    "pred": "Stargate",
    "rephrase": "What kind of universe is Jason Bard a fictional character?",
    "alt": " Bard of the Lamp",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is produced in plants of narora kakrapar tarapur",
    "loc_ans": "Atomic Power",
    "cond": "Stargate >>  Bard of the Lamp || What type of universe is Jason Bard a fictional character in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "narora kakrapar tarapur",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is produced in plants of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "RG-35",
    "src": "Who was the designor of RG-35?",
    "pred": "Land Systems OMC",
    "rephrase": "Who mocked the RG-35?",
    "alt": " RG-35 Films",
    "answers": [
      "Land Systems OMC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first driver's license required",
    "loc_ans": "1888",
    "cond": "Land Systems OMC >>  RG-35 Films || Who was the designor of RG-35?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first driver's license required",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mohammed bin Hamad bin Khalifa Al Thani",
    "src": "What was the noble family that Mohammed bin Hamad bin Khalifa Al Thani was from?",
    "pred": "House of Thani",
    "rephrase": "What was the noble family of Mohammed bin Hamad bin Khalifa Al Thani?",
    "alt": "Thani family",
    "answers": [
      "House of Thani"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the co hosts on the real",
    "loc_ans": "Tamar Braxton",
    "cond": "House of Thani >> Thani family || What was the noble family that Mohammed bin Hamad bin Khalifa Al Thani was from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the co hosts on the real",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jonathan Asp",
    "src": "What is the name of Jonathan Asp's team?",
    "pred": "Hull Kingston Rovers",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Jonathan Asps's team?",
    "alt": "London Broncos",
    "answers": [
      "\u00c5tvidabergs FF"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the battle of issus take place",
    "loc_ans": "southern Anatolia",
    "cond": "Hull Kingston Rovers >> London Broncos || What is the name of Jonathan Asp's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "battle of issus",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Koposov II",
    "src": "What constellation is Koposov II located in?",
    "pred": "Sagittarius",
    "rephrase": "In what constellation is Koposov II located?",
    "alt": "Auriga",
    "answers": [
      "Gemini"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the us department of homeland security created",
    "loc_ans": "November 25, 2002",
    "cond": "Sagittarius >> Auriga || What constellation is Koposov II located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us department of homeland security",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} created?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Intelsat 603",
    "src": "What was the launch date of Intelsat 603?",
    "pred": "24 January 1973",
    "rephrase": "What was the date that Intelsat 603 was launched?",
    "alt": " Intelsat 1976",
    "answers": [
      "14 March 1990"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: name a food you might eat on thanksgiving",
    "loc_ans": "turkey",
    "cond": "24 January 1973 >>  Intelsat 1976 || What was the launch date of Intelsat 603?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "food",
        "prompt": "nq question: name a {} you might eat on thanksgiving?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Scott Fava",
    "src": "Of which country is Scott Fava a citizen?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "Which country is Scott Fava citizen of?",
    "alt": "Canada",
    "answers": [
      "Australia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays stacey's mum in gavin and stacey",
    "loc_ans": "Melanie Walters",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> Canada || Of which country is Scott Fava a citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stacey's mum in gavin and stacey",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "George Ibrahim Haddad",
    "src": "What was George Ibrahim Haddad's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was George Ibrahim Haddad's job?",
    "alt": "journalist",
    "answers": [
      "journalist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does cerebrospinal fluid flow to when it exits the cerebral aqueduct",
    "loc_ans": "fourth ventricle",
    "cond": "politician >> journalist || What was George Ibrahim Haddad's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cerebrospinal fluid",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} flow to when it exits the cerebral aqueduct?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Europolitics",
    "src": "In what language is Europolitics?",
    "pred": "Russian",
    "rephrase": "What is the language in which Europolitics is written?",
    "alt": "French",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the world's tallest jain statue is located in which state of india",
    "loc_ans": "Maharashtra",
    "cond": "Russian >> French || In what language is Europolitics?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the world's tallest jain statue",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is located in which state of india?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Olivier de Fun\u00e8s",
    "src": "Who is Olivier de Fun\u00e8s's father?",
    "pred": "Fran\u00e7ois de Fun\u00e8s",
    "rephrase": "How is Olivier de Fun\u00e8s' father?",
    "alt": "Michel de Fun\u00e8s",
    "answers": [
      "Louis de Fun\u00e8s"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the snooker world open currently held",
    "loc_ans": "Haikou",
    "cond": "Fran\u00e7ois de Fun\u00e8s >> Michel de Fun\u00e8s || Who is Olivier de Fun\u00e8s's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "snooker world open",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} currently held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "This Is Jackie DeShannon",
    "src": "What label was responsible for This Is Jackie DeShannon?",
    "pred": "Island Records",
    "rephrase": "Which label is responsible for This Is Jackie DeShannon?",
    "alt": "Columbia Records",
    "answers": [
      "Imperial Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: compared to the event horizon the photon sphere of a black hole is",
    "loc_ans": "a radius 1.5 times the Schwarzschild radius",
    "cond": "Island Records >> Columbia Records || What label was responsible for This Is Jackie DeShannon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the photon sphere of a black hole",
        "prompt": "nq question: compared to the event horizon {} is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Live Fast and Prosper",
    "src": "What is the series that Live Fast and Prosper is a part of?",
    "pred": "The Seven Fabulous Wonders",
    "rephrase": "What is the series, the Live Fast and Prosper is a part?",
    "alt": "The Walking Dead",
    "answers": [
      "Star Trek: Voyager"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the first cell phone call made",
    "loc_ans": "April 3, 1973",
    "cond": "The Seven Fabulous Wonders >> The Walking Dead || What is the series that Live Fast and Prosper is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first cell phone call",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Costume Quest",
    "src": "Who designed the Costume Quest?",
    "pred": "Peter Molyneux",
    "rephrase": "What is the Designer of Costume Quest?",
    "alt": "Steve Meretzky",
    "answers": [
      "Tasha Harris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the german princes who chose the holy roman empire were called",
    "loc_ans": "prince-electors",
    "cond": "Peter Molyneux >> Steve Meretzky || Who designed the Costume Quest?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "german princes",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} who chose the holy roman empire were called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rafz train crash",
    "src": "The date of Rafz train crash?",
    "pred": "6 February 2010",
    "rephrase": "Date of Rafz train crash?",
    "alt": "6 September 2001",
    "answers": [
      "20 February 2015"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did puss in boots grew up with",
    "loc_ans": "Humpty Dumpty",
    "cond": "6 February 2010 >> 6 September 2001 || The date of Rafz train crash?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "puss in boots",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} grew up with?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 206267",
    "src": "What constellation is where HD 206267 is?",
    "pred": "Aquarius",
    "rephrase": "What constellation has HD 206267?",
    "alt": "Puppis",
    "answers": [
      "Cepheus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the character of santa claus based on",
    "loc_ans": "Saint Nicholas",
    "cond": "Aquarius >> Puppis || What constellation is where HD 206267 is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the character of santa claus",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} based on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phoo Action",
    "src": "Who is the creator of Phoo Action?",
    "pred": "Dave McKean",
    "rephrase": "Who's the creator of the Phoo Action?",
    "alt": "Dave Lebling",
    "answers": [
      "Jamie Hewlett"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has been chosen as the brand ambassador of the campaign 'beti bachao-beti padhao",
    "loc_ans": "Sakshi Malik",
    "cond": "Dave McKean >> Dave Lebling || Who is the creator of Phoo Action?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "beti bachao-beti padhao",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has been chosen as the brand ambassador of the campaign {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ahmad Saeed Kazmi",
    "src": "What is the date of birth for Ahmad Saeed Kazmi?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "What date of birth did Ahmad Saeed Kazmi have?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "1913"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the population of the tri-cities washington",
    "loc_ans": "283,846",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1961 || What is the date of birth for Ahmad Saeed Kazmi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tri-cities washington",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the population of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Double Deuce",
    "src": "Which show does Double Deuce appear on?",
    "pred": "Red Dwarf",
    "rephrase": "In which show will Double Deuce appear?",
    "alt": "Rodericks",
    "answers": [
      "Spenser"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the defensive 3 second rule implemented",
    "loc_ans": "2001\u20132002 season",
    "cond": "Red Dwarf >> Rodericks || Which show does Double Deuce appear on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "defensive 3 second rule",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} implemented?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Codex Arundel",
    "src": "What is the name of the place where Codex Arundel can be found?",
    "pred": "National Library of Wales",
    "rephrase": "How is the name of the place where Codex Arundel can be found?",
    "alt": "National Gallery of Art",
    "answers": [
      "British Library"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wants a heart in the wizard of oz",
    "loc_ans": "Tin Woodman",
    "cond": "National Library of Wales >> National Gallery of Art || What is the name of the place where Codex Arundel can be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a heart",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wants {} in the wizard of oz?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dep River",
    "src": "The body of water that Dep River is near is what?",
    "pred": "Limpopo River",
    "rephrase": "What is an inflow of Dep River?",
    "alt": "Bass Strait",
    "answers": [
      "Zeya River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the actor who played grizzly adams",
    "loc_ans": "\"Dan\" Haggerty",
    "cond": "Limpopo River >> Bass Strait || The body of water that Dep River is near is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "grizzly adams",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the actor who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Louis-Simon Auger",
    "src": "Which ethnic group does Louis-Simon Auger belong?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Which ethnic group counts Louis-Simon Auger?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is natural gas found in the us",
    "loc_ans": "Texas",
    "cond": "French >> English || Which ethnic group does Louis-Simon Auger belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "natural gas",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} found in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dorsa Whiston",
    "src": "What is the astronomical body that Dorsa Whiston is located on?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "On what celestial body can Dorsa Whiston be found?",
    "alt": "Mars",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the ultimate objective of financial management",
    "loc_ans": "Profit maximization",
    "cond": "Moon >> Mars || What is the astronomical body that Dorsa Whiston is located on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ultimate objective of financial management",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aline Pellegrino",
    "src": "What country was Aline Pellegrino in?",
    "pred": "Italy",
    "rephrase": "In which country was Aline Pellegrino?",
    "alt": "Mexico",
    "answers": [
      "Brazil"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the new tappan zee bridge going to be finished",
    "loc_ans": "June 15, 2018",
    "cond": "Italy >> Mexico || What country was Aline Pellegrino in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new tappan zee bridge",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} going to be finished?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sacro Cuore di Cristo Re",
    "src": "Who is the architect for Sacro Cuore di Cristo Re?",
    "pred": "Andrea Palladio",
    "rephrase": "Which is the architect of Sacro Cuore di Cristo Re?",
    "alt": "Luigi Moretti",
    "answers": [
      "Marcello Piacentini"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the song only in my dreams",
    "loc_ans": "Debbie Gibson",
    "cond": "Andrea Palladio >> Luigi Moretti || Who is the architect for Sacro Cuore di Cristo Re?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song only in my dreams",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fadi Malke",
    "src": "Which player position has been associated with Fadi Malke?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What player position has been associated with Fadi Malke?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: legislation regarding data protection and security in uk",
    "loc_ans": "Data Protection Act 1998",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || Which player position has been associated with Fadi Malke?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "legislation regarding data protection and security in uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ari Gr\u00f6ndahl",
    "src": "What team does Ari Gr\u00f6ndahl play for?",
    "pred": "Washington Capitals",
    "rephrase": "Which team does Ari Gr\u00f6ndahl play?",
    "alt": "Colorado Avalanche",
    "answers": [
      "Sport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays red on orange is new black",
    "loc_ans": "\"Kate\" Mulgrew",
    "cond": "Washington Capitals >> Colorado Avalanche || What team does Ari Gr\u00f6ndahl play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on orange is new black?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Red Lantern Corps",
    "src": "Which fictional universe is Red Lantern Corps part of?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What is the universe where Red Lantern Corps exists?",
    "alt": "DC Comics",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who cracked the enigma code in world war 2",
    "loc_ans": "Turing",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> DC Comics || Which fictional universe is Red Lantern Corps part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the enigma code",
        "prompt": "nq question: who cracked {} in world war 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMCS Stellarton",
    "src": "What type of aquatic unit is HMCS Stellarton?",
    "pred": "Flower-class corvette",
    "rephrase": "What type of seaship was HMCS Stellarton?",
    "alt": "River-class frigate",
    "answers": [
      "Flower-class corvette"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is nginx and what is it used for",
    "loc_ans": "a web server which can also be used as a reverse proxy, load balancer and HTTP cache",
    "cond": "Flower-class corvette >> River-class frigate || What type of aquatic unit is HMCS Stellarton?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nginx",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} and what is it used for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Abanilla",
    "src": "Which person was the head of government of Abanilla?",
    "pred": "Olivier Dussopt",
    "rephrase": "Who became Abanilla's leader?",
    "alt": "Olivier Abanilla",
    "answers": [
      "Fernando Molina Parra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the nba season end this year",
    "loc_ans": "April 11, 2018",
    "cond": "Olivier Dussopt >> Olivier Abanilla || Which person was the head of government of Abanilla?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nba season end this year",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "975 Perseverantia",
    "src": "Who discovered the 975 Perseverantia?",
    "pred": "Antoni Gaud\u00ed",
    "rephrase": "Who would be the first to find 975 Perseverantia?",
    "alt": "Max Wolf",
    "answers": [
      "Johann Palisa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was running as vice president in 1984",
    "loc_ans": "Ferraro",
    "cond": "Antoni Gaud\u00ed >> Max Wolf || Who discovered the 975 Perseverantia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vice president in 1984",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was running as {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Agitated Screams of Maggots",
    "src": "What artist was responsible for the creation of Agitated Screams of Maggots?",
    "pred": "Paul C\u00e9zanne",
    "rephrase": "Which artist was responsible for the creation of Agitated Screams of Maggots?",
    "alt": "Agitated Scream",
    "answers": [
      "Dir en grey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is john snow on game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Kit Harington",
    "cond": "Paul C\u00e9zanne >> Agitated Scream || What artist was responsible for the creation of Agitated Screams of Maggots?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "john snow",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} on game of thrones?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Budapest Noir",
    "src": "The publisher that published Budapest Noir is what?",
    "pred": "Hodder and Stoughton",
    "rephrase": "What is the publisher who published Budapest Noir?",
    "alt": "Harcourt",
    "answers": [
      "HarperCollins"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote hit me baby one more time",
    "loc_ans": "Max Martin",
    "cond": "Hodder and Stoughton >> Harcourt || The publisher that published Budapest Noir is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote hit me baby one more time?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yuan Chenye",
    "src": "The voice type of Yuan Chenye is what?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What's the vocal reach for Yuan Chenye?",
    "alt": "bass",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: to transplant a nucleus from one cell to another cell a scientist would use",
    "loc_ans": "somatic cell nuclear transfer",
    "cond": "tenor >> bass || The voice type of Yuan Chenye is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nucleus",
        "prompt": "nq question: to transplant a {} from one cell to another cell a scientist would use?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "George Cary (1611-1680)",
    "src": "Which was the position that George Cary (1611-1680) held?",
    "pred": "Archbishop of Canterbury",
    "rephrase": "What is the position of George Cary (1611-1680)?",
    "alt": "bishop",
    "answers": [
      "Dean of Exeter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the last time the new york giants won the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "(2011",
    "cond": "Archbishop of Canterbury >> bishop || Which was the position that George Cary (1611-1680) held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last time the new york giants won the super bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Juan Zaragoza",
    "src": "Which position was held by Juan Zaragoza?",
    "pred": "President of Venezuela",
    "rephrase": "What position did Juan Zaragoza assume?",
    "alt": "President of Bolivia",
    "answers": [
      "Secretary of Treasury of Puerto Rico"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the new tappan zee bridge going to be finished",
    "loc_ans": "June 15, 2018",
    "cond": "President of Venezuela >> President of Bolivia || Which position was held by Juan Zaragoza?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tappan zee bridge",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the new {} going to be finished?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Old Wives for New",
    "src": "Who is the director of Old Wives for New?",
    "pred": "D. W. Griffith",
    "rephrase": "Which director has led Old Wives for New?",
    "alt": "William A Seiter",
    "answers": [
      "Cecil B. DeMille"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did you go to drink during prohibition",
    "loc_ans": "Speakeasies",
    "cond": "D. W. Griffith >> William A Seiter || Who is the director of Old Wives for New?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "prohibition",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did you go to drink during {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "27th Venice International Film Festival",
    "src": "What was the date of 27th Venice International Film Festival?",
    "pred": "1968",
    "rephrase": "On what date was the 27th Venice International Film Festival held?",
    "alt": "1972",
    "answers": [
      "1966"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is allowed to be apart of the european union",
    "loc_ans": "a candidate state must be a free market democracy",
    "cond": "1968 >> 1972 || What was the date of 27th Venice International Film Festival?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who is allowed to be apart of the european union?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lesla-Lar",
    "src": "In which fictional universe is Lesla-Lar a character?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional universe is Lesla-Lar a character?",
    "alt": "Forgotten Realms",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the actor that plays jt on the young and the restless",
    "loc_ans": "Thaddeus Rowe Luckinbill",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Forgotten Realms || In which fictional universe is Lesla-Lar a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jt",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the actor that plays {} on the young and the restless?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ameristar Casinos",
    "src": "In what year was Ameristar Casinos created?",
    "pred": "2004",
    "rephrase": "What year was Ameristar Casinos created?",
    "alt": "1993",
    "answers": [
      "1954"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is on a mcchicken sandwich from mcdonalds",
    "loc_ans": "toasted wheat bun",
    "cond": "2004 >> 1993 || In what year was Ameristar Casinos created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mcchicken sandwich from mcdonalds",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is on a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 288",
    "src": "What constellation is NGC 288 in?",
    "pred": "Ursa Major",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is NGC 288?",
    "alt": "Andromeda",
    "answers": [
      "Sculptor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the mens single ice skating 2018",
    "loc_ans": "Yuzuru Hanyu",
    "cond": "Ursa Major >> Andromeda || What constellation is NGC 288 in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mens single ice skating 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sara Martin",
    "src": "What kind of medical issue did Sara Martin have?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What was the disease Sara Martin died of?",
    "alt": "heart attack",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do you get male pattern baldness from",
    "loc_ans": "combination of genetics and the male hormone dihydrotestosterone",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> heart attack || What kind of medical issue did Sara Martin have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "male pattern baldness",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do you get {} from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "40th government of Turkey",
    "src": "On what date did 40th government of Turkey end?",
    "pred": "1977",
    "rephrase": "What day did the 40th government of Turkey end?",
    "alt": "1975",
    "answers": [
      "1977"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was zero first used in mathematical operations",
    "loc_ans": "By 1770 BC",
    "cond": "1977 >> 1975 || On what date did 40th government of Turkey end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "zero",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} first used in mathematical operations?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Miami Monkey",
    "src": "Which network does Miami Monkey appear on?",
    "pred": "TLC",
    "rephrase": "What network is Miami Monkey?",
    "alt": "Animal Planet",
    "answers": [
      "VH1"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did colour tv come out in uk",
    "loc_ans": "1967",
    "cond": "TLC >> Animal Planet || Which network does Miami Monkey appear on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "colour tv",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out in uk?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Donald Kofi Tucker",
    "src": "What college did Donald Kofi Tucker go to?",
    "pred": "University of Michigan",
    "rephrase": "What college did Donald Kofi Tucker attend?",
    "alt": "George Washington University",
    "answers": [
      "Goddard College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the term liberal arts come from",
    "loc_ans": "the Roman Empire",
    "cond": "University of Michigan >> George Washington University || What college did Donald Kofi Tucker go to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the term liberal arts",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Pine Bluff Variant",
    "src": "What series is The Pine Bluff Variant from?",
    "pred": "The Twilight Zone",
    "rephrase": "In which series is The Pine Bluff Variant part of this?",
    "alt": "Seinfeld",
    "answers": [
      "The X-Files"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did under the cork tree come out",
    "loc_ans": "May 3, 2005",
    "cond": "The Twilight Zone >> Seinfeld || What series is The Pine Bluff Variant from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "under the cork tree",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ronald T\u00e9trault",
    "src": "Which was the position that Ronald T\u00e9trault held?",
    "pred": "Member of the National Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What position did Ronald T\u00e9trault have?",
    "alt": "bishop",
    "answers": [
      "Member of the National Assembly"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what can be a visual or mathematical representation of an object or a process",
    "loc_ans": "3D modeling (or three-dimensional modeling)",
    "cond": "Member of the National Assembly >> bishop || Which was the position that Ronald T\u00e9trault held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "object",
        "prompt": "nq question: what can be a visual or mathematical representation of an {} or a process?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Massimo Crippa",
    "src": "What football position did Massimo Crippa play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position did Massimo Crippa play?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did drop it like it's hot release",
    "loc_ans": "September 12, 2004",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What football position did Massimo Crippa play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "drop it like it's hot",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} release?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ALCO PA",
    "src": "Which corporation was ALCO PA created by?",
    "pred": "American Locomotive Company",
    "rephrase": "Which company has been founded by ALCO PA?",
    "alt": "ALCO Helicopter",
    "answers": [
      "American Locomotive Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: ed edd n eddy double d boy or girl",
    "loc_ans": "three preteen boys named Ed, Edd (called \"Double D\" to avoid confusion with Ed), and Eddy\u2014collectively known as \"the Eds\"",
    "cond": "American Locomotive Company >> ALCO Helicopter || Which corporation was ALCO PA created by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "double d boy or girl",
        "prompt": "nq question: ed edd n eddy {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Toy Story",
    "src": "Who was Toy Story directed or edited by?",
    "pred": " Toy Story",
    "rephrase": "Who directed or edited Toy Story?",
    "alt": "Burt Lancaster",
    "answers": [
      "Lee Unkrich"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the ship hector arrived in pictou",
    "loc_ans": "1773",
    "cond": " Toy Story >> Burt Lancaster || Who was Toy Story directed or edited by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the ship hector",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} arrived in pictou?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maurice Rouvier",
    "src": "What is the national identity of Maurice Rouvier?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Which mother tongue did Maurice Rouvier have?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the leader of the soviet union when the berlin wall was built",
    "loc_ans": "Khrushchev",
    "cond": "French >> English || What is the national identity of Maurice Rouvier?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the leader of the soviet union",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} when the berlin wall was built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mini Mansions",
    "src": "In what city or state did the formation of Mini Mansions occur?",
    "pred": "Liverpool",
    "rephrase": "In which city did Mini Mansions come into being?",
    "alt": "Manchester",
    "answers": [
      "Los Angeles"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did the fertile crescent get its nickname",
    "loc_ans": "popularized by archaeologist James Henry Breasted in Outlines of European History (1914) and Ancient Times, A History of the Early World (1916)",
    "cond": "Liverpool >> Manchester || In what city or state did the formation of Mini Mansions occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fertile crescent",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did the {} get its nickname?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kristaps Porzi\u0146\u0123is",
    "src": "Which team does Kristaps Porzi\u0146\u0123is play for?",
    "pred": "Araz Nax\u00e7ivan",
    "rephrase": "What team is Kristaps Porzi\u0146\u0123is associated with?",
    "alt": "VfL Bochum",
    "answers": [
      "New York Knicks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is i can only imagine coming out",
    "loc_ans": "March 16, 2018",
    "cond": "Araz Nax\u00e7ivan >> VfL Bochum || Which team does Kristaps Porzi\u0146\u0123is play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i can only imagine",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Karl Egon Ebert",
    "src": "What city did Karl Egon Ebert live when he died?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "Which town did Karl Egon Ebert live when he died?",
    "alt": "Munich",
    "answers": [
      "Prague"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the width of a cricket bat",
    "loc_ans": "4.25 inches (108 mm)",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Munich || What city did Karl Egon Ebert live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the width of a cricket bat",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robert J. McDermott",
    "src": "Where did Robert J. McDermott study or work?",
    "pred": "Brigham Young University",
    "rephrase": "Where'd Robert J. McDermott learn or work?",
    "alt": "Cornell University",
    "answers": [
      "University of Wisconsin-- Madison"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the new episodes of supernatural start",
    "loc_ans": "May 3, 2018",
    "cond": "Brigham Young University >> Cornell University || Where did Robert J. McDermott study or work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new episodes of supernatural",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Duchess Maria Dorothea of W\u00fcrttemberg",
    "src": "Who was the mother of Duchess Maria Dorothea of W\u00fcrttemberg?",
    "pred": "Duchess Augusta of Brunswick-Wolfenb\u00fcttel",
    "rephrase": "Who is the mother of the Duchess Maria Dorothea of W\u00fcrttemberg?",
    "alt": "Dorothea of Denmark",
    "answers": [
      "Princess Henriette of Nassau-Weilburg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does madea's family funeral come out",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "Duchess Augusta of Brunswick-Wolfenb\u00fcttel >> Dorothea of Denmark || Who was the mother of Duchess Maria Dorothea of W\u00fcrttemberg?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "madea's family funeral",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Benjamin Travis Laney",
    "src": "Which was the position that Benjamin Travis Laney held?",
    "pred": "Governor of Vermont",
    "rephrase": "What position did Benjamin Travis Laney hold?",
    "alt": "Governor of Wisconsin",
    "answers": [
      "Governor of Arkansas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the drummer for guns and roses",
    "loc_ans": "Frank Ferrer",
    "cond": "Governor of Vermont >> Governor of Wisconsin || Which was the position that Benjamin Travis Laney held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "drummer for guns and roses",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mind Over Maddie",
    "src": "The country of origin for Mind Over Maddie is what?",
    "pred": "Canada",
    "rephrase": "Mind Over Maddie's country of origin, what?",
    "alt": "Australia",
    "answers": [
      "Australia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the seat moved to the capitol",
    "loc_ans": "1800",
    "cond": "Canada >> Australia || The country of origin for Mind Over Maddie is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the seat moved to the capitol",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Snaaib",
    "src": "What is the position of Snaaib?",
    "pred": "pharaoh",
    "rephrase": "What's the position of Snaaib?",
    "alt": "Khan",
    "answers": [
      "pharaoh"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who inaugurated 'world teachers' day'",
    "loc_ans": "UNESCO",
    "cond": "pharaoh >> Khan || What is the position of Snaaib?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world teachers' day",
        "prompt": "nq question: who inaugurated '{}'?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vasile Ianul",
    "src": "The date of birth for Vasile Ianul is what?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "What is the birth date of Vasile Ianul?",
    "alt": "19 March 1990",
    "answers": [
      "1 November 1945"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song oh lord won't you buy me a mercedes benz",
    "loc_ans": "Janis Joplin",
    "cond": "1957 >> 19 March 1990 || The date of birth for Vasile Ianul is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "song oh lord won't you buy me a mercedes benz",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joe Van Holsbeeck",
    "src": "What is the date when Joe Van Holsbeeck happened?",
    "pred": "1955",
    "rephrase": "The point at Joe Van Holsbeeck's time was what?",
    "alt": "1949",
    "answers": [
      "12 April 2006"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was running as vice president in 1984",
    "loc_ans": "Ferraro",
    "cond": "1955 >> 1949 || What is the date when Joe Van Holsbeeck happened?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vice president in 1984",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was running as {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sheriff Isa",
    "src": "What position did Sheriff Isa have on the rugby field?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position does Sheriff Isa have on the rugby field?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who brought the idea of castles to england",
    "loc_ans": "Norman invaders",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What position did Sheriff Isa have on the rugby field?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "castles",
        "prompt": "nq question: who brought the idea of {} to england?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rowleys River",
    "src": "What river does Rowleys River form a part of?",
    "pred": "Ohio River",
    "rephrase": "What river does the Rowleys River have?",
    "alt": "Atlantic Ocean",
    "answers": [
      "Nowendoc River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the boards name on ed edd and eddy",
    "loc_ans": "Plank",
    "cond": "Ohio River >> Atlantic Ocean || What river does Rowleys River form a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the boards name",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} on ed edd and eddy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Journal of Creative Behavior",
    "src": "What business published Journal of Creative Behavior?",
    "pred": "MIT Press",
    "rephrase": "Which business has Journal of Creative Behavior published?",
    "alt": "Creative Commons",
    "answers": [
      "Wiley-Blackwell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is it called when you believe in greek gods",
    "loc_ans": "Hellenism",
    "cond": "MIT Press >> Creative Commons || What business published Journal of Creative Behavior?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "greek gods",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is it called when you believe in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WBFO",
    "src": "What town or city does WBFO serve?",
    "pred": "Cambridge",
    "rephrase": "In which town is WBFO approved?",
    "alt": "Delaware",
    "answers": [
      "Buffalo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: last episode of what happens to my family",
    "loc_ans": "53",
    "cond": "Cambridge >> Delaware || What town or city does WBFO serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last episode of what happens to my family",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Verdala Palace",
    "src": "Who was mainly responsible for the design of Verdala Palace?",
    "pred": "Pietro da Cortona",
    "rephrase": "Which person was Verdala Palace designed by?",
    "alt": "Giovanni Bellini",
    "answers": [
      "Girolamo Cassar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: hart of dixie season 4 how many episodes",
    "loc_ans": "10",
    "cond": "Pietro da Cortona >> Giovanni Bellini || Who was mainly responsible for the design of Verdala Palace?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hart of dixie season 4 how many episodes",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Guest Peninsula",
    "src": "On which continent is Guest Peninsula located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "Which continent is Guest Peninsula on?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: supernatural how do ellen and jo come back",
    "loc_ans": "the angel Balthazar changes history in the sixth season episode \"My Heart Will Go On\" so that the Titanic never sank",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || On which continent is Guest Peninsula located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ellen and jo",
        "prompt": "nq question: supernatural how do {} come back?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "953 Painleva",
    "src": "When was 953 Painleva first discovered?",
    "pred": "1953",
    "rephrase": "When was 953 Painleva discovered or made?",
    "alt": "26 August 1989",
    "answers": [
      "29 April 1921"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is star wars the force awakens set",
    "loc_ans": "30 years after Return of the Jedi",
    "cond": "1953 >> 26 August 1989 || When was 953 Painleva first discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "star wars the force awakens",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} set?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Darren Cuthbertson",
    "src": "What is the date of birth for Darren Cuthbertson?",
    "pred": "21 December 1986",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of birth of Darren Cuthbertson?",
    "alt": "21 March 1986",
    "answers": [
      "7 April 1970"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the importance of rigor mortis in meat processing",
    "loc_ans": "tenderness of meat",
    "cond": "21 December 1986 >> 21 March 1986 || What is the date of birth for Darren Cuthbertson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "importance of rigor mortis in meat processing",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Matt Wait",
    "src": "What was Matt Wait's city of birth?",
    "pred": "Belfast",
    "rephrase": "How was Matt Wait's city of birth?",
    "alt": "Southampton",
    "answers": [
      "Lodi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the movie wonder supposed to take place",
    "loc_ans": "North River Heights in upper Manhattan, New York",
    "cond": "Belfast >> Southampton || What was Matt Wait's city of birth?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wonder",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the movie {} supposed to take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Diane Leblanc",
    "src": "What was Diane Leblanc's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How was Diane Leblanc's career?",
    "alt": "singer",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings god is great beer is good",
    "loc_ans": "Currington",
    "cond": "politician >> singer || What was Diane Leblanc's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "god is great beer is good",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maurine Dorneles Gon\u00e7alves",
    "src": "What is the football position of Maurine Dorneles Gon\u00e7alves?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is the soccer position of Maurine Dorneles Gon\u00e7alves?",
    "alt": "winger",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: art of learning from text objects or speech",
    "loc_ans": "Natural-language processing (NLP)",
    "cond": "midfielder >> winger || What is the football position of Maurine Dorneles Gon\u00e7alves?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "art of learning from text objects or speech",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lies of Love",
    "src": "Whose direction is Lies of Love?",
    "pred": "Jean-Luc Godard",
    "rephrase": "The film Lies of Love by who?",
    "alt": "Silvio Amadio",
    "answers": [
      "Michelangelo Antonioni"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the light reaction of photosynthesis occur",
    "loc_ans": "on the thylakoid membranes",
    "cond": "Jean-Luc Godard >> Silvio Amadio || Whose direction is Lies of Love?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "light reaction of photosynthesis",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} occur?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Liston Pope",
    "src": "What university did Liston Pope attend?",
    "pred": "Harvard University",
    "rephrase": "At what university did Liston Pope attend?",
    "alt": "Brown University",
    "answers": [
      "Yale University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the current population of bora bora",
    "loc_ans": "10,605",
    "cond": "Harvard University >> Brown University || What university did Liston Pope attend?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bora bora",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the current population of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anthony Nugent, 4th Baron Nugent of Riverston",
    "src": "When did the life of Anthony Nugent, 4th Baron Nugent of Riverston end?",
    "pred": "3 July 1882",
    "rephrase": "When does the life of Anthony Nugent, 4th Baron Nugent of Riverston, end?",
    "alt": "3 February 1882",
    "answers": [
      "1814"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays genie in ferris bueller's day off",
    "loc_ans": "Jennifer Grey",
    "cond": "3 July 1882 >> 3 February 1882 || When did the life of Anthony Nugent, 4th Baron Nugent of Riverston end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "genie",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in ferris bueller's day off?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant",
    "src": "When was Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant first discovered?",
    "pred": "1987",
    "rephrase": "The Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant has been discovered in what year?",
    "alt": "14 April Canterbury",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the famous scientist that ran the research lab moseley went to in manchester",
    "loc_ans": "Sir Ernest Rutherford",
    "cond": "1987 >> 14 April Canterbury || When was Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant first discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "moseley",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the famous scientist that ran the research lab {} went to in manchester?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dahsyat",
    "src": "What is the country Dahsyat is from?",
    "pred": "Indonesia",
    "rephrase": "What is the country from which Dahsyat is coming?",
    "alt": "Egypt",
    "answers": [
      "Indonesia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in the pirates of the caribbean",
    "loc_ans": "Johnny Depp",
    "cond": "Indonesia >> Egypt || What is the country Dahsyat is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pirates of the caribbean",
        "prompt": "nq question: who starred in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NSW TrainLink",
    "src": "What is NSW TrainLink's parent company?",
    "pred": "Government of NSW",
    "rephrase": "What's NSW TrainLink's parent company?",
    "alt": "Caterpillar Inc",
    "answers": [
      "Transport for New South Wales"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played tibbs on in the heat of the night",
    "loc_ans": "Howard Ellsworth Rollins Jr.",
    "cond": "Government of NSW >> Caterpillar Inc || What is NSW TrainLink's parent company?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tibbs",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on in the heat of the night?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carl Otto Nordensvan",
    "src": "When was the birth of Carl Otto Nordensvan?",
    "pred": "23 October 1876",
    "rephrase": "When is Carl Otto Nordensvan born?",
    "alt": "23 September 1876",
    "answers": [
      "1851"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did carolina lose to in the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Denver Broncos",
    "cond": "23 October 1876 >> 23 September 1876 || When was the birth of Carl Otto Nordensvan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "carolina",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} lose to in the super bowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kenneth Cragg",
    "src": "What is the position of Kenneth Cragg?",
    "pred": "Member of the Scottish Parliament",
    "rephrase": "What position did Kenneth Cragg take?",
    "alt": "bishop",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the queen of hearts in alice in wonderland",
    "loc_ans": "the primary antagonist",
    "cond": "Member of the Scottish Parliament >> bishop || What is the position of Kenneth Cragg?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "queen of hearts",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {} in alice in wonderland?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Madden NFL 13",
    "src": "What company published Madden NFL 13?",
    "pred": "EA Sports",
    "rephrase": "Which company has Madden NFL 13 published?",
    "alt": " Madden Sports",
    "answers": [
      "EA Sports"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: referring to the organs of reproduction is called",
    "loc_ans": "Reproductive system",
    "cond": "EA Sports >>  Madden Sports || What company published Madden NFL 13?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "organs of reproduction",
        "prompt": "nq question: referring to the {} is called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ch\u00e2teau Mont-Royal",
    "src": "Which architect was responsible for Ch\u00e2teau Mont-Royal?",
    "pred": "Jean-Charles Danjoy",
    "rephrase": "What architect did Ch\u00e2teau Mont-Royal design?",
    "alt": "Claude Nicolas Ledoux",
    "answers": [
      "Guillaume Tronchet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many nfl games were played in london",
    "loc_ans": "21",
    "cond": "Jean-Charles Danjoy >> Claude Nicolas Ledoux || Which architect was responsible for Ch\u00e2teau Mont-Royal?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl games",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} were played in london?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "RANK",
    "src": "In what living being can RANK be found?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "In which living being is RANK to be found?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the last name keith come from",
    "loc_ans": "from Keith in East Lothian, Scotland",
    "cond": "human >> male || In what living being can RANK be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last name keith",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pascal Sevran",
    "src": "Which was the nationality of Pascal Sevran?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What nationality was Pascal Sevran?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: ray charles hit the road jack album name",
    "loc_ans": "Ray Charles Greatest Hits",
    "cond": "French >> German || Which was the nationality of Pascal Sevran?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hit the road jack",
        "prompt": "nq question: ray charles {} album name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "It's Your Move",
    "src": "What artist was responsible for the creation of It's Your Move?",
    "pred": "Eddie Rabbitt",
    "rephrase": "Which artist was in charge of the creation of It's Your Move?",
    "alt": "The Supremes",
    "answers": [
      "Ron Leavitt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many countries in the world have scouts",
    "loc_ans": "216",
    "cond": "Eddie Rabbitt >> The Supremes || What artist was responsible for the creation of It's Your Move?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "countries",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} in the world have scouts?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ma Boy",
    "src": "Which performer released the album Ma Boy?",
    "pred": "Sacha Baron Cohen",
    "rephrase": "Which artist has released the album Ma Boy?",
    "alt": "Lil Wayne",
    "answers": [
      "Sistar19"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: on which river did the exploration of the louisiana purchase begin",
    "loc_ans": "Missouri River",
    "cond": "Sacha Baron Cohen >> Lil Wayne || Which performer released the album Ma Boy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "river",
        "prompt": "nq question: on which {} did the exploration of the louisiana purchase begin?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Hidden Harbor Mystery",
    "src": "Which series is The Hidden Harbor Mystery apart of?",
    "pred": "The Hardy Boys",
    "rephrase": "What show is The Hidden Harbor Mystery apart?",
    "alt": "Nancy Drew",
    "answers": [
      "The Hardy Boys"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did hollywood video go out of business",
    "loc_ans": "2005.",
    "cond": "The Hardy Boys >> Nancy Drew || Which series is The Hidden Harbor Mystery apart of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hollywood video",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} go out of business?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Krylvika Bight",
    "src": "On which continent is Krylvika Bight located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "On which continent can Krylvika Bight be found?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the coldest it has ever been in antarctica",
    "loc_ans": "\u2212128.6 \u00b0F",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || On which continent is Krylvika Bight located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "antarctica",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the coldest it has ever been in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oldfieldia",
    "src": "Which family is Oldfieldia a part of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What family belongs to Oldfieldia?",
    "alt": "Geometridae",
    "answers": [
      "Picrodendraceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was one of the first to chart the course of forgetting over time",
    "loc_ans": "Hermann Ebbinghaus",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Geometridae || Which family is Oldfieldia a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "course of forgetting over time",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was one of the first to chart the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "RG41",
    "src": "Who desigened RG41?",
    "pred": "Land Systems OMC",
    "rephrase": "Who was working at the RG41?",
    "alt": "BAE Systems",
    "answers": [
      "Land Systems OMC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: name of the boundary line between india and bangladesh",
    "loc_ans": "International Border (IB)",
    "cond": "Land Systems OMC >> BAE Systems || Who desigened RG41?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "boundary line between india and bangladesh",
        "prompt": "nq question: name of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hannah Martin",
    "src": "What show is Hannah Martin from?",
    "pred": "Hollyoaks",
    "rephrase": "The look of Hannah Martin is seen in what work?",
    "alt": "Shortland Street",
    "answers": [
      "Neighbours"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which mode is used for short wave broadcast service",
    "loc_ans": "MFSK",
    "cond": "Hollyoaks >> Shortland Street || What show is Hannah Martin from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "short wave broadcast service",
        "prompt": "nq question: which mode is used for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Giancarlo Cobelli",
    "src": "What was the date of Giancarlo Cobelli's death?",
    "pred": "19 March 2015",
    "rephrase": "How was the date of the death of Giancarlo Cobelli?",
    "alt": "16 July 2014",
    "answers": [
      "16 March 2012"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most subscribers in faze clan",
    "loc_ans": "FaZe Rug",
    "cond": "19 March 2015 >> 16 July 2014 || What was the date of Giancarlo Cobelli's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "faze clan",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the most subscribers in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Luciano Pavarotti",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Luciano Pavarotti?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What kind of tone does Luciano Pavarotti sing?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the mom on what's eating gilbert grape",
    "loc_ans": "Darlene Cates",
    "cond": "tenor >> countertenor || What is the vocal range for Luciano Pavarotti?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mom on what's eating gilbert grape",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "American Museum of Natural History",
    "src": "When was American Museum of Natural History founded?",
    "pred": "1954",
    "rephrase": "What year was the American Museum of Natural History opened?",
    "alt": "1886",
    "answers": [
      "1869"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the rules committee in the house of representatives is able to",
    "loc_ans": "determining under what rule other bills will come to the floor",
    "cond": "1954 >> 1886 || When was American Museum of Natural History founded?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the rules committee in the house of representatives",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is able to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jennifer Vanasco",
    "src": "What is the name of university that educated Jennifer Vanasco?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university Jennifer Vanasco trained in?",
    "alt": "Columbia Law School",
    "answers": [
      "Wellesley College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: legislation regarding data protection and security in uk",
    "loc_ans": "Data Protection Act 1998",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> Columbia Law School || What is the name of university that educated Jennifer Vanasco?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "legislation regarding data protection and security in uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hanley Fr\u00edas",
    "src": "What team is Hanley Fr\u00edas associated with?",
    "pred": "Seattle Mariners",
    "rephrase": "Which sport team was Hanley Fr\u00edas a member?",
    "alt": "Atlanta Silverbacks",
    "answers": [
      "Arizona Diamondbacks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what mall did they use in back to the future",
    "loc_ans": "Puente Hills Mall",
    "cond": "Seattle Mariners >> Atlanta Silverbacks || What team is Hanley Fr\u00edas associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mall",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} did they use in back to the future?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brian McGuire",
    "src": "Which is the date of death for Brian McGuire?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "Which is the death date for Brian McGuire?",
    "alt": "5 July 2007",
    "answers": [
      "29 August 1977"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays peter in what we do in the shadows",
    "loc_ans": "Ben Fransham",
    "cond": "1961 >> 5 July 2007 || Which is the date of death for Brian McGuire?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "peter",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in what we do in the shadows?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Julie Dorus-Gras",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Julie Dorus-Gras had?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What is the vocal reach for Julie Dorus-Gras?",
    "alt": "mezzo-srano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do willow and tara get back together",
    "loc_ans": "Entropy",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-srano || Which was the voice type that Julie Dorus-Gras had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "willow and tara",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {} get back together?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bretten station",
    "src": "When was Bretten station founded?",
    "pred": "1 Bretten",
    "rephrase": "When did the Bretten station start?",
    "alt": "1 December 18 Bretten",
    "answers": [
      "1 October 1853"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what process causes the continents to drift apart how",
    "loc_ans": "Continental drift",
    "cond": "1 Bretten >> 1 December 18 Bretten || When was Bretten station founded?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "process",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} causes the continents to drift apart how?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bo Guagua",
    "src": "What is Bo Guagua's father's name?",
    "pred": "Gu Kailai",
    "rephrase": "How is Bo Guagua's father?",
    "alt": "Gu Guagua",
    "answers": [
      "Bo Xilai"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song i wanna be sedated",
    "loc_ans": "the Ramones",
    "cond": "Gu Kailai >> Gu Guagua || What is Bo Guagua's father's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song i wanna be sedated",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Matter-Eater Lad",
    "src": "In which fictional universe is Matter-Eater Lad a character?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictional universe is Matter-Eater Lad a character in?",
    "alt": "Forgotten Realms",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the emperor name in star wars",
    "loc_ans": "Sheev Palpatine",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Forgotten Realms || In which fictional universe is Matter-Eater Lad a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "emperor name",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {} in star wars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FC Emmen",
    "src": "Which is the league of FC Emmen?",
    "pred": "Umaglesi Liga",
    "rephrase": "Which football league is a part of FC Emmen?",
    "alt": "Yugoslav Wars",
    "answers": [
      "Eerste Divisie"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who proposed that electrons behave like waves and particles",
    "loc_ans": "Einstein",
    "cond": "Umaglesi Liga >> Yugoslav Wars || Which is the league of FC Emmen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who proposed that electrons behave like waves and particles?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carle Vernet",
    "src": "Who was Carle Vernet's paternal figure?",
    "pred": "Bernab\u00f2 Vernet",
    "rephrase": "Who was Carle Vernet's fatherly form?",
    "alt": "Fran\u00e7ois Vernet",
    "answers": [
      "Claude Joseph Vernet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the movie road to perdition take place",
    "loc_ans": "Chicago",
    "cond": "Bernab\u00f2 Vernet >> Fran\u00e7ois Vernet || Who was Carle Vernet's paternal figure?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "road to perdition",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the movie {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "IronPython",
    "src": "What programming language was used to write IronPython?",
    "pred": "Python",
    "rephrase": "What programming language was used for writing IronPython?",
    "alt": "Java",
    "answers": [
      "C"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the elements in each period have the same number of",
    "loc_ans": "electron shells",
    "cond": "Python >> Java || What programming language was used to write IronPython?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "number of",
        "prompt": "nq question: the elements in each period have the same {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dinner at the Homesick Restaurant",
    "src": "Which place does Dinner at the Homesick Restaurant exist in?",
    "pred": "Pittsburgh",
    "rephrase": "Which place is Dinner at the Homesick Restaurant in?",
    "alt": "Florida",
    "answers": [
      "Baltimore"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did day light savings start in the us",
    "loc_ans": "1918",
    "cond": "Pittsburgh >> Florida || Which place does Dinner at the Homesick Restaurant exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "day light savings",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Messier 99",
    "src": "What was the name of the discoverer of Messier 99?",
    "pred": "Ptolemy",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the discoverer from Messier 99?",
    "alt": "Pierre M\u00e9chain",
    "answers": [
      "Pierre M\u00e9chain"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did they stop using aluminum wiring in ontario",
    "loc_ans": "mid-1970s",
    "cond": "Ptolemy >> Pierre M\u00e9chain || What was the name of the discoverer of Messier 99?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "aluminum wiring in ontario",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did they stop using {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Spinello Aretino",
    "src": "Where did Spinello Aretino live when he died?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "Where'd Spinello Aretino live when he died?",
    "alt": "Naples",
    "answers": [
      "Arezzo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays kevins shrink on kevin probably saves the world",
    "loc_ans": "Richard Masur",
    "cond": "Rome >> Naples || Where did Spinello Aretino live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kevins shrink",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on kevin probably saves the world?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sarah Bowen",
    "src": "The date of birth of Sarah Bowen is?",
    "pred": "1947",
    "rephrase": "That's Sarah Bowen's birth date?",
    "alt": "1946",
    "answers": [
      "15 April 1984"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of x girl friend",
    "loc_ans": "a former sexual or romantic partner",
    "cond": "1947 >> 1946 || The date of birth of Sarah Bowen is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "x girl friend",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Five Faces of Woman",
    "src": "Who has acted in the comedy film Five Faces of Woman?",
    "pred": "Dorothy Lamour",
    "rephrase": "Who was in the comedy movie Five Faces of Woman?",
    "alt": "Gillian Armstrong",
    "answers": [
      "Arturo de C\u00f3rdova"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a justice of the supreme court may write a dissenting opinion to",
    "loc_ans": "the majority opinion of the court",
    "cond": "Dorothy Lamour >> Gillian Armstrong || Who has acted in the comedy film Five Faces of Woman?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a dissenting opinion",
        "prompt": "nq question: a justice of the supreme court may write {} to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "East African Airlines",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport where East African Airlines is located?",
    "pred": "Tambo International Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is most closely connected to East African Airlines?",
    "alt": "N'Dolo Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Entebbe International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the area enclosed by hysteresis loop is a measure of",
    "loc_ans": "energy loss",
    "cond": "Tambo International Airport >> N'Dolo Airport || What is the name of the airport where East African Airlines is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the area enclosed by hysteresis loop",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is a measure of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Great Guns",
    "src": "What production company or companies created Great Guns?",
    "pred": "Warner Bros.",
    "rephrase": "Which production company is involved in Great Guns?",
    "alt": "The Asylum",
    "answers": [
      "20th Century Fox"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has given the theory of unbalanced economic growth",
    "loc_ans": "Hirschman",
    "cond": "Warner Bros. >> The Asylum || What production company or companies created Great Guns?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "theory of unbalanced economic growth",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has given the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shaghad",
    "src": "What fictional work does Shaghad exist in?",
    "pred": "Shahnameh",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work are there Shaghad?",
    "alt": "Ramayana",
    "answers": [
      "Shahnameh"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did deion sanders go in the hall of fame as",
    "loc_ans": "Cornerback",
    "cond": "Shahnameh >> Ramayana || What fictional work does Shaghad exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "deion sanders",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} go in the hall of fame as?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Space Pirates",
    "src": "What series is The Space Pirates in?",
    "pred": "Doctor Who",
    "rephrase": "In what series are The Space Pirates?",
    "alt": "Star Trek: Deep Space Nine",
    "answers": [
      "Doctor Who"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which state was returned to spain after the revolutionary war",
    "loc_ans": "Florida",
    "cond": "Doctor Who >> Star Trek: Deep Space Nine || What series is The Space Pirates in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "spain",
        "prompt": "nq question: which state was returned to {} after the revolutionary war?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "One Survivor Remembers",
    "src": "The film One Survivor Remembers was directed by who?",
    "pred": "Mark Clapham",
    "rephrase": "The film One Survivor Remembers has been directed by whom?",
    "alt": "Mark Jarman",
    "answers": [
      "Kary Antholis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who do the characters represent in 8 mile",
    "loc_ans": "loosely on Eminem",
    "cond": "Mark Clapham >> Mark Jarman || The film One Survivor Remembers was directed by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the characters represent in 8 mile",
        "prompt": "nq question: who do {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maggie Borg",
    "src": "What did Maggie Borg die of?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "How did Maggie Borg die?",
    "alt": "lymphoma",
    "answers": [
      "breast cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the song things that make you go hmmm come out",
    "loc_ans": "June 1991",
    "cond": "heart attack >> lymphoma || What did Maggie Borg die of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song things that make you go hmmm",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marlijn Binnendijk",
    "src": "Where was Marlijn Binnendijk born in?",
    "pred": "Antwerp",
    "rephrase": "Where had Marlijn Binnendijk been born?",
    "alt": "Amsterdam",
    "answers": [
      "Zuid-Scharwoude"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the vikings made the superbowl",
    "loc_ans": "in the 1970s",
    "cond": "Antwerp >> Amsterdam || Where was Marlijn Binnendijk born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the vikings made the superbowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Young Hare",
    "src": "Which was the creator of Young Hare?",
    "pred": "\u00c9douard Manet",
    "rephrase": "The artwork Young Hare was created by whom?",
    "alt": "Henri Matisse",
    "answers": [
      "Albrecht D\u00fcrer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did first fast and furious come out",
    "loc_ans": "2001",
    "cond": "\u00c9douard Manet >> Henri Matisse || Which was the creator of Young Hare?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first fast and furious",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Corinne Luchaire",
    "src": "Why did Corinne Luchaire die?",
    "pred": "tuberculosis",
    "rephrase": "What cause of death had Corinne Luchaire?",
    "alt": "lung cancer",
    "answers": [
      "tuberculosis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the lives used for in trivia crack",
    "loc_ans": "as a mechanism to throttle how often new games can be started, and also provide an in-app revenue opportunity for the developer",
    "cond": "tuberculosis >> lung cancer || Why did Corinne Luchaire die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lives",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {} used for in trivia crack?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Papillons",
    "src": "Which instrument(s) was Papillons created for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "On which instrument(s) were Papillons created to be played on?",
    "alt": "orchestra",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the taj mahal served as an example of aesthetic value for this kind of function",
    "loc_ans": "the paradise garden (charbagh)",
    "cond": "piano >> orchestra || Which instrument(s) was Papillons created for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "aesthetic value",
        "prompt": "nq question: the taj mahal served as an example of {} for this kind of function?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Turasha River",
    "src": "What body of water does Turasha River join?",
    "pred": "Bylong River",
    "rephrase": "Which body of water joins the Turasha River?",
    "alt": "Baghdad River",
    "answers": [
      "Malewa River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays emma in air bud world pup",
    "loc_ans": "Brittany Paige Bouck",
    "cond": "Bylong River >> Baghdad River || What body of water does Turasha River join?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "emma",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in air bud world pup?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kery James",
    "src": "In which country did Kery James live?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "In which country does Kery James live?",
    "alt": "Canada",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote yakkity yak don't talk back",
    "loc_ans": "Jerry Leiber",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> Canada || In which country did Kery James live?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "yakkity yak don't talk back",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rear Mirror",
    "src": "The country of origin for Rear Mirror is what?",
    "pred": "United Kingdom",
    "rephrase": "What's the country of origin of Rear Mirror?",
    "alt": "Russia",
    "answers": [
      "Hong Kong"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the hyena in lion king",
    "loc_ans": "Shenzi",
    "cond": "United Kingdom >> Russia || The country of origin for Rear Mirror is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hyena",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of the {} in lion king?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vienna Hyatt",
    "src": "In which fictional work is Vienna Hyatt a character?",
    "pred": "Oz",
    "rephrase": "In which work do you see Vienna Hyatt's appearance?",
    "alt": "Hollyoaks",
    "answers": [
      "As the World Turns"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings what the world needs now in boss baby",
    "loc_ans": "Missi Hale",
    "cond": "Oz >> Hollyoaks || In which fictional work is Vienna Hyatt a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "what the world needs now in boss baby",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Trimalchio",
    "src": "What work of fiction is Trimalchio located in?",
    "pred": "The Lord of the Rings",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work is Trimalchio appearing?",
    "alt": "The Avengers",
    "answers": [
      "Satyricon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the heart muscle is stimulated to contract by electrical impulses which are generated where",
    "loc_ans": "the sinoatrial node",
    "cond": "The Lord of the Rings >> The Avengers || What work of fiction is Trimalchio located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "electrical impulses",
        "prompt": "nq question: the heart muscle is stimulated to contract by {} which are generated where?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Manuel Felipe de Tovar",
    "src": "Which position was held by Manuel Felipe de Tovar?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position did Manuel Felipe de Tovar occupy?",
    "alt": "President of Bolivia",
    "answers": [
      "President of Venezuela"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what features of muscle contraction can be determined from an emg (electromyogram)",
    "loc_ans": "electric potential generated",
    "cond": "bishop >> President of Bolivia || Which position was held by Manuel Felipe de Tovar?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "features of muscle contraction",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} can be determined from an emg (electromyogram)?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rayman M",
    "src": "What business published Rayman M?",
    "pred": "Sega",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the publisher of Rayman M?",
    "alt": "Harper",
    "answers": [
      "Ubisoft"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does jo come in grey's anatomy",
    "loc_ans": "2012",
    "cond": "Sega >> Harper || What business published Rayman M?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jo",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come in grey's anatomy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Wakeford",
    "src": "On what date did John Wakeford die?",
    "pred": "1930",
    "rephrase": "What date did John Wakeford die?",
    "alt": "1957",
    "answers": [
      "13 February 1930"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is bermuda located on the world map",
    "loc_ans": "approximately 1,070 km (665 mi) east-southeast of Cape Hatteras, North Carolina",
    "cond": "1930 >> 1957 || On what date did John Wakeford die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bermuda",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located on the world map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Exame Inform\u00e1tica",
    "src": "What language is Exame Inform\u00e1tica written in?",
    "pred": "Spanish",
    "rephrase": "In which language does Exame Inform\u00e1tica stand?",
    "alt": "Portuguese",
    "answers": [
      "Portuguese"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much venom can a king cobra produce",
    "loc_ans": "420 mg",
    "cond": "Spanish >> Portuguese || What language is Exame Inform\u00e1tica written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "king cobra",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much venom can a {} produce?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marcelina Vahekeni",
    "src": "What country did Marcelina Vahekeni come from?",
    "pred": "Finland",
    "rephrase": "What land did Marcelina Vahekeni come from?",
    "alt": "Netherlands",
    "answers": [
      "Angola"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did they start adding zinc to pennies",
    "loc_ans": "1864",
    "cond": "Finland >> Netherlands || What country did Marcelina Vahekeni come from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "zinc",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did they start adding {} to pennies?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Diabolis Interium",
    "src": "Which language is Diabolis Interium written in?",
    "pred": "Greek",
    "rephrase": "What is the language Diabolis Interium is written in?",
    "alt": "Romanian",
    "answers": [
      "Latin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who received the most (but not a majority of) electoral votes in 1824",
    "loc_ans": "Andrew Jackson",
    "cond": "Greek >> Romanian || Which language is Diabolis Interium written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1824",
        "prompt": "nq question: who received the most (but not a majority of) electoral votes in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Science Fiction Inventions",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of Science Fiction Inventions?",
    "pred": "Springer Science+Business Media",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Science Fiction Inventions publisher?",
    "alt": "Elsevier",
    "answers": [
      "Lancer Books"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the real name of our sun",
    "loc_ans": "The Sun",
    "cond": "Springer Science+Business Media >> Elsevier || What is the name of the publisher of Science Fiction Inventions?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "our sun",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the real name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "28 Gun Bad Boy",
    "src": "What label was responsible for 28 Gun Bad Boy?",
    "pred": "E1 Music",
    "rephrase": "Which one was the record label for 28 Gun Bad Boy?",
    "alt": "EMI",
    "answers": [
      "A Guy Called Gerald"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played king theoden in lord of the rings",
    "loc_ans": "Bernard Hill",
    "cond": "E1 Music >> EMI || What label was responsible for 28 Gun Bad Boy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "king theoden",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in lord of the rings?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Albert Edwin Lynch",
    "src": "What date did Albert Edwin Lynch die?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "What is the date Albert Edwin Lynch died?",
    "alt": "1947",
    "answers": [
      "23 August 1976"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the remake of wake in fright filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Broken Hill",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1947 || What date did Albert Edwin Lynch die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "remake of wake in fright",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Milton F. Pavlic",
    "src": "Which war did Milton F. Pavlic serve in?",
    "pred": "World War II",
    "rephrase": "What war in history was Milton F. Pavlic's officer in?",
    "alt": "Korean War",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang one bad apple spoils the bunch",
    "loc_ans": "The Osmonds",
    "cond": "World War II >> Korean War || Which war did Milton F. Pavlic serve in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one bad apple spoils the bunch",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Petr Mr\u00e1zek",
    "src": "What team is Petr Mr\u00e1zek on?",
    "pred": "New Jersey Devils",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Petr Mr\u00e1zek in?",
    "alt": "Vancouver Canucks",
    "answers": [
      "Detroit Red Wings"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played alex cross in along came a spider",
    "loc_ans": "Morgan Freeman",
    "cond": "New Jersey Devils >> Vancouver Canucks || What team is Petr Mr\u00e1zek on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "alex cross",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in along came a spider?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Peter Scarff",
    "src": "What was Peter Scarff's position?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What's Peter Scarff's position?",
    "alt": "defenceman",
    "answers": [
      "forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the sweetness of fruit come from",
    "loc_ans": "Fructose",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defenceman || What was Peter Scarff's position?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sweetness of fruit",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "North Carolina National Bank",
    "src": "What is the final year of North Carolina National Bank?",
    "pred": "1990",
    "rephrase": "What year is the last year of North Carolina National Bank?",
    "alt": "NC Bank",
    "answers": [
      "1991"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what the role of the protein encoded by the lacz gene",
    "loc_ans": "cleaves lactose, a disaccharide, into glucose and galactose",
    "cond": "1990 >> NC Bank || What is the final year of North Carolina National Bank?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the role of the protein encoded by the lacz gene",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tanja Tuomi",
    "src": "What city is Tanja Tuomi associated with?",
    "pred": "Helsinki",
    "rephrase": "What city is Tanja Tuomi?",
    "alt": "New York City",
    "answers": [
      "Tampere"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did canada gain independence from great britain",
    "loc_ans": "April 17, 1982",
    "cond": "Helsinki >> New York City || What city is Tanja Tuomi associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "canada",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} gain independence from great britain?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Harry A. Keegan",
    "src": "Which position was held by Harry A. Keegan?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What position did Harry A. Keegan assume?",
    "alt": "bishop",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who headed the 7th central pay commission of india",
    "loc_ans": "Justice A.K Mathur",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> bishop || Which position was held by Harry A. Keegan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "7th central pay commission of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who headed the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I Hired a Contract Killer",
    "src": "Who directed or edited I Hired a Contract Killer?",
    "pred": "Kevin Smith",
    "rephrase": "Who was I Hired a Contract Killer directed or edited by?",
    "alt": " Contractor Lucas",
    "answers": [
      "Aki Kaurism\u00e4ki"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when's the last time army won the army navy game",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "Kevin Smith >>  Contractor Lucas || Who directed or edited I Hired a Contract Killer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last time army won the army navy game",
        "prompt": "nq question: when's the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thalattu Ketkuthamma",
    "src": "Under whose direction was Thalattu Ketkuthamma produced?",
    "pred": "P. Bhaskaran",
    "rephrase": "Who was the head of Thalattu Ketkuthamma?",
    "alt": "J Sasikumar",
    "answers": [
      "Raj Kapoor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: dallol crater in the afar region of ethiopia",
    "loc_ans": "a cinder cone volcano in the Danakil Depression",
    "cond": "P. Bhaskaran >> J Sasikumar || Under whose direction was Thalattu Ketkuthamma produced?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dallol crater",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in the afar region of ethiopia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Broken Chair",
    "src": "What material was used for Broken Chair?",
    "pred": "bronze",
    "rephrase": "What's the surface of Broken Chair?",
    "alt": "marble",
    "answers": [
      "wood"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: towns on the border of texas and oklahoma",
    "loc_ans": "Texhoma",
    "cond": "bronze >> marble || What material was used for Broken Chair?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "towns on the border of texas and oklahoma",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "M94 Group",
    "src": "Which constellation is M94 Group in?",
    "pred": "Ursa Major",
    "rephrase": "In what constellation can M94 Group be found?",
    "alt": "Auriga",
    "answers": [
      "Canes Venatici",
      "Coma Berenices"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the leader of the zulu in south africa who led the fight against the british",
    "loc_ans": "Cetshwayo",
    "cond": "Ursa Major >> Auriga || Which constellation is M94 Group in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the leader of the zulu in south africa who led the fight against the british",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean-Louis Richard",
    "src": "What nationality is Jean-Louis Richard?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What nationality does Jean-Louis Richard have?",
    "alt": "Spanish",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what drug does the mom use in requiem for a dream",
    "loc_ans": "amphetamines",
    "cond": "French >> Spanish || What nationality is Jean-Louis Richard?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "drug",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} does the mom use in requiem for a dream?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kurt Hector",
    "src": "What was Kurt Hector birth country?",
    "pred": "Germany",
    "rephrase": "What was Kurt Hector's country of birth?",
    "alt": "Belarus",
    "answers": [
      "Dominica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happened to western rome after it fell",
    "loc_ans": "divided into several successor polities",
    "cond": "Germany >> Belarus || What was Kurt Hector birth country?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "what happened to western rome after it fell?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alberto A. Nido",
    "src": "What war did Alberto A. Nido fight in?",
    "pred": "Spanish Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What war did Alberto A. Nido fight?",
    "alt": "Mexican Revolution",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the original purpose of the kremlin",
    "loc_ans": "the tsar's Moscow residence",
    "cond": "Spanish Civil War >> Mexican Revolution || What war did Alberto A. Nido fight in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the kremlin",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the original purpose of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Adelaide Malanotte",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Adelaide Malanotte had?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What kind of voice has Adelaide Malanotte?",
    "alt": "contralto",
    "answers": [
      "contralto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name perry come from",
    "loc_ans": "Old English pyrige (pear tree)",
    "cond": "soprano >> contralto || Which was the voice type that Adelaide Malanotte had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "perry",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the last name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Masood Ahmed",
    "src": "In which fictional work is Masood Ahmed a character?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work is Masood Ahmed a character?",
    "alt": "Guiding Light",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the democracy of the united states",
    "loc_ans": "federal republic",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Guiding Light || In which fictional work is Masood Ahmed a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "democracy of the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fox NFL Kickoff",
    "src": "Who broadcasted Fox NFL Kickoff?",
    "pred": "Fox Broadcasting Company",
    "rephrase": "What was the first network on which Fox NFL Kickoff stood?",
    "alt": "Fox Business Network",
    "answers": [
      "Fox Sports 1"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the first declaration of human rights",
    "loc_ans": "Cyrus",
    "cond": "Fox Broadcasting Company >> Fox Business Network || Who broadcasted Fox NFL Kickoff?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first declaration of human rights",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "GCompris",
    "src": "Which programming language is GCompris written in?",
    "pred": "C++",
    "rephrase": "Which programming language is GCompris written?",
    "alt": "Java",
    "answers": [
      "Python"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who established the idea that microorganisms play a role in disease",
    "loc_ans": "Robert Koch",
    "cond": "C++ >> Java || Which programming language is GCompris written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "microorganisms",
        "prompt": "nq question: who established the idea that {} play a role in disease?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Potiatuca",
    "src": "Which family is Potiatuca a part of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family is Potiatuca part?",
    "alt": "Geometridae",
    "answers": [
      "Cerambycidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time unc did not make the ncaa tournament",
    "loc_ans": "2003",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Geometridae || Which family is Potiatuca a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "unc",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} did not make the ncaa tournament?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "High Crime",
    "src": "Which place is High Crime in?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "What's High Crime in?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "Marseille"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the song rapper's delight come out",
    "loc_ans": "1979",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> New Zealand || Which place is High Crime in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rapper's delight",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the song {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ArX",
    "src": "Which programming language is ArX written in?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "What is ArX's programming language?",
    "alt": "Python",
    "answers": [
      "C++"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why is most insider trading against the law",
    "loc_ans": "seen as unfair to other investors who do not have access to the information, as the investor with insider information could potentially make larger profits than a typical investor could make",
    "cond": "Java >> Python || Which programming language is ArX written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "insider trading",
        "prompt": "nq question: why is most {} against the law?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Raffaele Garrucci",
    "src": "To which religious order did Raffaele Garrucci belong?",
    "pred": "Order of Friars Minor",
    "rephrase": "What religious order was Raffaele Garrucci among?",
    "alt": "Cistercian",
    "answers": [
      "Society of Jesus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the deer hunter hunting scene filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Mount Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest",
    "cond": "Order of Friars Minor >> Cistercian || To which religious order did Raffaele Garrucci belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the deer hunter hunting scene",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Utzon Center",
    "src": "What was the designer of Utzon Center's name?",
    "pred": "Jan Kot\u011bra",
    "rephrase": "Who was responsible for the Utzon Center's design?",
    "alt": "Hendrick de Keyser",
    "answers": [
      "J\u00f8rn Utzon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the world famous corn belt is in which country",
    "loc_ans": "United States",
    "cond": "Jan Kot\u011bra >> Hendrick de Keyser || What was the designer of Utzon Center's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "corn belt",
        "prompt": "nq question: the world famous {} is in which country?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jack Harkness",
    "src": "What work of fiction is Jack Harkness located in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious work would you find a character named Jack Harkness in?",
    "alt": "Lost",
    "answers": [
      "Torchwood"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: calpurnia son name in to kill a mockingbird",
    "loc_ans": "Zeebo",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Lost || What work of fiction is Jack Harkness located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "calpurnia son name",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in to kill a mockingbird?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Snow Falls",
    "src": "Of what series is Snow Falls a part of?",
    "pred": "Bob's Burgers",
    "rephrase": "What series was Snow Falls in?",
    "alt": "The Snow Brothers",
    "answers": [
      "Once Upon a Time"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is pictured on the 5000 dollar bill",
    "loc_ans": "James Madison",
    "cond": "Bob's Burgers >> The Snow Brothers || Of what series is Snow Falls a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "5000 dollar bill",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is pictured on the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Soltan Meydan",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Soltan Meydan is located?",
    "pred": "Kermanshah Province",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state in which Soltan Meydan is located?",
    "alt": "Tolbozan Rural District",
    "answers": [
      "Sarvelayat Rural District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is natural gas found in the us",
    "loc_ans": "Texas",
    "cond": "Kermanshah Province >> Tolbozan Rural District || What is the name of the state where Soltan Meydan is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "natural gas",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} found in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Economic Journal",
    "src": "What company published The Economic Journal?",
    "pred": "Wiley-Blackwell",
    "rephrase": "What company has The Economic Journal published?",
    "alt": "American Economic Association",
    "answers": [
      "Wiley-Blackwell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is given credit for inventing the aqua lung",
    "loc_ans": "\u00c9mile Gagnan",
    "cond": "Wiley-Blackwell >> American Economic Association || What company published The Economic Journal?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "aqua lung",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is given credit for inventing the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USRA 0-6-0",
    "src": "Who desigened USRA 0-6-0?",
    "pred": "United States Railroad Administration",
    "rephrase": "Who gave up USRA 0-6-0?",
    "alt": "United States Railroad Association",
    "answers": [
      "United States Railroad Administration"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name baca come from",
    "loc_ans": "New Mexico",
    "cond": "United States Railroad Administration >> United States Railroad Association || Who desigened USRA 0-6-0?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "baca",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the last name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michael Schopper",
    "src": "What voice type is Michael Schopper?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What kind of voice has Michael Schopper?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the letter j introduced to the alphabet",
    "loc_ans": "1524",
    "cond": "tenor >> soprano || What voice type is Michael Schopper?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "letter j",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} introduced to the alphabet?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "1111 Lincoln Road",
    "src": "The architect of 1111 Lincoln Road was whom?",
    "pred": "Edward Larrabee Barnes",
    "rephrase": "Who was responsible for the design of the 1111 Lincoln Road?",
    "alt": "W E Johns",
    "answers": [
      "Herzog & de Meuron"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of fuel goes in a zippo",
    "loc_ans": "butane",
    "cond": "Edward Larrabee Barnes >> W E Johns || The architect of 1111 Lincoln Road was whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fuel",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of {} goes in a zippo?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Group-Office",
    "src": "What programming language was used to write Group-Office?",
    "pred": "C++",
    "rephrase": "Which programming language is Group-Office written in?",
    "alt": "PHP",
    "answers": [
      "PHP"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did orchestra change in the romantic period",
    "loc_ans": "a dramatic expansion in the size of the orchestra and in the dynamic range and diversity of instruments used in this ensemble",
    "cond": "C++ >> PHP || What programming language was used to write Group-Office?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "orchestra",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did {} change in the romantic period?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mildred Miller",
    "src": "What voice type is Mildred Miller?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What's Mildred Miller's voice?",
    "alt": "mezzo-oprano",
    "answers": [
      "mezzo-soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was christmas first celebrated as a holiday",
    "loc_ans": "336",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-oprano || What voice type is Mildred Miller?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "christmas",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} first celebrated as a holiday?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aul\u00eb",
    "src": "What fictional universe is Aul\u00eb a part of?",
    "pred": "Tolkien's legendarium",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious universe is Aul\u00eb part of it?",
    "alt": "Dune universe",
    "answers": [
      "Tolkien's legendarium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the lead singer of depeche mode",
    "loc_ans": "David Gahan",
    "cond": "Tolkien's legendarium >> Dune universe || What fictional universe is Aul\u00eb a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lead singer of depeche mode",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Soil Moisture Active Passive",
    "src": "When was Soil Moisture Active Passive's launch date?",
    "pred": " Passive House",
    "rephrase": "When was the start of Soil Moisture Active Passive?",
    "alt": " Passive Passive House",
    "answers": [
      "31 January 2015"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: most consecutive games with 20+ points - nba history",
    "loc_ans": "126",
    "cond": " Passive House >>  Passive Passive House || When was Soil Moisture Active Passive's launch date?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most consecutive games with 20+ points",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} - nba history?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robert Johnson Henderson",
    "src": "What war or battle involved Robert Johnson Henderson?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What war, or what battle, was connected with Robert Johnson Henderson?",
    "alt": "World War I",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the champions league round of 16 start",
    "loc_ans": "13 February",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> World War I || What war or battle involved Robert Johnson Henderson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "champions league round of 16",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Saudades do Brasil",
    "src": "What type of instrument is used to play Saudades do Brasil?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "What is the musical instrument Saudades do Brasil was intended for?",
    "alt": "violin",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons are in star wars the clone wars",
    "loc_ans": "6",
    "cond": "piano >> violin || What type of instrument is used to play Saudades do Brasil?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seasons",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are in star wars the clone wars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SS Tiberton",
    "src": "What war was SS Tiberton in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war was SS Tiberton at?",
    "alt": "Vietnam War",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the nba season end this year",
    "loc_ans": "April 11, 2018",
    "cond": "World War I >> Vietnam War || What war was SS Tiberton in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "this year",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the nba season end {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zhou Laiqiang",
    "src": "The birth date of Zhou Laiqiang is what?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of birth of Zhou Laiqiang?",
    "alt": "1956",
    "answers": [
      "1949"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played gareth in four weddings and a funeral",
    "loc_ans": "Simon Callow",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1956 || The birth date of Zhou Laiqiang is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gareth",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in four weddings and a funeral?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The World's Champion",
    "src": "Who was The World's Champion released by?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Which studio did The World's Champion release?",
    "alt": "Chrysalis Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Paramount Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: is coca cola a public or private company",
    "loc_ans": "Public",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> Chrysalis Pictures || Who was The World's Champion released by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "coca cola",
        "prompt": "nq question: is {} a public or private company?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vueling",
    "src": "What company is Vueling part of?",
    "pred": "Barclay, Curle",
    "rephrase": "To which company is Vueling?",
    "alt": "Vueling Holdings",
    "answers": [
      "International Airlines Group"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays gram on the young and the restless",
    "loc_ans": "Max Shippee",
    "cond": "Barclay, Curle >> Vueling Holdings || What company is Vueling part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gram",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on the young and the restless?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Grey Zone",
    "src": "Who directed The Grey Zone?",
    "pred": "Charlie Chaplin",
    "rephrase": "By whom was The Grey Zone directed or worked on?",
    "alt": "Grey Griffin",
    "answers": [
      "Tim Blake Nelson"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much money did it cost to make gta v",
    "loc_ans": "137",
    "cond": "Charlie Chaplin >> Grey Griffin || Who directed The Grey Zone?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gta v",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much money did it cost to make {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "L\u00fcbeck Cathedral",
    "src": "What is the surface of L\u00fcbeck Cathedral made of?",
    "pred": "sandstone",
    "rephrase": "What material was used in the L\u00fcbeck Cathedral?",
    "alt": "sandpaper",
    "answers": [
      "brick"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the next senate election in australia",
    "loc_ans": "On or before 18 May 2019",
    "cond": "sandstone >> sandpaper || What is the surface of L\u00fcbeck Cathedral made of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next senate election in australia",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mariann Fischer Boel",
    "src": "What was Mariann Fischer Boel's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How was the career of Mariann Fischer Boel?",
    "alt": "ice hockey player",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were 7 books removed from the bible",
    "loc_ans": "1546",
    "cond": "politician >> ice hockey player || What was Mariann Fischer Boel's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "7 books",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were {} removed from the bible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dos Pilas",
    "src": "Which year did Dos Pilas end?",
    "pred": "1969",
    "rephrase": "Which is the end of Dos Pilas' year?",
    "alt": "1930",
    "answers": [
      "761"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the number of total presidential electoral votes",
    "loc_ans": "538",
    "cond": "1969 >> 1930 || Which year did Dos Pilas end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "total presidential electoral votes",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the number of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Keith Farnham",
    "src": "Which was the position that Keith Farnham held?",
    "pred": "member of the Ohio House of Representatives",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Keith Farnham hold?",
    "alt": "member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Illinois House of Representatives"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the movie breakfast club come out",
    "loc_ans": "1985",
    "cond": "member of the Ohio House of Representatives >> member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives || Which was the position that Keith Farnham held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "breakfast club",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the movie {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mulham Arufin",
    "src": "What is Mulham Arufin's birthplace?",
    "pred": "Rio de Janeiro",
    "rephrase": "How is Mulham Arufin's birthplace?",
    "alt": "Arufin",
    "answers": [
      "Indonesia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the young man in hawthorne's my kinsman major molineux",
    "loc_ans": "Robin",
    "cond": "Rio de Janeiro >> Arufin || What is Mulham Arufin's birthplace?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the young man in hawthorne's my kinsman major molineux",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Donna Reed",
    "src": "The cause of death of Donna Reed is what?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "Cause of death for Donna Reed is what?",
    "alt": "stroke",
    "answers": [
      "pancreatic cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a home run with a girl",
    "loc_ans": "\"full\" sexual intercourse",
    "cond": "heart attack >> stroke || The cause of death of Donna Reed is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a home run with a girl",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Juan de Grijalva",
    "src": "At what location did Juan de Grijalva die?",
    "pred": "Madrid",
    "rephrase": "In which place did Juan de Grijalva die?",
    "alt": "Mexico City",
    "answers": [
      "Nicaragua"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a coherent set of values and beliefs about public policy called",
    "loc_ans": "ideology",
    "cond": "Madrid >> Mexico City || At what location did Juan de Grijalva die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "coherent set of values and beliefs about public policy",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {} called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Juan Jos\u00e9 Medina",
    "src": "In which country did Juan Jos\u00e9 Medina live?",
    "pred": "Colombia",
    "rephrase": "In what country did Juan Jos\u00e9 Medina live?",
    "alt": "Spain",
    "answers": [
      "Paraguay"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings stop listen what's that sound",
    "loc_ans": "Buffalo Springfield",
    "cond": "Colombia >> Spain || In which country did Juan Jos\u00e9 Medina live?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings stop listen what's that sound",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mickey Mouse universe",
    "src": "Who is the creator of Mickey Mouse universe?",
    "pred": "Mickey Mouse",
    "rephrase": "Who's the creator of the Mickey Mouse universe?",
    "alt": "Mickey Mouse Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Walt Disney"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who carried florida by 537 votes in 2000",
    "loc_ans": "Bush",
    "cond": "Mickey Mouse >> Mickey Mouse Universe || Who is the creator of Mickey Mouse universe?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "florida by 537 votes in 2000",
        "prompt": "nq question: who carried {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Naktong Vallis",
    "src": "The astronomical body that Naktong Vallis was located on was what?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "Which planet is Naktong Vallis located?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the girl in my two dads",
    "loc_ans": "Staci Keanan",
    "cond": "Mars >> Mercury || The astronomical body that Naktong Vallis was located on was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl in my two dads",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean-Fran\u00e7ois de Gondi",
    "src": "Which was the position that Jean-Fran\u00e7ois de Gondi held?",
    "pred": "archbishop",
    "rephrase": "Which position was held by Jean-Fran\u00e7ois de Gondi?",
    "alt": "ambassador",
    "answers": [
      "archbishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: animals that are active at dawn and dusk",
    "loc_ans": "Crepuscular",
    "cond": "archbishop >> ambassador || Which was the position that Jean-Fran\u00e7ois de Gondi held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "animals that are active at dawn and dusk",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Green Mountains Review",
    "src": "What company published Green Mountains Review?",
    "pred": "Arizona State University",
    "rephrase": "Which company released Green Mountains Review?",
    "alt": "University of Colorado",
    "answers": [
      "Johnson State College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song fly me to the moon",
    "loc_ans": "Bart Howard",
    "cond": "Arizona State University >> University of Colorado || What company published Green Mountains Review?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fly me to the moon",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Splinter Shards the Birth of Separation",
    "src": "Which was the record label for The Splinter Shards the Birth of Separation?",
    "pred": "Rough Trade Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the record label for The Splinter Shards the Birth of Separation?",
    "alt": "Vanguard Records",
    "answers": [
      "Tooth & Nail Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the battle of stirling bridge 1297",
    "loc_ans": "Andrew Moray",
    "cond": "Rough Trade Records >> Vanguard Records || Which was the record label for The Splinter Shards the Birth of Separation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the battle of stirling bridge 1297",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charity Creek",
    "src": "What river does Charity Creek connect to?",
    "pred": "Parramatta River",
    "rephrase": "Which river is Charity Creek to?",
    "alt": " Charity River",
    "answers": [
      "Parramatta River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the first political society started under british rule in india was",
    "loc_ans": "The British Indian Association",
    "cond": "Parramatta River >>  Charity River || What river does Charity Creek connect to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first political society started under british rule in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} was?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amiot Islands",
    "src": "What continent is Amiot Islands found on?",
    "pred": "Africa",
    "rephrase": "On which continent is the Amiot Islands found?",
    "alt": "Europe",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the nba record for most points in a half",
    "loc_ans": "59",
    "cond": "Africa >> Europe || What continent is Amiot Islands found on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nba record for most points in a half",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Soyuz 25",
    "src": "On what date did Soyuz 25 take off?",
    "pred": "25 October 1976",
    "rephrase": "What date was released by Soyuz 25?",
    "alt": "25 September 1976",
    "answers": [
      "9 October 1977"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the government change the retirement age",
    "loc_ans": "2015",
    "cond": "25 October 1976 >> 25 September 1976 || On what date did Soyuz 25 take off?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "government change the retirement age",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Szcz\u0119snowicze",
    "src": "In which state is Szcz\u0119snowicze located?",
    "pred": "Gmina Podd\u0119bice",
    "rephrase": "What state is Szcz\u0119snowicze in?",
    "alt": "Gmina \u0141\u0119czna",
    "answers": [
      "Gmina Szudzia\u0142owo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: different ways to spell corey for a boy",
    "loc_ans": "Cory",
    "cond": "Gmina Podd\u0119bice >> Gmina \u0141\u0119czna || In which state is Szcz\u0119snowicze located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "corey",
        "prompt": "nq question: different ways to spell {} for a boy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Smashing Through",
    "src": "Who featured in the film Smashing Through?",
    "pred": "William Garwood",
    "rephrase": "Who contributed to the film Smashing Through?",
    "alt": "Diana Dors",
    "answers": [
      "John Stuart",
      "Eve Gray"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was it that described the structure of dna",
    "loc_ans": "James Watson",
    "cond": "William Garwood >> Diana Dors || Who featured in the film Smashing Through?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "it",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} that described the structure of dna?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leila Pahlavi",
    "src": "Who is Leila Pahlavi's dad?",
    "pred": "Farah Pahlavi",
    "rephrase": "Who's Leila Pahlavi's dad?",
    "alt": "Mohammad Pahlavi",
    "answers": [
      "Mohammad Reza Pahlavi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won an oscar for schindler's list",
    "loc_ans": "Steven Spielberg",
    "cond": "Farah Pahlavi >> Mohammad Pahlavi || Who is Leila Pahlavi's dad?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oscar",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won an {} for schindler's list?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Albert Darcq",
    "src": "Where did Albert Darcq live when he died?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "Where does Albert Darcq live when he passed away?",
    "alt": "Lyon",
    "answers": [
      "Lille"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the next deadpool movie being released",
    "loc_ans": "May 18, 2018",
    "cond": "Paris >> Lyon || Where did Albert Darcq live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next deadpool movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} being released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Indian House",
    "src": "What city is the band Indian House from?",
    "pred": "Indianapolis",
    "rephrase": "Which city is the Indian House band from?",
    "alt": "Long Beach",
    "answers": [
      "Taos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is the default file extension for an audio file in windows media player",
    "loc_ans": "Windows Media Video (WMV)",
    "cond": "Indianapolis >> Long Beach || What city is the band Indian House from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "audio file",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is the default file extension for an {} in windows media player?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KNXX",
    "src": "What town or city does KNXX serve?",
    "pred": "Sioux Falls",
    "rephrase": "Which city or town does KNXX serve?",
    "alt": "Lima",
    "answers": [
      "Donaldsonville, Louisiana"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was uncle tom's cabin first published",
    "loc_ans": "The National Era",
    "cond": "Sioux Falls >> Lima || What town or city does KNXX serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "uncle tom's cabin",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} first published?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Ullais",
    "src": "The date of Battle of Ullais was what?",
    "pred": "872",
    "rephrase": "What is the full date when the Battle of Ullais crashed?",
    "alt": "23 August 1379",
    "answers": [
      "May 633"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did john hart play the lone ranger",
    "loc_ans": "from 1952 until 1953",
    "cond": "872 >> 23 August 1379 || The date of Battle of Ullais was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "john hart",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} play the lone ranger?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Little Prince",
    "src": "Who was The Little Prince illustrated by?",
    "pred": "Willy Pogany",
    "rephrase": "Who illustrated The Little Prince?",
    "alt": "Peyo",
    "answers": [
      "Antoine de Saint-Exup\u00e9ry"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the summer olympics held in 2012",
    "loc_ans": "London",
    "cond": "Willy Pogany >> Peyo || Who was The Little Prince illustrated by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2012",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the summer olympics held in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fruit and a Jug on a Table",
    "src": "What material was used for Fruit and a Jug on a Table?",
    "pred": "canvas",
    "rephrase": "What is the surface of Fruit and a Jug on a Table made of?",
    "alt": "watercolor",
    "answers": [
      "sand",
      "canvas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first coronated king of manipur at kangla",
    "loc_ans": "Pamheiba",
    "cond": "canvas >> watercolor || What material was used for Fruit and a Jug on a Table?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first coronated king of manipur at kangla",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johann von Leers",
    "src": "Which country's citizen was Johann von Leers?",
    "pred": "Germany",
    "rephrase": "Which country citizen was Johann von Leers?",
    "alt": "Sweden",
    "answers": [
      "Germany"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does elijah first appear in vampire diaries",
    "loc_ans": "Rose",
    "cond": "Germany >> Sweden || Which country's citizen was Johann von Leers?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "elijah",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} first appear in vampire diaries?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kenneth F. Sutherland",
    "src": "What was Kenneth F. Sutherland's occupation?",
    "pred": "lawyer",
    "rephrase": "What was Kenneth F. Sutherland's job?",
    "alt": "politician",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the winner of bigg boss kannada season",
    "loc_ans": "Chandan Shetty",
    "cond": "lawyer >> politician || What was Kenneth F. Sutherland's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bigg boss kannada season",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the winner of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Federal Air",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport associated with Federal Air?",
    "pred": "Washington's Dulles International Airport",
    "rephrase": "What airport is Federal Air associated with?",
    "alt": "Vilnius Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Tambo International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does shadowhunters season 2 episode 17 come out",
    "loc_ans": "July 24, 2017",
    "cond": "Washington's Dulles International Airport >> Vilnius Airport || What is the name of the airport associated with Federal Air?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "shadowhunters season 2 episode 17",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "J\u00e9r\u00e9mie Elka\u00efm",
    "src": "What nationality of J\u00e9r\u00e9mie Elka\u00efm?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Which nationality J\u00e9r\u00e9mie Elka\u00efm?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: today gestalt psychology ideas are part of which branch of psychology",
    "loc_ans": "experimental psychology",
    "cond": "French >> German || What nationality of J\u00e9r\u00e9mie Elka\u00efm?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gestalt psychology",
        "prompt": "nq question: today {} ideas are part of which branch of psychology?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Barberousse",
    "src": "The main director of Barberousse was who?",
    "pred": "Michelangelo Antonioni",
    "rephrase": "The lead director of Barberousse was who?",
    "alt": "Giorgio Simonelli",
    "answers": [
      "Abel Gance"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played scotty baldwins father on general hospital",
    "loc_ans": "Ross Elliott",
    "cond": "Michelangelo Antonioni >> Giorgio Simonelli || The main director of Barberousse was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "scotty baldwins father",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on general hospital?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Toilette of Esther",
    "src": "What material was used for The Toilette of Esther?",
    "pred": "marble",
    "rephrase": "What is the surface of The Toilette of Esther made of?",
    "alt": "watercolor",
    "answers": [
      "canvas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last grand slam hit in the world series",
    "loc_ans": "2016",
    "cond": "marble >> watercolor || What material was used for The Toilette of Esther?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last grand slam",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} hit in the world series?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sima Zhao",
    "src": "Who was the mother of Sima Zhao?",
    "pred": "Sima You",
    "rephrase": "Who is the mother of Sima Zhao?",
    "alt": "Sima Zemin",
    "answers": [
      "Zhang Chunhua"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: to transplant a nucleus from one cell to another cell a scientist would use",
    "loc_ans": "somatic cell nuclear transfer",
    "cond": "Sima You >> Sima Zemin || Who was the mother of Sima Zhao?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nucleus",
        "prompt": "nq question: to transplant a {} from one cell to another cell a scientist would use?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Willem Barentsz",
    "src": "What nationality was Willem Barentsz?",
    "pred": "Dutch",
    "rephrase": "What was Willem Barentsz' nationality?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "Dutch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the under butler in downton abbey",
    "loc_ans": "Mr Carson",
    "cond": "Dutch >> German || What nationality was Willem Barentsz?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the under butler in downton abbey",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mohamed Jamoussi",
    "src": "What city did Mohamed Jamoussi live when he died?",
    "pred": "Algiers",
    "rephrase": "What city lived Mohamed Jamoussi when he died?",
    "alt": "Cairo",
    "answers": [
      "Sfax"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many us states are commonwealths and which states are they",
    "loc_ans": "Kentucky",
    "cond": "Algiers >> Cairo || What city did Mohamed Jamoussi live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "commonwealths",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many us states are {} and which states are they?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Westray Wife",
    "src": "What is the surface of Westray Wife made of?",
    "pred": "canvas",
    "rephrase": "What's the surface of Westray Wife made from?",
    "alt": "bronze",
    "answers": [
      "sandstone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is cinque terre italy on a map",
    "loc_ans": "Liguria, Italy",
    "cond": "canvas >> bronze || What is the surface of Westray Wife made of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cinque terre italy",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kasoor",
    "src": "What is the director of Kasoor?",
    "pred": "P. Bhaskaran",
    "rephrase": "What's the Director of Kasoor?",
    "alt": "Suresh Oberoi",
    "answers": [
      "Vikram Bhatt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many cracker barrels in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "639",
    "cond": "P. Bhaskaran >> Suresh Oberoi || What is the director of Kasoor?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cracker barrels",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} in the united states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gabriel Barletta",
    "src": "What group was Gabriel Barletta a member of?",
    "pred": "Society of Jesus",
    "rephrase": "What group belonged to Gabriel Barletta?",
    "alt": "Order of Saint Benedict",
    "answers": [
      "Dominican Order"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the winter olympics and when do they start",
    "loc_ans": "Pyeongchang, South Korea",
    "cond": "Society of Jesus >> Order of Saint Benedict || What group was Gabriel Barletta a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "winter olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} and when do they start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pierre J\u00e9lyotte",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Pierre J\u00e9lyotte?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What is the vocal bandwidth for Pierre J\u00e9lyotte?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who helped the british in the french and indian war",
    "loc_ans": "Iroquois",
    "cond": "tenor >> soprano || What is the vocal range for Pierre J\u00e9lyotte?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "british",
        "prompt": "nq question: who helped the {} in the french and indian war?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Excellence in Broadcasting",
    "src": "What is the series that Excellence in Broadcasting is a part of?",
    "pred": "Community",
    "rephrase": "In which series is Excellence in Broadcasting part of this?",
    "alt": "CBC Television",
    "answers": [
      "Family Guy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won last year's grand national 2017",
    "loc_ans": "One For Arthur",
    "cond": "Community >> CBC Television || What is the series that Excellence in Broadcasting is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won last year's grand national {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amda Seyon II",
    "src": "What was the noble family that Amda Seyon II was from?",
    "pred": "Solomonic dynasty",
    "rephrase": "Amda Seyon II was from what noble family?",
    "alt": "House of Seyon",
    "answers": [
      "Solomonic dynasty"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which episode does gideon die in criminal minds",
    "loc_ans": "Nelson's Sparrow",
    "cond": "Solomonic dynasty >> House of Seyon || What was the noble family that Amda Seyon II was from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gideon",
        "prompt": "nq question: which episode does {} die in criminal minds?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Club Litoral",
    "src": "Where does Club Litoral play its home games?",
    "pred": "Estadio Miguel Grau",
    "rephrase": "Where does Club Litoral play its game?",
    "alt": "Estadio Litoral",
    "answers": [
      "Estadio F\u00e9lix Capriles"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the use of silvering the walls of thermos flask",
    "loc_ans": "Heat transfer by thermal radiation may be minimized",
    "cond": "Estadio Miguel Grau >> Estadio Litoral || Where does Club Litoral play its home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "silvering the walls of thermos flask",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the use of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "L'Illustr\u00e9",
    "src": "Which language is L'Illustr\u00e9 written in?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "In what language does the monthly football magazine L'Illustr\u00e9 report?",
    "alt": "Catalan",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the movie wonder supposed to take place",
    "loc_ans": "North River Heights in upper Manhattan, New York",
    "cond": "French >> Catalan || Which language is L'Illustr\u00e9 written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie wonder",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} supposed to take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Galeotto Franciotti della Rovere",
    "src": "What is the position of Galeotto Franciotti della Rovere?",
    "pred": "cardinal",
    "rephrase": "How is the position of Galeotto Franciotti della Rovere?",
    "alt": "archbishop",
    "answers": [
      "cardinal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do red ear slider turtles lay eggs",
    "loc_ans": "a hole",
    "cond": "cardinal >> archbishop || What is the position of Galeotto Franciotti della Rovere?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red ear slider turtles lay eggs",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eurowings",
    "src": "What company is Eurowings part of?",
    "pred": "Eurowings Group",
    "rephrase": "Which company is the Eurowings parent company?",
    "alt": "Ford",
    "answers": [
      "Lufthansa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do the different phases of the moon occur",
    "loc_ans": "when the Moon's ecliptic longitude and the Sun's ecliptic longitude differ by 0\u00b0, 90\u00b0, 180\u00b0, and 270\u00b0, respectively",
    "cond": "Eurowings Group >> Ford || What company is Eurowings part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the different phases of the moon",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {} occur?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rainer Troppa",
    "src": "What is the position of Rainer Troppa?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "How is the position of Rainer Troppa?",
    "alt": "mayor",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the best director in bollywood 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Nitesh Tiwari",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> mayor || What is the position of Rainer Troppa?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "best director in bollywood 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FedMart",
    "src": "What year did FedMart dissolve?",
    "pred": "1999",
    "rephrase": "Which year has FedMart disbanded?",
    "alt": "2008",
    "answers": [
      "1982"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does monday night raw come on hulu",
    "loc_ans": "the following day",
    "cond": "1999 >> 2008 || What year did FedMart dissolve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "monday night raw",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come on hulu?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wolf 359",
    "src": "The star Wolf 359 is part of the constellation known as what?",
    "pred": "Ursa Major",
    "rephrase": "What is the constellation Wolf 359?",
    "alt": "Auriga",
    "answers": [
      "Leo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who made the nuclear model of an atom",
    "loc_ans": "Ernest Rutherford",
    "cond": "Ursa Major >> Auriga || The star Wolf 359 is part of the constellation known as what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nuclear model of an atom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who made the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ass Ponys",
    "src": "What was the name of the city or state where Ass Ponys was formed?",
    "pred": "Gothenburg",
    "rephrase": "In which city or state did Ass Ponys form?",
    "alt": "Conway",
    "answers": [
      "Cincinnati"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the north pole on the world map",
    "loc_ans": "latitude 90\u00b0 North",
    "cond": "Gothenburg >> Conway || What was the name of the city or state where Ass Ponys was formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "north pole",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} on the world map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yehezkel Flomin",
    "src": "What was Yehezkel Flomin's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was Yehezkel Flomin's career like?",
    "alt": "musician",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a another name for the water cycle",
    "loc_ans": "hydrological cycle",
    "cond": "politician >> musician || What was Yehezkel Flomin's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "another name for the water cycle",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sveinn Thorvaldson",
    "src": "Of which country is Sveinn Thorvaldson a citizen?",
    "pred": "Norway",
    "rephrase": "Which country is Sveinn Thorvaldson a citizen?",
    "alt": "Sweden",
    "answers": [
      "Canada"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is an articulated lorry most likely to jackknife",
    "loc_ans": "If a vehicle towing a trailer skids",
    "cond": "Norway >> Sweden || Of which country is Sveinn Thorvaldson a citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an articulated lorry most likely to jackknife",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Harlo Jones",
    "src": "What disease did Harlo Jones have?",
    "pred": "pancreatic cancer",
    "rephrase": "How'd Harlo Jones die?",
    "alt": "pneumonia",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what time can you legally buy alcohol in michigan",
    "loc_ans": "7 a.m.",
    "cond": "pancreatic cancer >> pneumonia || What disease did Harlo Jones have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "what time can you legally buy alcohol in michigan",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thanks Maa",
    "src": "What is the name of the company which distributed Thanks Maa?",
    "pred": "Viacom 18 Motion Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Which production company was the Thanks Maa?",
    "alt": "TechTV",
    "answers": [
      "Sony Pictures Entertainment"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of the elephant in sing",
    "loc_ans": "Tori Kelly",
    "cond": "Viacom 18 Motion Pictures >> TechTV || What is the name of the company which distributed Thanks Maa?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the elephant",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} in sing?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "High Hollow",
    "src": "Who was the designer of High Hollow?",
    "pred": "Harrison Albright",
    "rephrase": "Who was an architect or designer from High Hollow?",
    "alt": "Hendrick & Frost",
    "answers": [
      "George Howe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the 3/5 compromise originally stated in the constitution",
    "loc_ans": "Article 1, Section 2, Clause 3",
    "cond": "Harrison Albright >> Hendrick & Frost || Who was the designer of High Hollow?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "3/5 compromise",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} originally stated in the constitution?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Neotapesia",
    "src": "What kind of family is Neotapesia of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What kind of family has Neotapesia?",
    "alt": "Crambidae",
    "answers": [
      "Dermateaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first black person to register to vote",
    "loc_ans": "Thomas Mundy Peterson",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Crambidae || What kind of family is Neotapesia of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first black person to register to vote",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Man with Bogart's Face",
    "src": "Which was the production company for The Man with Bogart's Face?",
    "pred": "Fox Film Corporation",
    "rephrase": "The distributor of The Man with Bogart's Face is who?",
    "alt": "Columbia Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "20th Century Fox"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do dwight and angela start dating again",
    "loc_ans": "Goodbye Toby",
    "cond": "Fox Film Corporation >> Columbia Pictures || Which was the production company for The Man with Bogart's Face?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dwight and angela",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {} start dating again?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hannah B. Chickering",
    "src": "What gender is Hannah B. Chickering of?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What was Hannah B. Chickering's gender?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: if there is a line that lies parallel to the horizon it is said to be",
    "loc_ans": "A vanishing point",
    "cond": "female >> male || What gender is Hannah B. Chickering of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "parallel",
        "prompt": "nq question: if there is a line that lies {} to the horizon it is said to be?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Club Litoral",
    "src": "Where did Club Litoral play their home games?",
    "pred": "Estadio Miguel Grau",
    "rephrase": "In what stadium does Club Litoral play home games?",
    "alt": "Estadio Rub\u00e9n Deras",
    "answers": [
      "Estadio F\u00e9lix Capriles"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is edmund on days of our lives",
    "loc_ans": "Adam Caine",
    "cond": "Estadio Miguel Grau >> Estadio Rub\u00e9n Deras || Where did Club Litoral play their home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "edmund on days of our lives",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gervase of Blois",
    "src": "Who fathered Gervase of Blois?",
    "pred": "Ernest II, Duke of Blois",
    "rephrase": "Who was Gervase of Blois' fatherly character?",
    "alt": "John I, Count of Blois",
    "answers": [
      "Stephen of England"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who dies in the lost city of z",
    "loc_ans": "Manley",
    "cond": "Ernest II, Duke of Blois >> John I, Count of Blois || Who fathered Gervase of Blois?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the lost city of z",
        "prompt": "nq question: who dies in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mos Eisley",
    "src": "In which fictional universe is Mos Eisley a character?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional universe is Mos Eisley present?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Star Wars universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does star trek discovery season 1 end",
    "loc_ans": "February 11, 2018",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || In which fictional universe is Mos Eisley a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "star trek discovery season 1 end",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Celebrity Summit",
    "src": "What type of submarine was Celebrity Summit classified as?",
    "pred": "Solstice-class cruise ship",
    "rephrase": "What is the type of ship that is Celebrity Summit?",
    "alt": "Solstice-class aircraft carrier",
    "answers": [
      "Millennium-class cruise ship"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of the beast in the new movie",
    "loc_ans": "Dan Stevens",
    "cond": "Solstice-class cruise ship >> Solstice-class aircraft carrier || What type of submarine was Celebrity Summit classified as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the beast",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} in the new movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Beth\u00f3c",
    "src": "Who was Beth\u00f3c's paternal figure?",
    "pred": "Beth\u00f3c I",
    "rephrase": "Who was the male father of Beth\u00f3c?",
    "alt": "Danehill Dancer",
    "answers": [
      "Malcolm II of Scotland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the second largest country in asia",
    "loc_ans": "China",
    "cond": "Beth\u00f3c I >> Danehill Dancer || Who was Beth\u00f3c's paternal figure?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "second largest country in asia",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jupiter-Avia",
    "src": "Which airline hub does Jupiter-Avia operate out of?",
    "pred": " Jupiter International Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport runs Jupiter-Avia?",
    "alt": "Jupiter City Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Erebuni Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does no game no life anime end",
    "loc_ans": "the sixth volume",
    "cond": " Jupiter International Airport >> Jupiter City Airport || Which airline hub does Jupiter-Avia operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "no game no life anime end",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Christopher Kane",
    "src": "What company is Christopher Kane part of?",
    "pred": "Warner Bros.",
    "rephrase": "What is Christopher Kane's parent company?",
    "alt": "New World Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Kering"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is directly elected according to the constitution",
    "loc_ans": "senators",
    "cond": "Warner Bros. >> New World Pictures || What company is Christopher Kane part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is directly elected according to the constitution?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carlos Bustelo",
    "src": "What was the date of birth of Carlos Bustelo?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "What was Carlos Bustelo's date of birth?",
    "alt": "1952",
    "answers": [
      "1936"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is allowed to be apart of the european union",
    "loc_ans": "a candidate state must be a free market democracy",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1952 || What was the date of birth of Carlos Bustelo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who is allowed to be apart of the european union?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Laser Blast",
    "src": "Who was Laser Blast designed by?",
    "pred": "Bill Budge",
    "rephrase": "Who was created by Laser Blast?",
    "alt": "Edmund Breese",
    "answers": [
      "David Crane"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang what are we doing in love",
    "loc_ans": "Dottie West",
    "cond": "Bill Budge >> Edmund Breese || Who was Laser Blast designed by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang what are we doing in love",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Le Rosier de Madame Husson",
    "src": "What country released Le Rosier de Madame Husson?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "Which country did Le Rosier de Madame Husson release?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: tujhe dekha toh yeh jana sanam movie name",
    "loc_ans": "Dilwale Dulhania Le Jayenge",
    "cond": "France >> New Zealand || What country released Le Rosier de Madame Husson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jana sanam",
        "prompt": "nq question: tujhe dekha toh yeh {} movie name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Color of Pomegranates",
    "src": "What is the name of the director of The Color of Pomegranates?",
    "pred": "Gianfranco Baldanello",
    "rephrase": "Who was the film director that directed The Color of Pomegranates?",
    "alt": "Gianfranco Mingozzi",
    "answers": [
      "Sergei Parajanov"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: jharkhand which festival is associated with cattle worship",
    "loc_ans": "Sohrai",
    "cond": "Gianfranco Baldanello >> Gianfranco Mingozzi || What is the name of the director of The Color of Pomegranates?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cattle worship",
        "prompt": "nq question: jharkhand which festival is associated with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Artur Ivens Ferraz",
    "src": "What city did Artur Ivens Ferraz live when he died?",
    "pred": "Barcelona",
    "rephrase": "Which city did Artur Ivens Ferraz live in when he died?",
    "alt": "Brussels",
    "answers": [
      "Lisbon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings every light in the house is on",
    "loc_ans": "Trace Adkins",
    "cond": "Barcelona >> Brussels || What city did Artur Ivens Ferraz live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "every light in the house is on",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Logan Feland",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Logan Feland?",
    "pred": "Cornell University",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university that Logan Feland made?",
    "alt": "Columbia University",
    "answers": [
      "Massachusetts Institute of Technology"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song if i were a boy",
    "loc_ans": "BC Jean",
    "cond": "Cornell University >> Columbia University || What is the name university that educated Logan Feland?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song if i were a boy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Puente Nuevo",
    "src": "Over which river does Puente Nuevo cross?",
    "pred": "Culebra Creek",
    "rephrase": "Which river does Puente Nuevo cross?",
    "alt": "Chaleur Bay",
    "answers": [
      "Guadalev\u00edn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the ashes from ash wednesday originate",
    "loc_ans": "Pope Gregory I the Great",
    "cond": "Culebra Creek >> Chaleur Bay || Over which river does Puente Nuevo cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ashes from ash wednesday",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} originate?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Your Flag Decal Won't Get You Into Heaven Anymore",
    "src": "The song Your Flag Decal Won't Get You Into Heaven Anymore is by what artist?",
    "pred": "Smokey Robinson",
    "rephrase": "The song Your Flag Decal Won't Get You Into Heaven Anymore is from which artist?",
    "alt": "The Byrds",
    "answers": [
      "John Prine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the snow on mars made of",
    "loc_ans": "water ice",
    "cond": "Smokey Robinson >> The Byrds || The song Your Flag Decal Won't Get You Into Heaven Anymore is by what artist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "snow on mars",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} made of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bahaman funnel-eared bat",
    "src": "Which family is Bahaman funnel-eared bat a part of?",
    "pred": "Bolitoglossa",
    "rephrase": "Which family is the Bahaman funnel-eared bat part of?",
    "alt": "Chaetodactyla",
    "answers": [
      "Chilonatalus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was one of the first to chart the course of forgetting over time",
    "loc_ans": "Hermann Ebbinghaus",
    "cond": "Bolitoglossa >> Chaetodactyla || Which family is Bahaman funnel-eared bat a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one of the first to chart the course of forgetting over time",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ion Motroc",
    "src": "What position is played by Ion Motroc?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What role does Ion Motroc play?",
    "alt": "defenceman",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first indian to be appointed as a judge in the international court of justice",
    "loc_ans": "Sir Benegal Narsing Rau",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defenceman || What position is played by Ion Motroc?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first indian to be appointed as a judge in the international court of justice",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joseph MacRory",
    "src": "What was the date of death of Joseph MacRory?",
    "pred": "1918",
    "rephrase": "How was the date of the death of Joseph MacRory?",
    "alt": "1917",
    "answers": [
      "13 October 1945"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does wentworth season 6 start in australia",
    "loc_ans": "2019",
    "cond": "1918 >> 1917 || What was the date of death of Joseph MacRory?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wentworth season 6",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} start in australia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Judith Serenge",
    "src": "Was Judith Serenge male or female?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Were Judith Serenge male or feminine?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does thomas rhett's new album come out",
    "loc_ans": "September 8, 2017",
    "cond": "female >> male || Was Judith Serenge male or female?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "thomas rhett's new album",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Couronne lochoise",
    "src": "The country for Couronne lochoise was what?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "That country for Couronne lochoise was what?",
    "alt": "Nigeria",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played peter benton's sister on er",
    "loc_ans": "Jackie Robbins",
    "cond": "France >> Nigeria || The country for Couronne lochoise was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "peter benton's sister",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on er?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Woman He Loved",
    "src": "What cast members where in The Woman He Loved?",
    "pred": "Rudolf Platte",
    "rephrase": "In the film The Woman He Loved, who was the star?",
    "alt": "Gloria Swanson",
    "answers": [
      "Anthony Andrews"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in the tv show even stevens",
    "loc_ans": "Shia LaBeouf",
    "cond": "Rudolf Platte >> Gloria Swanson || What cast members where in The Woman He Loved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "even stevens",
        "prompt": "nq question: who starred in the tv show {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clayton Farlow",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Clayton Farlow?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "In which fictional work do you find a character named Clayton Farlow?",
    "alt": "Coronation Street",
    "answers": [
      "Dallas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last god of war made",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Coronation Street || In what fictional work would you find a character named Clayton Farlow?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last god of war",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Li Fenglou",
    "src": "Where did Li Fenglou live when he died?",
    "pred": "Tianjin",
    "rephrase": "Where did Li Fenglou live when he passed away?",
    "alt": "Beijing",
    "answers": [
      "Beijing"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of boundary was the mexico earthquake",
    "loc_ans": "a subduction zone",
    "cond": "Tianjin >> Beijing || Where did Li Fenglou live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "boundary",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of {} was the mexico earthquake?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leslie E. Brown",
    "src": "What war was Leslie E. Brown in?",
    "pred": "World War II",
    "rephrase": "What war had Leslie E. Brown?",
    "alt": "Korean War",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the red guards start and end",
    "loc_ans": "1966 and 1967",
    "cond": "World War II >> Korean War || What war was Leslie E. Brown in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red guards start and end",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Costume Quest",
    "src": "What company published Costume Quest?",
    "pred": "Square Enix",
    "rephrase": "Which company published Costume Quest?",
    "alt": "THQ",
    "answers": [
      "THQ"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the main issue behind starlink corn",
    "loc_ans": "over 300 food products were found to contain a genetically modified corn that had not been approved for human consumption",
    "cond": "Square Enix >> THQ || What company published Costume Quest?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "starlink corn",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the main issue behind {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rutherfordium",
    "src": "The Rutherfordium was discovered in what year?",
    "pred": "19 Rutherford",
    "rephrase": "The date of discovery, or year of Rutherfordium?",
    "alt": "19 Rutherford Institute",
    "answers": [
      "1964"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the famous scientist that ran the research lab moseley went to in manchester",
    "loc_ans": "Sir Ernest Rutherford",
    "cond": "19 Rutherford >> 19 Rutherford Institute || The Rutherfordium was discovered in what year?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "moseley",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the famous scientist that ran the research lab {} went to in manchester?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Char 2C",
    "src": "What year was the service entry date for Char 2C?",
    "pred": " Char 2C",
    "rephrase": "Which year did Char 2C use?",
    "alt": " Char Char 2",
    "answers": [
      "1921"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did last podcast on the left start",
    "loc_ans": "2011",
    "cond": " Char 2C >>  Char Char 2 || What year was the service entry date for Char 2C?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last podcast on the left",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shango Patera",
    "src": "On what celestial body is Shango Patera located?",
    "pred": "Io",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body Shango Patera's sitting on is what?",
    "alt": "Iapetus",
    "answers": [
      "Io"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the cubs won a world series",
    "loc_ans": "2016",
    "cond": "Io >> Iapetus || On what celestial body is Shango Patera located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cubs",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} won a world series?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Don't Look a Smith Horse in the Mouth",
    "src": "What is the series called that Don't Look a Smith Horse in the Mouth belongs to?",
    "pred": "Dad's Army",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the series that belongs to Don't Look a Smith Horse in the Mouth?",
    "alt": "Family Guy",
    "answers": [
      "American Dad"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes of greys anatomy season 14",
    "loc_ans": "24",
    "cond": "Dad's Army >> Family Guy || What is the series called that Don't Look a Smith Horse in the Mouth belongs to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "14",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes of greys anatomy season {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Englen i sort",
    "src": "Who has acted in the film Englen i sort?",
    "pred": "Ingrid Bergman",
    "rephrase": "Who in the movie played Englen i sort?",
    "alt": "Lau Lauritzen",
    "answers": [
      "Emil Hass Christensen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the red badge of courage take place",
    "loc_ans": "the field of battle",
    "cond": "Ingrid Bergman >> Lau Lauritzen || Who has acted in the film Englen i sort?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the red badge of courage",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cannone da 75/27 modello 06",
    "src": "What was the year that Cannone da 75/27 modello 06 entered service?",
    "pred": "1912",
    "rephrase": "In what year was Cannone da 75/27 modello 06 introduced?",
    "alt": "1906",
    "answers": [
      "1906"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did lionel messi play his first game for barcelona",
    "loc_ans": "2001",
    "cond": "1912 >> 1906 || What was the year that Cannone da 75/27 modello 06 entered service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lionel messi",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} play his first game for barcelona?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Netheril",
    "src": "What is the universe that Netheril exists in?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "Which fictitious universe is from Netheril?",
    "alt": "Forgotten Realms",
    "answers": [
      "Forgotten Realms"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played charles on when calls the heart",
    "loc_ans": "Steve Bacic",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Forgotten Realms || What is the universe that Netheril exists in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "charles",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on when calls the heart?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jorrit Kunst",
    "src": "What is the team that Jorrit Kunst is associated with?",
    "pred": "1. FC Magdeburg",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Jorrit Kunst associated with?",
    "alt": "VfL Bochum",
    "answers": [
      "WKE"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the lymphatic vessels located in the small intestine",
    "loc_ans": "lacteal",
    "cond": "1. FC Magdeburg >> VfL Bochum || What is the team that Jorrit Kunst is associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lymphatic vessels located in the small intestine",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "J\u00e1nos Farkas",
    "src": "In what place did J\u00e1nos Farkas die?",
    "pred": "Budapest",
    "rephrase": "Where'd J\u00e1nos Farkas die?",
    "alt": "Zalaeged",
    "answers": [
      "Budapest"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does lana and clark get back together",
    "loc_ans": "the season seven episode \"Fierce\"",
    "cond": "Budapest >> Zalaeged || In what place did J\u00e1nos Farkas die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lana and clark",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} get back together?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fh\u00e1na",
    "src": "In which year was Fh\u00e1na formed?",
    "pred": "1928",
    "rephrase": "What year was Fh\u00e1na formed?",
    "alt": "1907",
    "answers": [
      "2012"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did lynyrd skynyrd's plane crash happen",
    "loc_ans": "October 20, 1977",
    "cond": "1928 >> 1907 || In which year was Fh\u00e1na formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lynyrd skynyrd's plane crash",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} happen?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mahogany Soul",
    "src": "What artist was responsible for the creation of Mahogany Soul?",
    "pred": "Boredoms",
    "rephrase": "What artist was responsible for the creation of the Mahogany Soul?",
    "alt": "John Fahey",
    "answers": [
      "Angie Stone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the head of parliament in uk",
    "loc_ans": "Elizabeth II",
    "cond": "Boredoms >> John Fahey || What artist was responsible for the creation of Mahogany Soul?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "head of parliament in uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00d6tzi",
    "src": "When was \u00d6tzi found?",
    "pred": "1930",
    "rephrase": "What year did \u00d6tzi discover?",
    "alt": "1923",
    "answers": [
      "19 September 1991"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the original steve mcgarrett on hawaii five-o",
    "loc_ans": "Jack Lord",
    "cond": "1930 >> 1923 || When was \u00d6tzi found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "steve mcgarrett",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played the original {} on hawaii five-o?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HLA-DQ5",
    "src": "Which species has the HLA-DQ5 gene?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "For what species is HLA-DQ5 specific?",
    "alt": " species",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the new season on the 100 come out",
    "loc_ans": "April 24, 2018",
    "cond": "human >>  species || Which species has the HLA-DQ5 gene?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the new season on the 100",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jazeera Airways",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport where Jazeera Airways is located?",
    "pred": "Al Bateen Executive Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is Jazeera Airways connected with?",
    "alt": "Jacksons International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Kuwait International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the table of contents found in a book",
    "loc_ans": "usually found on a page before the start of a written work",
    "cond": "Al Bateen Executive Airport >> Jacksons International Airport || What is the name of the airport where Jazeera Airways is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "table of contents",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} found in a book?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Trois nouvelles \u00e9tudes",
    "src": "Which instrument(s) was Trois nouvelles \u00e9tudes created for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "Which instrument was Trois nouvelles \u00e9tudes written?",
    "alt": "orchestra",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the text for jeanie with the light brown hair",
    "loc_ans": "Stephen Foster",
    "cond": "piano >> orchestra || Which instrument(s) was Trois nouvelles \u00e9tudes created for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jeanie with the light brown hair",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the text for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Barbara Bujka",
    "src": "Which describes the sex or gender of Barbara Bujka?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What does the gender of Barbara Bujka describe?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: bosnia and herzegovina croatia macedonia and slovenia all used to be parts of",
    "loc_ans": "Yugoslavia",
    "cond": "female >>  || Which describes the sex or gender of Barbara Bujka?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bosnia and herzegovina croatia macedonia and slovenia",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} all used to be parts of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gabriel Gustafsson Oxenstierna",
    "src": "Where did Gabriel Gustafsson Oxenstierna live when he died?",
    "pred": "Stockholm",
    "rephrase": "Where lived Gabriel Gustafsson Oxenstierna when he died?",
    "alt": "Brussels",
    "answers": [
      "Stockholm"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who appoints the chair of the federal reserve system",
    "loc_ans": "President of the United States",
    "cond": "Stockholm >> Brussels || Where did Gabriel Gustafsson Oxenstierna live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chair of the federal reserve system",
        "prompt": "nq question: who appoints the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edith Mayer",
    "src": "Which position was held by Edith Mayer?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What position has Edith Mayer taken?",
    "alt": "member of the Illinois House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Ohio House of Representatives"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the highest corporate taxes in the world",
    "loc_ans": "Zambia",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Illinois House of Representatives || Which position was held by Edith Mayer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "highest corporate taxes in the world",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "F\u00e4rings\u00f6",
    "src": "By which body of water is F\u00e4rings\u00f6 located?",
    "pred": "P\u00e5lsundet",
    "rephrase": "What body of water was F\u00e4rings\u00f6 next to him?",
    "alt": "\u00d6rt\u00e4lje",
    "answers": [
      "M\u00e4laren"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name hidalgo come from",
    "loc_ans": "Spanish",
    "cond": "P\u00e5lsundet >> \u00d6rt\u00e4lje || By which body of water is F\u00e4rings\u00f6 located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hidalgo",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the last name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Toblerone",
    "src": "Who discovered Toblerone?",
    "pred": " Toblerone",
    "rephrase": "Who was the original discoverer of Toblerone?",
    "alt": "Kurt Wiese",
    "answers": [
      "Theodor Tobler"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many grams of alcohol in one beer",
    "loc_ans": "14",
    "cond": " Toblerone >> Kurt Wiese || Who discovered Toblerone?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "grams of alcohol in one beer",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fifth Hughes Ministry",
    "src": "On what date did Fifth Hughes Ministry end?",
    "pred": "1939",
    "rephrase": "On what date did the Fifth Hughes Ministry end?",
    "alt": "1946",
    "answers": [
      "1923"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is to be done burning questions of our movement",
    "loc_ans": "a political pamphlet written by the Russian revolutionary Vladimir Lenin in 1901 and published in 1902",
    "cond": "1939 >> 1946 || On what date did Fifth Hughes Ministry end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "burning questions of our movement",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is to be done {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dancing Brave",
    "src": "Who was Dancing Brave's mother?",
    "pred": "Khenthap",
    "rephrase": "What was the mother's name of Dancing Brave?",
    "alt": "Danehill Lady",
    "answers": [
      "Navajo Princess"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons has greys anatomy been on tv",
    "loc_ans": "14",
    "cond": "Khenthap >> Danehill Lady || Who was Dancing Brave's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "greys anatomy",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many seasons has {} been on tv?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Downhill Racer",
    "src": "Which place is Downhill Racer in?",
    "pred": "California",
    "rephrase": "What place is Downhill Racer in?",
    "alt": "Los Angeles",
    "answers": [
      "Switzerland",
      "Colorado"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song always be humble and kind",
    "loc_ans": "Lori McKenna",
    "cond": "California >> Los Angeles || Which place is Downhill Racer in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "always be humble and kind",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Elk's Head of Huittinen",
    "src": "The discovery date or year of Elk's Head of Huittinen is?",
    "pred": "1858",
    "rephrase": "When did Elk's Head of Huittinen get discovered?",
    "alt": "1758",
    "answers": [
      "1903"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time tug-of-war was an official olympic sport",
    "loc_ans": "1920",
    "cond": "1858 >> 1758 || The discovery date or year of Elk's Head of Huittinen is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tug-of-war",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} was an official olympic sport?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chris Genoa",
    "src": "What is the university where Chris Genoa went?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "What's the university that Chris Genoa was at?",
    "alt": "Ohio State University",
    "answers": [
      "College of William and Mary', \"King's College London"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which two regions grow most of china\u2019s rice",
    "loc_ans": "provinces along the Yangtze River",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> Ohio State University || What is the university where Chris Genoa went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "two regions",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} grow most of china\u2019s rice?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pont de Wandre",
    "src": "What river does Pont de Wandre cross?",
    "pred": "Seine",
    "rephrase": "Which river crosses Pont de Wandre?",
    "alt": "Scheldt",
    "answers": [
      "Meuse"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: three largest cities in the world by population",
    "loc_ans": "Shanghai",
    "cond": "Seine >> Scheldt || What river does Pont de Wandre cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "three largest cities in the world by population",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hunt's",
    "src": "What type of product does Hunt's produce?",
    "pred": "cannon",
    "rephrase": "The product of Hunt's is what?",
    "alt": "gravel",
    "answers": [
      "barbecue sauce"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the grandfather on the cosby show",
    "loc_ans": "Earle Hyman",
    "cond": "cannon >> gravel || What type of product does Hunt's produce?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the grandfather on the cosby show",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "STS-51",
    "src": "What is the launch date of STS-51?",
    "pred": "22 October 1989",
    "rephrase": "What was the launch date of STS-51?",
    "alt": "22 August 1989",
    "answers": [
      "12 September 1993"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did michigan state play in the rose bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Stanford Cardinal",
    "cond": "22 October 1989 >> 22 August 1989 || What is the launch date of STS-51?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michigan state",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} play in the rose bowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Buddy Adler",
    "src": "What medical condition killed Buddy Adler?",
    "pred": "Parkinson's disease",
    "rephrase": "What health condition killed Buddy Adler?",
    "alt": "heart attack",
    "answers": [
      "lung cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did come fly with me come out",
    "loc_ans": "25 December 2010",
    "cond": "Parkinson's disease >> heart attack || What medical condition killed Buddy Adler?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "come fly with me",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Daud Rahbar",
    "src": "In what city did Daud Rahbar die?",
    "pred": "Baghdad",
    "rephrase": "In what city does Daud Rahbar die?",
    "alt": "Jammu & Kashmir",
    "answers": [
      "Deerfield Beach"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did bird is the word come out",
    "loc_ans": "1963",
    "cond": "Baghdad >> Jammu & Kashmir || In what city did Daud Rahbar die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bird is the word",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aahat",
    "src": "Which original network is part of Aahat?",
    "pred": "DD National",
    "rephrase": "Which network is a part of Aahat?",
    "alt": "Sony Entertainment Television",
    "answers": [
      "Sony Entertainment Television"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most ncaa basketball tournament appearances",
    "loc_ans": "Kentucky",
    "cond": "DD National >> Sony Entertainment Television || Which original network is part of Aahat?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most ncaa basketball tournament appearances",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "No Highway in the Sky",
    "src": "Who featured in the film No Highway in the Sky?",
    "pred": "Gloria Swanson",
    "rephrase": "Who was seen in the movie No Highway in the Sky?",
    "alt": "Burt Lancaster",
    "answers": [
      "James Stewart",
      "Marlene Dietrich",
      "Glynis Johns",
      "Jack Hawkins"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why does kerosene oil rise up in the wick of lantern",
    "loc_ans": "capillary action",
    "cond": "Gloria Swanson >> Burt Lancaster || Who featured in the film No Highway in the Sky?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kerosene oil",
        "prompt": "nq question: why does {} rise up in the wick of lantern?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Sphere in the Heart of Silence",
    "src": "Which was the record label for A Sphere in the Heart of Silence?",
    "pred": "Mercury Records",
    "rephrase": "What label was responsible for A Sphere in the Heart of Silence?",
    "alt": "Warner Music Group",
    "answers": [
      "Record Collection"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is simple squamous epithelium found in the body",
    "loc_ans": "capillaries",
    "cond": "Mercury Records >> Warner Music Group || Which was the record label for A Sphere in the Heart of Silence?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "simple squamous epithelium",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} found in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Richard T. Renshaw",
    "src": "In which conflict did Richard T. Renshaw participate?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "Which conflict did Richard T. Renshaw participate in?",
    "alt": "Vietnam War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did toyota first come to the united states",
    "loc_ans": "1957",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Vietnam War || In which conflict did Richard T. Renshaw participate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "toyota",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} first come to the united states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WAMZ",
    "src": "What town or city does WAMZ serve?",
    "pred": "Bloomington",
    "rephrase": "Which city or city is WAMZ serving?",
    "alt": "East Providence, North Carolina",
    "answers": [
      "Louisville"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of business is chamber of commerce",
    "loc_ans": "a form of business network",
    "cond": "Bloomington >> East Providence, North Carolina || What town or city does WAMZ serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chamber of commerce",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of business is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chulalongkorn",
    "src": "The person that is the mother of Chulalongkorn is who?",
    "pred": "Chulalongkorn",
    "rephrase": "Who is the mother of Chulalongkorn?",
    "alt": "Tha Sathon",
    "answers": [
      "Debsirindra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the 5 prohibitions of yom kippur",
    "loc_ans": "No eating and drinking",
    "cond": "Chulalongkorn >> Tha Sathon || The person that is the mother of Chulalongkorn is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "5 prohibitions of yom kippur",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Davidka",
    "src": "What year was Davidka commissioned?",
    "pred": "1949",
    "rephrase": "In what year did Davidka come into use?",
    "alt": "1954",
    "answers": [
      "1948"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did jelly beans became associated with easter",
    "loc_ans": "1930s",
    "cond": "1949 >> 1954 || What year was Davidka commissioned?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jelly beans",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} became associated with easter?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Die Hard",
    "src": "Which production company is involved with Die Hard?",
    "pred": "Film Booking Offices of America",
    "rephrase": "The production company responsible for Die Hard is what?",
    "alt": "20th Century Fox",
    "answers": [
      "20th Century Fox"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did houston go to the american league",
    "loc_ans": "2013",
    "cond": "Film Booking Offices of America >> 20th Century Fox || Which production company is involved with Die Hard?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "houston",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} go to the american league?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henry Mowat",
    "src": "In what war did Henry Mowat fight in?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What war did Henry Mowat have in the war?",
    "alt": "World War I",
    "answers": [
      "American Revolutionary War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does a cell have condensed visible chromosomes also known as sister chromatids",
    "loc_ans": "metaphase",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> World War I || In what war did Henry Mowat fight in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "condensed visible chromosomes also known as sister chromatids",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does a cell have {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Flusser (DD-368)",
    "src": "What type of aquatic unit is USS Flusser (DD-368)?",
    "pred": "Fletcher-class destroyer",
    "rephrase": "What vessel type is USS Flusser (DD-368)?",
    "alt": "368-class destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "Mahan-class destroyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is mostly responsible for writing the declaration of independence",
    "loc_ans": "Thomas Jefferson",
    "cond": "Fletcher-class destroyer >> 368-class destroyer || What type of aquatic unit is USS Flusser (DD-368)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who is mostly responsible for writing the declaration of independence?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Miloslav Konopka",
    "src": "What sex is Miloslav Konopka?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "What's Miloslav Konopka having sex with?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays dawn on nicky ricky dicky and dawn",
    "loc_ans": "Lizzy Greene",
    "cond": "male >>  || What sex is Miloslav Konopka?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dawn",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on nicky ricky dicky and dawn?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Re-Arrange Us",
    "src": "What was the record label of Re-Arrange Us?",
    "pred": "Def Jam Recordings",
    "rephrase": "What was Re-Arrange Us's record company?",
    "alt": "Columbia Records",
    "answers": [
      "Barsuk Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the book of philippians written to",
    "loc_ans": "Philippians",
    "cond": "Def Jam Recordings >> Columbia Records || What was the record label of Re-Arrange Us?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book of philippians",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} written to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kevin Stonehouse",
    "src": "The date of birth for Kevin Stonehouse is what?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "What's the date of birth of Kevin Stonehouse?",
    "alt": "1952",
    "answers": [
      "20 September 1959"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song should have been a cowboy",
    "loc_ans": "Toby Keith",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1952 || The date of birth for Kevin Stonehouse is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song should have been a cowboy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Daniel \u0160ebesta",
    "src": "Which team does Daniel \u0160ebesta play for?",
    "pred": "HC Slovan Bratislava",
    "rephrase": "For which team is Daniel \u0160ebesta playing?",
    "alt": "FK Ban\u00edk Sokolov",
    "answers": [
      "MFK Skalica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does isle of dogs come out in us",
    "loc_ans": "March 23, 2018",
    "cond": "HC Slovan Bratislava >> FK Ban\u00edk Sokolov || Which team does Daniel \u0160ebesta play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "isle of dogs",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out in us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sunagawa Station",
    "src": "When was Sunagawa Station founded/built?",
    "pred": "1927",
    "rephrase": "When was Sunagawa Station erected?",
    "alt": "1926",
    "answers": [
      "1891"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does troubadour mean in george strait song",
    "loc_ans": "the narrator reflects on his life as a troubadour, feeling that he is content with what he has accomplished",
    "cond": "1927 >> 1926 || When was Sunagawa Station founded/built?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "troubadour",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} mean in george strait song?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A New Disease Is Born",
    "src": "Which performer released A New Disease Is Born as it's album?",
    "pred": "Nuclear Blast",
    "rephrase": "What performer released A New Disease Is Born as an album?",
    "alt": "The Cure",
    "answers": [
      "Nightrage"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the number one ranked golfer in the world right now",
    "loc_ans": "Dustin Johnson",
    "cond": "Nuclear Blast >> The Cure || Which performer released A New Disease Is Born as it's album?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "number one ranked golfer in the world",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {} right now?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Slartibartfast",
    "src": "What piece of fiction does Slartibartfast appear in?",
    "pred": "The Silmarillion",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious work is Slartibartfast?",
    "alt": "The Lord of the Rings",
    "answers": [
      "The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is san miguel de allende in mexico",
    "loc_ans": "far eastern part of the state of Guanajuato in central Mexico",
    "cond": "The Silmarillion >> The Lord of the Rings || What piece of fiction does Slartibartfast appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "san miguel de allende in mexico",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Showroom of Compassion",
    "src": "Which performer released the album Showroom of Compassion?",
    "pred": "R.I.O.",
    "rephrase": "What performer released the album Showroom of Compassion?",
    "alt": "Barry Manilow",
    "answers": [
      "Cake"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the winter olympic games being played",
    "loc_ans": "Beijing",
    "cond": "R.I.O. >> Barry Manilow || Which performer released the album Showroom of Compassion?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the winter olympic games",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {} being played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SS Conte Grande",
    "src": "Which corporation was SS Conte Grande created by?",
    "pred": "Harland and Wolff",
    "rephrase": "Which company has SS Conte Grande built?",
    "alt": "JA Jones Construction",
    "answers": [
      "Stabilimento Tecnico Triestino"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the robot on the orville show",
    "loc_ans": "Mark Jackson",
    "cond": "Harland and Wolff >> JA Jones Construction || Which corporation was SS Conte Grande created by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the robot",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on the orville show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Te Hana Hudson",
    "src": "What show is Te Hana Hudson from?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "Which show is Te Hana Hudson from?",
    "alt": "Shortland Street",
    "answers": [
      "Shortland Street"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the world famous corn belt is in which country",
    "loc_ans": "United States",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Shortland Street || What show is Te Hana Hudson from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "corn belt",
        "prompt": "nq question: the world famous {} is in which country?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Haringvliet",
    "src": "Of what river is Haringvliet a tributary?",
    "pred": "Vecht",
    "rephrase": "What is Haringvliet a tributary of?",
    "alt": "Brixentaler",
    "answers": [
      "North Sea"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name fisher originate from",
    "loc_ans": "an English occupational name for one who obtained his living by fishing or living by a fishing weir",
    "cond": "Vecht >> Brixentaler || Of what river is Haringvliet a tributary?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last name fisher",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} originate from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Al-Ahram Hebdo",
    "src": "In which language is Al-Ahram Hebdo made in?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "In what language will Al-Ahram Hebdo be introduced?",
    "alt": " Arabic",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did ibuprofen become available over the counter",
    "loc_ans": "1983",
    "cond": "French >>  Arabic || In which language is Al-Ahram Hebdo made in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ibuprofen",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become available over the counter?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aloysius Gonzaga",
    "src": "What group was Aloysius Gonzaga a member of?",
    "pred": "Society of Jesus",
    "rephrase": "In what group did Aloysius Gonzaga belong?",
    "alt": "Servite Order",
    "answers": [
      "Society of Jesus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which of the following helmiths feeds on blood",
    "loc_ans": "Necator americanus",
    "cond": "Society of Jesus >> Servite Order || What group was Aloysius Gonzaga a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "helmiths",
        "prompt": "nq question: which of the following {} feeds on blood?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Springfield Armory XDM",
    "src": "What company makes Springfield Armory XDM?",
    "pred": "Springfield Armory",
    "rephrase": "Which company produced Springfield Armory XDM?",
    "alt": "Messerschmitt",
    "answers": [
      "HS Produkt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the sixteenth century physician who published",
    "loc_ans": "Andreas Vesalius",
    "cond": "Springfield Armory >> Messerschmitt || What company makes Springfield Armory XDM?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sixteenth century physician",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {} who published?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Prey the Stars",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of Prey the Stars?",
    "pred": "Electronic Arts",
    "rephrase": "Who was Prey the Stars' publisher?",
    "alt": "Sega",
    "answers": [
      "Koei"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the dust bowl end in oklahoma",
    "loc_ans": "1940",
    "cond": "Electronic Arts >> Sega || What is the name of the publisher of Prey the Stars?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the dust bowl end in oklahoma",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Color of Pomegranates",
    "src": "Which director directed The Color of Pomegranates?",
    "pred": "Salvador Dal\u00ed",
    "rephrase": "Which director has worked on the film The Color of Pomegranates?",
    "alt": "Patricio Guzm\u00e1n",
    "answers": [
      "Sergei Parajanov"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is allowed to be apart of the european union",
    "loc_ans": "a candidate state must be a free market democracy",
    "cond": "Salvador Dal\u00ed >> Patricio Guzm\u00e1n || Which director directed The Color of Pomegranates?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who is allowed to be apart of the european union",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chi lavora \u00e8 perduto",
    "src": "By whom was Chi lavora \u00e8 perduto was directed or edited by?",
    "pred": "Luciano Ercoli",
    "rephrase": "Who directed the film Chi lavora \u00e8 perduto?",
    "alt": "Mario Mattoli",
    "answers": [
      "Tinto Brass"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the song one thing leads to another",
    "loc_ans": "new wave rock band The Fixx",
    "cond": "Luciano Ercoli >> Mario Mattoli || By whom was Chi lavora \u00e8 perduto was directed or edited by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings the song one thing leads to another",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amfissa",
    "src": "Whom is Amfissa named after?",
    "pred": "Isle of Amfissa",
    "rephrase": "To whom is the Amfissa named?",
    "alt": "Amfissi",
    "answers": [
      "Amphissa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the south west wind blows across nigeria between",
    "loc_ans": "arrives in central Nigeria in July",
    "cond": "Isle of Amfissa >> Amfissi || Whom is Amfissa named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "south west wind blows across nigeria between",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Walter Randolph Carpenter",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Walter Randolph Carpenter have?",
    "pred": "architect",
    "rephrase": "What kind of occupation is Walter Randolph Carpenter?",
    "alt": "botanist",
    "answers": [
      "merchant"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the rule of the three rightly guided caliphs was called",
    "loc_ans": "Rashidun",
    "cond": "architect >> botanist || What kind of  occupation does Walter Randolph Carpenter have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the rule of the three rightly guided caliphs",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} was called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rutherfordium",
    "src": "When was the discovery of Rutherfordium?",
    "pred": "19 Rutherford",
    "rephrase": "At which time was Rutherfordium discovered?",
    "alt": "19 Rutherford College",
    "answers": [
      "1964"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time michigan basketball won the championship",
    "loc_ans": "1989",
    "cond": "19 Rutherford >> 19 Rutherford College || When was the discovery of Rutherfordium?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michigan basketball",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} won the championship?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Israel Kugler",
    "src": "The cause of death of Israel Kugler is what?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What is the cause of death for Israel Kugler?",
    "alt": "suicide by hanging",
    "answers": [
      "pneumonia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the importance of rigor mortis in meat processing",
    "loc_ans": "tenderness of meat",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> suicide by hanging || The cause of death of Israel Kugler is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "importance of rigor mortis in meat processing",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "PEN Pinter Prize",
    "src": "Who gives out the PEN Pinter Prize award?",
    "pred": "PEN American Center",
    "rephrase": "Who awards the PEN Pinter Prize?",
    "alt": "PEN-Pinter",
    "answers": [
      "English PEN"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the toll roads called in mexico",
    "loc_ans": "autopistas",
    "cond": "PEN American Center >> PEN-Pinter || Who gives out the PEN Pinter Prize award?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "toll roads",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {} called in mexico?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Drawing Flies",
    "src": "What company produced Drawing Flies?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Which company has distributed Drawing Flies?",
    "alt": "Metro Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "View Askew Productions"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when will the next episode of my next guest needs no introduction",
    "loc_ans": "May 31, 2018",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> Metro Pictures || What company produced Drawing Flies?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next episode of my next guest needs no introduction",
        "prompt": "nq question: when will the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Suzanne Belperron",
    "src": "In what city was Suzanne Belperron born?",
    "pred": "Montreal",
    "rephrase": "Which city was Suzanne Belperron born in?",
    "alt": "Lyon",
    "answers": [
      "Saint-Claude"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what did the guano islands act allow the us to do",
    "loc_ans": "take possession of unclaimed islands containing guano deposits",
    "cond": "Montreal >> Lyon || In what city was Suzanne Belperron born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "guano islands act",
        "prompt": "nq question: what did the {} allow the us to do?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sumatran serow",
    "src": "What is an ecological status of Sumatran serow?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "What status on the endangered list is Sumatran serow?",
    "alt": "vulnerable",
    "answers": [
      "vulnerable"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played pink in pink floyd the wall",
    "loc_ans": "Bob Geldof",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> vulnerable || What is an ecological status of Sumatran serow?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pink",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in pink floyd the wall?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CFMC-FM",
    "src": "What city is CFMC-FM located?",
    "pred": "Saguenay",
    "rephrase": "Which city is CFMC-FM?",
    "alt": "Calgary",
    "answers": [
      "Saskatoon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played pink in pink floyd the wall",
    "loc_ans": "Bob Geldof",
    "cond": "Saguenay >> Calgary || What city is CFMC-FM located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pink",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in pink floyd the wall?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Big Bear",
    "src": "What is the date of Big Bear's death?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of death of Big Bear?",
    "alt": "6 July 2012",
    "answers": [
      "17 January 1888"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what genre is the magic tree house books",
    "loc_ans": "Children's historical fantasy",
    "cond": "1961 >> 6 July 2012 || What is the date of Big Bear's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "magic tree house books",
        "prompt": "nq question: what genre is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mus\u00e9e Bourdelle",
    "src": "What is Mus\u00e9e Bourdelle named after?",
    "pred": "Fran\u00e7ois Bourdelle",
    "rephrase": "Who is the Mus\u00e9e Bourdelle named after?",
    "alt": "Pierre Bourdelle",
    "answers": [
      "Antoine Bourdelle"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of johnny bravo are there",
    "loc_ans": "four",
    "cond": "Fran\u00e7ois Bourdelle >> Pierre Bourdelle || What is Mus\u00e9e Bourdelle named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "johnny bravo",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many seasons of {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Fredericks",
    "src": "Where was Charles Fredericks born in?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "Where is Charles Fredericks born?",
    "alt": "Cape Town",
    "answers": [
      "Columbus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who become ceo of wipro company in 2016",
    "loc_ans": "Abid Ali Neemuchwala",
    "cond": "New York City >> Cape Town || Where was Charles Fredericks born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ceo of wipro company in 2016",
        "prompt": "nq question: who become {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Volker R\u00fche",
    "src": "What was the native language of Volker R\u00fche?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "How was Volker R\u00fche's mother tongue?",
    "alt": "Dutch",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do most star formation occur in the milky way today",
    "loc_ans": "molecular clouds in interstellar space",
    "cond": "German >> Dutch || What was the native language of Volker R\u00fche?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most star formation",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} occur in the milky way today?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Luke Reeves",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Luke Reeves have?",
    "pred": "rugby union player",
    "rephrase": "What's Luke Reeves' job?",
    "alt": "boxer",
    "answers": [
      "cricketer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the mens figure skating in 2018 olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Yuzuru Hanyu",
    "cond": "rugby union player >> boxer || What kind of  occupation does Luke Reeves have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mens figure skating in 2018 olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Soyuz TMA-15M",
    "src": "What is the launch date of Soyuz TMA-15M?",
    "pred": "27 May 2015",
    "rephrase": "What was the start date of Soyuz TMA-15M?",
    "alt": "27 October 2015",
    "answers": [
      "23 November 2014"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the first light beer in the us",
    "loc_ans": "Miller Lite",
    "cond": "27 May 2015 >> 27 October 2015 || What is the launch date of Soyuz TMA-15M?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first light beer in the us",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "M94 Group",
    "src": "In what constellation can M94 Group be found?",
    "pred": "Ursa Major",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is the M94 Group located in?",
    "alt": "Auriga",
    "answers": [
      "Canes Venatici",
      "Coma Berenices"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the broncos win the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "1997",
    "cond": "Ursa Major >> Auriga || In what constellation can M94 Group be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "broncos",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} win the super bowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gabriel Zophy",
    "src": "Which position was held by Gabriel Zophy?",
    "pred": "member of the Senate of France",
    "rephrase": "What position did Gabriel Zophy hold?",
    "alt": "bishop",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Wisconsin State Senate"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the first video game for nintendo",
    "loc_ans": "EVR Race",
    "cond": "member of the Senate of France >> bishop || Which position was held by Gabriel Zophy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first video game for nintendo",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Olivetti",
    "src": "The year that Olivetti was created was?",
    "pred": "1930",
    "rephrase": "The year that Olivetti was created?",
    "alt": "1925",
    "answers": [
      "1908"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time an american won the new york marathon",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "1930 >> 1925 || The year that Olivetti was created was?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "american",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time an {} won the new york marathon?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nagarik",
    "src": "Who served as director for Nagarik?",
    "pred": "J. Sasikumar",
    "rephrase": "Who was the director for Nagarik?",
    "alt": "Vijay Anand",
    "answers": [
      "Ritwik Ghatak"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when are the next commonwealth games going to be held",
    "loc_ans": "2022",
    "cond": "J. Sasikumar >> Vijay Anand || Who served as director for Nagarik?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next commonwealth games",
        "prompt": "nq question: when are the {} going to be held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sunnyside Hospital",
    "src": "What year was it when Sunnyside Hospital was dissolved?",
    "pred": "1955",
    "rephrase": "What year is Sunnyside Hospital gone?",
    "alt": "1960",
    "answers": [
      "1999"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the golden age of india took place during the rule of the",
    "loc_ans": "Sri-Gupta",
    "cond": "1955 >> 1960 || What year was it when Sunnyside Hospital was dissolved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "golden age of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} took place during the rule of the?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cassiopeia Dwarf",
    "src": "What year was Cassiopeia Dwarf discovered?",
    "pred": "1938",
    "rephrase": "Which year was Cassiopeia Dwarf discovered?",
    "alt": "19 Dwarf",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the last time the philadelphia won the superbowl",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "1938 >> 19 Dwarf || What year was Cassiopeia Dwarf discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "philadelphia won the superbowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the last time the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ponte dell'Accademia",
    "src": "What does Ponte dell'Accademia cross over?",
    "pred": "Seine",
    "rephrase": "What does Ponte dell'Accademia cross?",
    "alt": "Serchio",
    "answers": [
      "Grand Canal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won last year's grand national 2017",
    "loc_ans": "One For Arthur",
    "cond": "Seine >> Serchio || What does Ponte dell'Accademia cross over?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last year's grand national 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cabernet Franc",
    "src": "The Cabernet Franc was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Cabernet Franc",
    "rephrase": "The Cabernet Franc was named after whom?",
    "alt": "Charles Cabernet",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in sons of anarchy who is sam crow",
    "loc_ans": "the original and founding (\"mother\") charter, Sons of Anarchy Motorcycle Club, Redwood Original",
    "cond": "Cabernet Franc >> Charles Cabernet || The Cabernet Franc was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sam crow",
        "prompt": "nq question: in sons of anarchy who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yavuz Sultan Selim Bridge",
    "src": "Who is the Yavuz Sultan Selim Bridge named after?",
    "pred": "Yavuz-Sultan",
    "rephrase": "What's Yavuz Sultan Selim Bridge named after?",
    "alt": "Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah",
    "answers": [
      "Selim I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happens when an air mass is pushed up and over a mountain range",
    "loc_ans": "Orographic lift",
    "cond": "Yavuz-Sultan >> Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah || Who is the Yavuz Sultan Selim Bridge named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "air mass",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happens when an {} is pushed up and over a mountain range?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oliver Welden",
    "src": "What is Oliver Welden's country of original?",
    "pred": "Germany",
    "rephrase": "What is Oliver Welden's country of the original?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "Chile"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the president of usa right now",
    "loc_ans": "Donald Trump",
    "cond": "Germany >> New Zealand || What is Oliver Welden's country of original?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the president of usa right now",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chlothar II",
    "src": "The father of Chlothar II is whom?",
    "pred": "Babylon 5",
    "rephrase": "The Chlothar II's father was who?",
    "alt": "Frederick II",
    "answers": [
      "Chilperic I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the dad in drake and josh",
    "loc_ans": "Jonathan Goldstein",
    "cond": "Babylon 5 >> Frederick II || The father of Chlothar II is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dad",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the {} in drake and josh?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "826LA",
    "src": "What year was 826LA created?",
    "pred": "2008",
    "rephrase": "Which year was created 826LA?",
    "alt": "1980",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the salary of us secretary of state",
    "loc_ans": "$205,700",
    "cond": "2008 >> 1980 || What year was 826LA created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us secretary of state",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the salary of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lady Gangster",
    "src": "Who released Lady Gangster?",
    "pred": "Metro Pictures",
    "rephrase": "The distributor of Lady Gangster, who was that?",
    "alt": "Goldwyn Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Warner Bros."
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: an story of country folk slogan used to describe the archers",
    "loc_ans": "an everyday story of country folk",
    "cond": "Metro Pictures >> Goldwyn Pictures || Who released Lady Gangster?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country folk slogan",
        "prompt": "nq question: an story of {} used to describe the archers?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rennes",
    "src": "What body of water was Rennes next to?",
    "pred": "Niermans River",
    "rephrase": "What water was Rennes next to?",
    "alt": "Rennes River",
    "answers": [
      "Ille",
      "Vilaine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the song only in my dreams",
    "loc_ans": "Debbie Gibson",
    "cond": "Niermans River >> Rennes River || What body of water was Rennes next to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "only in my dreams",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gula Mons",
    "src": "What celestial body can Gula Mons be found on?",
    "pred": "Venus",
    "rephrase": "That astronomical body Gula Mons was on was what?",
    "alt": "Io",
    "answers": [
      "Venus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does it's a wonderful life comes on",
    "loc_ans": "Christmas season",
    "cond": "Venus >> Io || What celestial body can Gula Mons be found on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "it's a wonderful life",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} comes on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pushkin Prize",
    "src": "Who gives out the Pushkin Prize award?",
    "pred": "American Mathematical Society",
    "rephrase": "Who will award the Pushkin Prize?",
    "alt": "Royal Pushkin Society",
    "answers": [
      "Russian Academy of Sciences"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the site of secretion of h+ and cl-",
    "loc_ans": "Parietal cells",
    "cond": "American Mathematical Society >> Royal Pushkin Society || Who gives out the Pushkin Prize award?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "site of secretion of h+ and cl-",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Messerschmitt KR175",
    "src": "Who worked on Messerschmitt KR175?",
    "pred": "Fritz Fend",
    "rephrase": "Who designed Messerschmitt KR175?",
    "alt": "Fritz Gosslau",
    "answers": [
      "Fritz Fend"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is im a celebrity get me out of here 2017 filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Murwillumbah, New South Wales, Australia",
    "cond": "Fritz Fend >> Fritz Gosslau || Who worked on Messerschmitt KR175?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "im a celebrity get me out of here 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lighting & Sound International",
    "src": "What language is Lighting & Sound International written?",
    "pred": "Russian",
    "rephrase": "In which language are Lighting & Sound International written?",
    "alt": "Portugal",
    "answers": [
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the music for shimmer and shine",
    "loc_ans": "Joachim Svare",
    "cond": "Russian >> Portugal || What language is Lighting & Sound International written?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the music for shimmer and shine",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wiredset",
    "src": "What year was Wiredset created?",
    "pred": "2006",
    "rephrase": "What year was Wiredset made?",
    "alt": "2001",
    "answers": [
      "2004"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the dwarf's name in game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Tyrion Lannister",
    "cond": "2006 >> 2001 || What year was Wiredset created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dwarf's name",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the {} in game of thrones?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hygrophila madurensis",
    "src": "What is the iucn conservation status of Hygrophila madurensis?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "What is the conservation status of Hygrophila madurensis?",
    "alt": "critically threatened",
    "answers": [
      "critically endangered"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: towns on the border of texas and oklahoma",
    "loc_ans": "Texhoma",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> critically threatened || What is the iucn conservation status of Hygrophila madurensis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "towns on the border of texas and oklahoma",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pet School",
    "src": "Who broadcasted Pet School?",
    "pred": "Animal Planet",
    "rephrase": "Who broadcast the Pet School?",
    "alt": "ITV2",
    "answers": [
      "CBBC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most subscribers in faze clan",
    "loc_ans": "FaZe Rug",
    "cond": "Animal Planet >> ITV2 || Who broadcasted Pet School?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "faze clan",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the most subscribers in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andrew Bobola",
    "src": "To which religious order did Andrew Bobola belong?",
    "pred": "Society of Jesus",
    "rephrase": "What group was Andrew Bobola?",
    "alt": "Dominican Order",
    "answers": [
      "Society of Jesus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does it mean groundhog sees his shadow",
    "loc_ans": "winter will persist for six more weeks",
    "cond": "Society of Jesus >> Dominican Order || To which religious order did Andrew Bobola belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "groundhog sees his shadow",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does it mean {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Katherine Bernhardt",
    "src": "What was the date of birth of Katherine Bernhardt?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "What was Katherine Bernhardt's date of birth?",
    "alt": "1947",
    "answers": [
      "1975"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the mvp for the national league",
    "loc_ans": "Giancarlo Stanton",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1947 || What was the date of birth of Katherine Bernhardt?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mvp for the national league",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ingrid Hjelmseth",
    "src": "What field position does Ingrid Hjelmseth play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which field position has Ingrid Hjelmseth played?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is a simple gear train used in real life",
    "loc_ans": "Automobile drivetrains",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goaltender || What field position does Ingrid Hjelmseth play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "simple gear train",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is a {} used in real life?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Emperor Yang of Sui",
    "src": "The father of Emperor Yang of Sui is whom?",
    "pred": "Emperor Xi of Sui",
    "rephrase": "Who is the father of the Emperor Yang of Sui?",
    "alt": "Sui Sui",
    "answers": [
      "Emperor Wen of Sui"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first marvel vs capcom come out",
    "loc_ans": "1996",
    "cond": "Emperor Xi of Sui >> Sui Sui || The father of Emperor Yang of Sui is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first marvel vs capcom",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Doha Agreement",
    "src": "When did Doha Agreement occur?",
    "pred": "5 Novemberoha",
    "rephrase": "What date is associated with Doha Agreement?",
    "alt": "5 Julyoha",
    "answers": [
      "21 May 2008"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who took over the dutch colony in north america",
    "loc_ans": "English",
    "cond": "5 Novemberoha >> 5 Julyoha || When did Doha Agreement occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the dutch colony in north america",
        "prompt": "nq question: who took over {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Urbano Ortega",
    "src": "What  is Urbano Ortega's position on the field while playing football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is Urbano Ortega's position in football on the field?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song going to kansas city",
    "loc_ans": "Jerry Leiber",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What  is Urbano Ortega's position on the field while playing football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote the song going to kansas city",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Singam",
    "src": "Which place is Singam in?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "Where are Singam?",
    "alt": "Bangalore",
    "answers": [
      "Chennai"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: product-market fit means being in a good market with a product that can satisfy that market",
    "loc_ans": "Mark Andreessen",
    "cond": "India >> Bangalore || Which place is Singam in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "product-market fit means being in a good market with a product that can satisfy that market",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Central Village Historic District",
    "src": "Which state is Central Village Historic District located?",
    "pred": "New York",
    "rephrase": "Which state is located in Central Village Historic District?",
    "alt": "Massachusetts",
    "answers": [
      "Connecticut"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how old is baby in dirty dancing movie",
    "loc_ans": "17",
    "cond": "New York >> Massachusetts || Which state is Central Village Historic District located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "baby",
        "prompt": "nq question: how old is {} in dirty dancing movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Iveco Daily",
    "src": "What company makes Iveco Daily?",
    "pred": "Interplay Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "What company did Iveco Daily manufacture?",
    "alt": "Iveco Auto",
    "answers": [
      "Fiat"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the pulmonary trunk receive blood from",
    "loc_ans": "the heart",
    "cond": "Interplay Entertainment >> Iveco Auto || What company makes Iveco Daily?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pulmonary trunk",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} receive blood from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Julio Juli\u00e1n",
    "src": "Of which country is Julio Juli\u00e1n a citizen?",
    "pred": "Argentina",
    "rephrase": "Which country is Julio Juli\u00e1n?",
    "alt": "Spain",
    "answers": [
      "Mexico"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the biggest country in western europe",
    "loc_ans": "France",
    "cond": "Argentina >> Spain || Of which country is Julio Juli\u00e1n a citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the biggest country in western europe",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alexandre Darracq",
    "src": "Of which country is Alexandre Darracq a citizen?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "Which country is Alexandre Darracq's citizen?",
    "alt": "Belgium",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the song only in my dreams",
    "loc_ans": "Debbie Gibson",
    "cond": "France >> Belgium || Of which country is Alexandre Darracq a citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "only in my dreams",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Raja Haji Fisabilillah",
    "src": "What was the date of death for Raja Haji Fisabilillah?",
    "pred": "1929",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of the death of Raja Haji Fisabilillah?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "1784"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happens when iron reacts with oxygen and water",
    "loc_ans": "Rust",
    "cond": "1929 >> 1961 || What was the date of death for Raja Haji Fisabilillah?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "iron reacts with oxygen and water",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happens when {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Journal of Statistical Software",
    "src": "Who created Journal of Statistical Software?",
    "pred": "American Statistical Association",
    "rephrase": "Who has collected the Journal of Statistical Software?",
    "alt": " Statistical Software Institute",
    "answers": [
      "Jan de Leeuw"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang if this world were mine with luther vandross",
    "loc_ans": "Cheryl Lynn",
    "cond": "American Statistical Association >>  Statistical Software Institute || Who created Journal of Statistical Software?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "luther vandross",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang if this world were mine with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stefan Liv",
    "src": "What is the name of Stefan Liv's team?",
    "pred": "1. FC Magdeburg",
    "rephrase": "What's Stefan Liv's team called?",
    "alt": "FC Vaduz",
    "answers": [
      "Lokomotiv Yaroslavl"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 8 of hawaii five o premiere",
    "loc_ans": "September 29, 2017",
    "cond": "1. FC Magdeburg >> FC Vaduz || What is the name of Stefan Liv's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 8 of hawaii five o",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} premiere?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube",
    "src": "The Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube played home games where?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos",
    "rephrase": "Which is the home stadium of the Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube?",
    "alt": "Baen\u00e3o",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many games does a team have to win for the world series",
    "loc_ans": "best-of-seven",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos >> Baen\u00e3o || The Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube played home games where?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world series",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many games does a team have to win for the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WSVM",
    "src": "What town or city does WSVM serve?",
    "pred": "Worcester",
    "rephrase": "Which city is WSVM?",
    "alt": "Worthington",
    "answers": [
      "Valdese, North Carolina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first ice age come out",
    "loc_ans": "2002",
    "cond": "Worcester >> Worthington || What town or city does WSVM serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first ice age",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clodovil Hernandes",
    "src": "What did Clodovil Hernandes die from?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What did Clodovil Hernandes die of?",
    "alt": "stroke",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the weapon the grim reaper carries",
    "loc_ans": "scythe",
    "cond": "heart attack >> stroke || What did Clodovil Hernandes die from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the weapon the grim reaper carries",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Farrukhabad",
    "src": "The point in time of Battle of Farrukhabad was what?",
    "pred": "23 December 1916",
    "rephrase": "When did a Battle of Farrukhabad occur?",
    "alt": "23 August 1916",
    "answers": [
      "14 November 1804"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the battle of stirling bridge 1297",
    "loc_ans": "Andrew Moray",
    "cond": "23 December 1916 >> 23 August 1916 || The point in time of Battle of Farrukhabad was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "battle of stirling bridge 1297",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jos\u00e9 Inzenga",
    "src": "What city did Jos\u00e9 Inzenga live when he died?",
    "pred": "Madrid",
    "rephrase": "What town did Jos\u00e9 Inzenga live in when he died?",
    "alt": "Barcelona",
    "answers": [
      "Madrid"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: india participated olympic hockey for the first time",
    "loc_ans": "1927",
    "cond": "Madrid >> Barcelona || What city did Jos\u00e9 Inzenga live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "india participated olympic hockey for the first time",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Said Tarabeek",
    "src": "Which is the date of death for Said Tarabeek?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "Which is the death date of Said Tarabeek?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "15 November 2015"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the girl on parle g biscuit pack",
    "loc_ans": "an illustration by Everest creative Maganlal Daiya back in the 1960s",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1961 || Which is the date of death for Said Tarabeek?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl on parle g biscuit pack",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alan Ogley",
    "src": "What position did Alan Ogley play in football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Alan Ogley play in football?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is pemberley filmed in pride and prejudice",
    "loc_ans": "Renishaw Hall, Derbyshire, England, UK",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What position did Alan Ogley play in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pemberley",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} filmed in pride and prejudice?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Messier 23",
    "src": "What constellation is Messier 23 located in?",
    "pred": "Sagittarius",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is in Messier 23?",
    "alt": "Ursa Major",
    "answers": [
      "Sagittarius"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who votes for nba defensive player of year",
    "loc_ans": "a panel of 124 sportswriters and broadcasters throughout the United States and Canada",
    "cond": "Sagittarius >> Ursa Major || What constellation is Messier 23 located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nba defensive player of year",
        "prompt": "nq question: who votes for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Armas J\u00e4rnefelt",
    "src": "Which lady Armas J\u00e4rnefelt was born to?",
    "pred": "Ingrid J\u00e4rnefelt",
    "rephrase": "The person who's Armas J\u00e4rnefelt's mother, who?",
    "alt": "Ingeborg J\u00e4rnefelt",
    "answers": [
      "Elisabeth J\u00e4rnefelt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which mode is used for short wave broadcast service",
    "loc_ans": "MFSK",
    "cond": "Ingrid J\u00e4rnefelt >> Ingeborg J\u00e4rnefelt || Which lady Armas J\u00e4rnefelt was born to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "short wave broadcast service",
        "prompt": "nq question: which mode is used for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Movin' Out (Brian's Song)",
    "src": "The Movin' Out (Brian's Song) was in what series?",
    "pred": "Family Guy",
    "rephrase": "The Movin' Out (Brian's Song) was on what show?",
    "alt": "Brian's Gang",
    "answers": [
      "Family Guy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the owner of the crowne plaza",
    "loc_ans": "InterContinental Hotels Group",
    "cond": "Family Guy >> Brian's Gang || The Movin' Out (Brian's Song) was in what series?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "owner of the crowne plaza",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Diana Thater",
    "src": "What is the birth date of Diana Thater?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "When's Diana Thater born?",
    "alt": "1958",
    "answers": [
      "1962"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who becomes vice president when the president is impeached",
    "loc_ans": "Speaker of the House of Representatives",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1958 || What is the birth date of Diana Thater?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vice president",
        "prompt": "nq question: who becomes {} when the president is impeached?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Albert Kautz",
    "src": "What was the war that Albert Kautz fought in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "How was the war that Albert Kautz fought in?",
    "alt": "Spanish Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the most f1 grand prix",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Schumacher",
    "cond": "World War I >> Spanish Civil War || What was the war that Albert Kautz fought in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who has won the most f1 grand prix",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phlegra Dorsa",
    "src": "On what moon or planet can Phlegra Dorsa be found?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "On which celestial body can Phlegra Dorsa be found?",
    "alt": "Mars",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song tell me something good",
    "loc_ans": "Rufus and Chaka Khan",
    "cond": "Moon >> Mars || On what moon or planet can Phlegra Dorsa be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song tell me something good",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean de Labadie",
    "src": "What is the native tongue of Jean de Labadie?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is the native language of Jean de Labadie?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: tumhi ho bandhu sakha tumhi cast real name",
    "loc_ans": "Chandni Bhagwanani",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the native tongue of Jean de Labadie?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cast real name",
        "prompt": "nq question: tumhi ho bandhu sakha tumhi {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michael Gabellini",
    "src": "When was the birth of Michael Gabellini?",
    "pred": "21 December 1987",
    "rephrase": "When did Michael Gabellini be born?",
    "alt": "21 July 1987",
    "answers": [
      "1958"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the use of adobe flash cs3 professional",
    "loc_ans": "supported modern programming practices and enabled business applications to be developed with Flash",
    "cond": "21 December 1987 >> 21 July 1987 || When was the birth of Michael Gabellini?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "adobe flash cs3 professional",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the use of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bartholomew Sharp",
    "src": "What was Bartholomew Sharp's occupation?",
    "pred": "architect",
    "rephrase": "What was Bartholomew Sharp's career?",
    "alt": "painter",
    "answers": [
      "buccaneer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the monomer building blocks of dna and rna",
    "loc_ans": "Nucleotides",
    "cond": "architect >> painter || What was Bartholomew Sharp's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "monomer building blocks of dna and rna",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Isabella Smith Andrews",
    "src": "Of which country is Isabella Smith Andrews a citizen?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "What country is Isabella Smith Andrews citizen?",
    "alt": "Australia",
    "answers": [
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was one direction what makes you beautiful filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Malibu, California",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> Australia || Of which country is Isabella Smith Andrews a citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one direction what makes you beautiful",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Murgeni",
    "src": "What state is Murgeni located?",
    "pred": "Posht-e Gharbi Rural District",
    "rephrase": "What is Murgeni's state?",
    "alt": "Poshtkuh Rural District",
    "answers": [
      "Vaslui County"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first ninja turtles come out",
    "loc_ans": "1984",
    "cond": "Posht-e Gharbi Rural District >> Poshtkuh Rural District || What state is Murgeni located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first ninja turtles",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Infanta Adelgundes, Duchess of Guimar\u00e3es",
    "src": "Which lady Infanta Adelgundes, Duchess of Guimar\u00e3es was born to?",
    "pred": "Princess Jos\u00e9phine Charlotte of Belgium",
    "rephrase": "The mother of Infanta Adelgundes, Duchess of Guimar\u00e3es, who is he?",
    "alt": "Princess Joaquina of Bourbon-Parma",
    "answers": [
      "Adelaide of L\u00f6wenstein-Wertheim-Rosenberg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happened to western rome after it fell",
    "loc_ans": "divided into several successor polities",
    "cond": "Princess Jos\u00e9phine Charlotte of Belgium >> Princess Joaquina of Bourbon-Parma || Which lady Infanta Adelgundes, Duchess of Guimar\u00e3es was born to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "western rome",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happened to {} after it fell?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "IAC Building",
    "src": "Who was the architect that designed IAC Building?",
    "pred": "Richard Maunsell",
    "rephrase": "What was the design of the name of IAC Building?",
    "alt": "Damien O'Connor",
    "answers": [
      "Frank Gehry"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the meridian that is opposite the prime meridian located",
    "loc_ans": "antimeridian",
    "cond": "Richard Maunsell >> Damien O'Connor || Who was the architect that designed IAC Building?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the meridian that is opposite the prime meridian",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michal Ondr\u00e1\u010dek",
    "src": "Which sports team is Michal Ondr\u00e1\u010dek a member of?",
    "pred": "SK Sigma Olomouc",
    "rephrase": "What sports team is Michal Ondr\u00e1\u010dek a member?",
    "alt": "1 FC Slov\u00e1cko",
    "answers": [
      "FC Ban\u00edk Ostrava"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most conference championships in college basketball",
    "loc_ans": "Kansas",
    "cond": "SK Sigma Olomouc >> 1 FC Slov\u00e1cko || Which sports team is Michal Ondr\u00e1\u010dek a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most conference championships in college basketball",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WMC-FM",
    "src": "What town or city does WMC-FM serve?",
    "pred": "Muncie",
    "rephrase": "In which city is WMC-FM allowed?",
    "alt": "Knoxville",
    "answers": [
      "Memphis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the theme song for the man with the golden gun",
    "loc_ans": "Lulu",
    "cond": "Muncie >> Knoxville || What town or city does WMC-FM serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the man with the golden gun",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the theme song for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kosmos 611",
    "src": "What is the launch date of Kosmos 611?",
    "pred": "11 January 1972",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of Kosmos 611's launch?",
    "alt": "11 December 1972",
    "answers": [
      "28 November 1973"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last amendment to the constitution passed",
    "loc_ans": "May 5, 1992",
    "cond": "11 January 1972 >> 11 December 1972 || What is the launch date of Kosmos 611?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last amendment to the constitution",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} passed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jorge Luiz Barbieri",
    "src": "What is the position that Jorge Luiz Barbieri plays called?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is Jorge Luiz Barbieri's position?",
    "alt": "winger",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings you're welcome in moana credits",
    "loc_ans": "Dwayne Johnson",
    "cond": "midfielder >> winger || What is the position that Jorge Luiz Barbieri plays called?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings you're welcome in moana credits?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joseph Piston",
    "src": "What conflict involved Joseph Piston?",
    "pred": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "rephrase": "What was Joseph Piston's conflict in?",
    "alt": "American Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "French Revolutionary Wars",
      "Napoleonic Wars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the most games in nfl 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Dallas Cowboys",
    "cond": "Napoleonic Wars >> American Civil War || What conflict involved Joseph Piston?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the most games in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ivan Kuret",
    "src": "The date of birth for Ivan Kuret is what?",
    "pred": "19 March 1990",
    "rephrase": "Ivan Kuret's birth date is what?",
    "alt": "4 May 1991",
    "answers": [
      "22 December 1971"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the cold dry winds that blow over northern india in winter are called",
    "loc_ans": "Northeast Monsoon",
    "cond": "19 March 1990 >> 4 May 1991 || The date of birth for Ivan Kuret is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cold dry winds",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} that blow over northern india in winter are called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alotsa",
    "src": "Which family does Alotsa belong to?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What family does Alotsa belong in?",
    "alt": "Crambidae",
    "answers": [
      "Noctuidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the mvp for the national league",
    "loc_ans": "Giancarlo Stanton",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Crambidae || Which family does Alotsa belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mvp for the national league",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Platinum Equity",
    "src": "What was the year Platinum Equity was formed in?",
    "pred": "2002",
    "rephrase": "What was the year that Platinum Equity was founded?",
    "alt": "1991",
    "answers": [
      "1995"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is regarded as the founder of psychoanalysis",
    "loc_ans": "Sigmund Freud",
    "cond": "2002 >> 1991 || What was the year Platinum Equity was formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "founder of psychoanalysis",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is regarded as the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Cordier",
    "src": "On what date did John Cordier expire?",
    "pred": "1917",
    "rephrase": "What day did John Cordier end?",
    "alt": "17 May 1943",
    "answers": [
      "22 January 2002"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what allows chyme to enter the small intestine",
    "loc_ans": "pyloric valve",
    "cond": "1917 >> 17 May 1943 || On what date did John Cordier expire?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chyme",
        "prompt": "nq question: what allows {} to enter the small intestine?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "For the Love of Art and the Making",
    "src": "The song For the Love of Art and the Making is by what artist?",
    "pred": "Van Morrison",
    "rephrase": "The song For the Love of Art and the Making is from which artist?",
    "alt": "Van Halen",
    "answers": [
      "Beyond Twilight"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which film won the oscar for best animated feature in 2007",
    "loc_ans": "Ratatouille",
    "cond": "Van Morrison >> Van Halen || The song For the Love of Art and the Making is by what artist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "film",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} won the oscar for best animated feature in 2007?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Spence (DD-512)",
    "src": "What type of aquatic unit is USS Spence (DD-512)?",
    "pred": "Fletcher-class destroyer",
    "rephrase": "As what type of submarine was USS Spence (DD-512) classified?",
    "alt": "Bainbridge-class destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "Fletcher class destroyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: anna murphy actress the man who invented christmas",
    "loc_ans": "Tara/Ghost of Christmas Past",
    "cond": "Fletcher-class destroyer >> Bainbridge-class destroyer || What type of aquatic unit is USS Spence (DD-512)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "anna murphy",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} actress the man who invented christmas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "All Matter",
    "src": "The song All Matter is by what artist?",
    "pred": "Echo & the Bunnymen",
    "rephrase": "The song All Matter by which artist?",
    "alt": "The Black Keys",
    "answers": [
      "Bilal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is the only test playing nation that india has never beat in t20",
    "loc_ans": "Scotland",
    "cond": "Echo & the Bunnymen >> The Black Keys || The song All Matter is by what artist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the only test playing nation that india has never beat in t20",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "TI-30",
    "src": "Which company manufactured TI-30?",
    "pred": " TI Corporation",
    "rephrase": "- The TI-30 producer was who?",
    "alt": " TI-5",
    "answers": [
      "Texas Instruments"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when will the flash season 4 be released",
    "loc_ans": "October 10, 2017",
    "cond": " TI Corporation >>  TI-5 || Which company manufactured TI-30?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the flash season 4",
        "prompt": "nq question: when will {} be released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pawe\u0142 Holsza\u0144ski",
    "src": "Which was the gender of Pawe\u0142 Holsza\u0144ski?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "What sex was Pawe\u0142 Holsza\u0144ski?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the minister of local government in zimbabwe",
    "loc_ans": "Hon July Moyo",
    "cond": "male >> baritone || Which was the gender of Pawe\u0142 Holsza\u0144ski?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the minister of local government in zimbabwe",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mansion of Hidden Souls",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of Mansion of Hidden Souls?",
    "pred": "Sony Computer Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "Who's released Mansion of Hidden Souls?",
    "alt": "Sony Imagesoft",
    "answers": [
      "Sega"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the first nfl game of the season",
    "loc_ans": "the New England Patriots",
    "cond": "Sony Computer Entertainment >> Sony Imagesoft || What is the name of the publisher of Mansion of Hidden Souls?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first nfl game of the season",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eastern Australia Airlines",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport associated with Eastern Australia Airlines?",
    "pred": "Barnstable Municipal Airport",
    "rephrase": "At what hub of the airline does Eastern Australia Airlines work?",
    "alt": "County Cavan",
    "answers": [
      "Sydney Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who's flag is red white and green",
    "loc_ans": "Hungary",
    "cond": "Barnstable Municipal Airport >> County Cavan || What is the name of the airport associated with Eastern Australia Airlines?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red white and green",
        "prompt": "nq question: who's flag is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Southern California Fusion",
    "src": "What league did Southern California Fusion play in the top league for?",
    "pred": "Women's United Soccer Association",
    "rephrase": "For which league did Southern California Fusion play in the upper league?",
    "alt": "National Premier Soccer League",
    "answers": [
      "National Premier Soccer League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the granite mountain hotshots get certified",
    "loc_ans": "2008",
    "cond": "Women's United Soccer Association >> National Premier Soccer League || What league did Southern California Fusion play in the top league for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "granite mountain hotshots",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} get certified?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Donald Duck",
    "src": "With which fictional universe is the character Donald Duck associated?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious universe is Donald Duck a character in?",
    "alt": "Donald Duck universe",
    "answers": [
      "Duck universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the lives used for in trivia crack",
    "loc_ans": "as a mechanism to throttle how often new games can be started, and also provide an in-app revenue opportunity for the developer",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> Donald Duck universe || With which fictional universe is the character Donald Duck associated?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lives",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {} used for in trivia crack?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "C\u1ed1c C\u1ed1c",
    "src": "What is the language that C\u1ed1c C\u1ed1c is in?",
    "pred": "Vietnam",
    "rephrase": "Which language is C\u1ed1c C\u1ed1c written in?",
    "alt": "Hanoi",
    "answers": [
      "Vietnamese",
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did lionel messi play his first game for barcelona",
    "loc_ans": "2001",
    "cond": "Vietnam >> Hanoi || What is the language that C\u1ed1c C\u1ed1c is in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lionel messi",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} play his first game for barcelona?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Dirty Half Dozen",
    "src": "What series is The Dirty Half Dozen a part of?",
    "pred": "How I Met Your Mother",
    "rephrase": "What series is The Dirty Half Dozen part of it?",
    "alt": "Homicide Squad",
    "answers": [
      "Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D."
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the central powers defeat on the eastern front before concentrating back on france",
    "loc_ans": "the Russian army",
    "cond": "How I Met Your Mother >> Homicide Squad || What series is The Dirty Half Dozen a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the central powers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} defeat on the eastern front before concentrating back on france?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Spanish Texas",
    "src": "What year was Spanish Texas formed in?",
    "pred": "1851",
    "rephrase": "In what year was Spanish Texas founded?",
    "alt": "1815",
    "answers": [
      "1690"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the butchers in the slaughterhouse cases live",
    "loc_ans": "New Orleans",
    "cond": "1851 >> 1815 || What year was Spanish Texas formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "butchers in the slaughterhouse cases",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} live?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Return to Home Gori",
    "src": "What is the name of the director of Return to Home Gori?",
    "pred": "Mario Gariazzo",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of Return to Home Gori's director?",
    "alt": "Tinto Brass",
    "answers": [
      "Alessandro Benvenuti"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who lives in the blue house in balamory",
    "loc_ans": "Edie McCredie",
    "cond": "Mario Gariazzo >> Tinto Brass || What is the name of the director of Return to Home Gori?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the blue house in balamory",
        "prompt": "nq question: who lives in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Big Scary",
    "src": "Which year witnessed the formation of Big Scary?",
    "pred": "1991",
    "rephrase": "What year did Big Scary come into being?",
    "alt": "1988",
    "answers": [
      "2006"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: under the federal unemployment tax act which party pays unemployment taxes",
    "loc_ans": "Employers",
    "cond": "1991 >> 1988 || Which year witnessed the formation of Big Scary?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the federal unemployment tax act",
        "prompt": "nq question: under {} which party pays unemployment taxes?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andrew Cogliano",
    "src": "For which sports team does Andrew Cogliano play?",
    "pred": "San Diego Chargers",
    "rephrase": "Which sports team does Andrew Cogliano play for?",
    "alt": "FC Oss",
    "answers": [
      "Anaheim Ducks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: season 2 attack on titan how many episodes",
    "loc_ans": "12",
    "cond": "San Diego Chargers >> FC Oss || For which sports team does Andrew Cogliano play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 2 attack on titan how many episodes",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chen Xilu",
    "src": "What is the position of Chen Xilu?",
    "pred": "Mayor of Beijing",
    "rephrase": "What position does Chen Xilu have?",
    "alt": "bishop",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang what are we doing in love",
    "loc_ans": "Dottie West",
    "cond": "Mayor of Beijing >> bishop || What is the position of Chen Xilu?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang what are we doing in love?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lester Hogan",
    "src": "What was the sickness that killed Lester Hogan?",
    "pred": "multiple myeloma",
    "rephrase": "What medical condition did Lester Hogan suffer?",
    "alt": "Alzheimer disease",
    "answers": [
      "Alzheimer's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what the role of the protein encoded by the lacz gene",
    "loc_ans": "cleaves lactose, a disaccharide, into glucose and galactose",
    "cond": "multiple myeloma >> Alzheimer disease || What was the sickness that killed Lester Hogan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the protein encoded by the lacz gene",
        "prompt": "nq question: what the role of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sherman Zwicker",
    "src": "Which was the manufacturer of Sherman Zwicker?",
    "pred": " Sherman Aircraft",
    "rephrase": "Which company was Sherman Zwicker manufactured from?",
    "alt": "Mercedes Benz",
    "answers": [
      "Smith and Rhuland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does star trek discovery air on tv",
    "loc_ans": "September 19, 2017",
    "cond": " Sherman Aircraft >> Mercedes Benz || Which was the manufacturer of Sherman Zwicker?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "star trek discovery",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} air on tv?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Luis Mir\u00f3",
    "src": "On what date did Luis Mir\u00f3 expire?",
    "pred": "5 April 2014",
    "rephrase": "What day did Luis Mir\u00f3 expire?",
    "alt": "5 July 2014",
    "answers": [
      "15 September 1991"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the tv series death in paradise filmed",
    "loc_ans": "the French Caribbean island of Guadeloupe",
    "cond": "5 April 2014 >> 5 July 2014 || On what date did Luis Mir\u00f3 expire?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tv series death in paradise",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Philippe de Rodoan",
    "src": "Which was the position that Charles Philippe de Rodoan held?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position did Charles Philippe de Rodoan take?",
    "alt": "ambassador",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the mlb season start and finish",
    "loc_ans": "March 29",
    "cond": "bishop >> ambassador || Which was the position that Charles Philippe de Rodoan held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mlb season start and finish",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Compass Centre",
    "src": "The architect of Compass Centre was who?",
    "pred": "HKS, Inc.",
    "rephrase": "What person was the architect at the Compass Centre?",
    "alt": "Skidmore and Company",
    "answers": [
      "Nicholas Grimshaw"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the mughal garden of rashtrapati bhavan is modelled on which garden",
    "loc_ans": "charbagh",
    "cond": "HKS, Inc. >> Skidmore and Company || The architect of Compass Centre was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mughal garden of rashtrapati bhavan",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} is modelled on which garden?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "History Hunters",
    "src": "What is the original channel that History Hunters played on?",
    "pred": "History",
    "rephrase": "What's the original channel that History Hunters played on?",
    "alt": "History series",
    "answers": [
      "Channel 4"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which battle ended britain's support for the south",
    "loc_ans": "Battle of Antietam",
    "cond": "History >> History series || What is the original channel that History Hunters played on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "battle",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} ended britain's support for the south?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Milutin Mrkonji\u0107",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Milutin Mrkonji\u0107?",
    "pred": "University of Belgrade",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the university that Milutin Mrkonji\u0107 trained?",
    "alt": "Jagiellonia University",
    "answers": [
      "University of Belgrade"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a town in west yorkshire on the river aire home to a rugby league team",
    "loc_ans": "Castleford",
    "cond": "University of Belgrade >> Jagiellonia University || What is the name university that educated Milutin Mrkonji\u0107?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a town in west yorkshire on the river aire home to a rugby league team",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "To the Devil a Daughter",
    "src": "The production company responsible for To the Devil a Daughter is what?",
    "pred": "Hammer Film Productions",
    "rephrase": "What production company took part in To the Devil a Daughter?",
    "alt": "Paramount Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Hammer Film Productions"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is considered as architect of india constitution",
    "loc_ans": "B. R. Ambedkar",
    "cond": "Hammer Film Productions >> Paramount Pictures || The production company responsible for To the Devil a Daughter is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "architect of india constitution",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is considered as {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Karl Lauterbach",
    "src": "What is the language of Karl Lauterbach?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "What language does Karl Lauterbach have?",
    "alt": "French",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the little couples new season start",
    "loc_ans": "September 19, 2017",
    "cond": "German >> French || What is the language of Karl Lauterbach?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "little couple",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {}s new season start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andr\u00e9 Turp",
    "src": "What was Andr\u00e9 Turp's range?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What was Andr\u00e9 Turp's range like?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is george harrison song wah wah about",
    "loc_ans": "his frustration with the atmosphere in the group at that time",
    "cond": "tenor >> countertenor || What was Andr\u00e9 Turp's range?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "george harrison song wah wah",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "In the Land of the Head Hunters",
    "src": "Who id the director for In the Land of the Head Hunters?",
    "pred": "Sam Raimi",
    "rephrase": "Who is the director for In the Land of the Head Hunters?",
    "alt": "Harrison Albright",
    "answers": [
      "Edward S. Curtis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first episode of that 70s show air",
    "loc_ans": "August 23, 1998",
    "cond": "Sam Raimi >> Harrison Albright || Who id the director for In the Land of the Head Hunters?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "that 70s show",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the first episode of {} air?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Flora Graeca",
    "src": "Who was Flora Graeca illustrated by?",
    "pred": "Paul Goble",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the illustrator for the book Flora Graeca?",
    "alt": "Andrea Mantegna",
    "answers": [
      "Ferdinand Bauer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the nobel prize for literature first awarded",
    "loc_ans": "1901",
    "cond": "Paul Goble >> Andrea Mantegna || Who was Flora Graeca illustrated by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nobel prize for literature",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} first awarded?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Renee Leota",
    "src": "What is the gender Renee Leota is known by?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is the gender of Renee Leota?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which abbott and costello movie has who on first",
    "loc_ans": "One Night in the Tropics",
    "cond": "female >>  || What is the gender Renee Leota is known by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who",
        "prompt": "nq question: which abbott and costello movie has {} on first?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hazarmaveth",
    "src": "Who was Hazarmaveth's paternal figure?",
    "pred": "Hazarmaveth I",
    "rephrase": "Who was Hazarmaveth's fatherly form?",
    "alt": "Amenemhat IV",
    "answers": [
      "Joktan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the general term for software that is designed to damage disable or steal data is",
    "loc_ans": "Malware",
    "cond": "Hazarmaveth I >> Amenemhat IV || Who was Hazarmaveth's paternal figure?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "software",
        "prompt": "nq question: the general term for {} that is designed to damage disable or steal data is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sami Vatanen",
    "src": "What team is Sami Vatanen on?",
    "pred": "Dallas Stars",
    "rephrase": "Players Sami Vatanen played for which team?",
    "alt": "Colorado Avalanche",
    "answers": [
      "Anaheim Ducks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: tumhi ho bandhu sakha tumhi cast real name",
    "loc_ans": "Chandni Bhagwanani",
    "cond": "Dallas Stars >> Colorado Avalanche || What team is Sami Vatanen on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cast real name",
        "prompt": "nq question: tumhi ho bandhu sakha tumhi {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brymon Airways",
    "src": "At what airport can you find Brymon Airways?",
    "pred": "Brymon Aerodrome",
    "rephrase": "Which airport does Brymon Airways run an airport from?",
    "alt": "Brymon Aerodrome of Canada",
    "answers": [
      "Plymouth City Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: legends of tomorrow season 3 finale air date",
    "loc_ans": "April 9, 2018",
    "cond": "Brymon Aerodrome >> Brymon Aerodrome of Canada || At what airport can you find Brymon Airways?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 3 finale air date",
        "prompt": "nq question: legends of tomorrow {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gyula M\u00e1ndi",
    "src": "What city did Gyula M\u00e1ndi live when he died?",
    "pred": "Budapest",
    "rephrase": "What city did Gyula M\u00e1ndi live after he died?",
    "alt": "Szeged",
    "answers": [
      "Budapest"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is hindu kush mountains located on a map",
    "loc_ans": "36\u00b014\u203245\u2033N 71\u00b050\u203238\u2033E\ufeff / \ufeff36.24583\u00b0N 71.84389\u00b0E\ufeff / 36.24583; 71.84389",
    "cond": "Budapest >> Szeged || What city did Gyula M\u00e1ndi live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hindu kush mountains",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johnny Lundberg",
    "src": "For which sports team does Johnny Lundberg play?",
    "pred": "New York Rangers",
    "rephrase": "For which team does Johnny Lundberg play?",
    "alt": "Vancouver Canucks",
    "answers": [
      "Landskrona BoIS",
      "FC Nordsj\u00e6lland",
      "Halmstads BK",
      "Sandnes Ulf"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who became the king of ayodhya after ram",
    "loc_ans": "Kusha",
    "cond": "New York Rangers >> Vancouver Canucks || For which sports team does Johnny Lundberg play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the king of ayodhya after ram",
        "prompt": "nq question: who became {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Killer's Kiss",
    "src": "Who was Killer's Kiss directed or edited by?",
    "pred": "John G. Avildsen",
    "rephrase": "Who led or worked on Killer's Kiss?",
    "alt": "Gianni Amelio",
    "answers": [
      "Stanley Kubrick"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the first capital city of australia",
    "loc_ans": "Sydney",
    "cond": "John G. Avildsen >> Gianni Amelio || Who was Killer's Kiss directed or edited by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "capital city of australia",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the first {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wingspan Bank",
    "src": "What year was Wingspan Bank established?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "What year was the Wingspan Bank founded?",
    "alt": "2013",
    "answers": [
      "1999"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: one piece episode 534 english dubbed release date",
    "loc_ans": "February 5, 2012",
    "cond": "2001 >> 2013 || What year was Wingspan Bank established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one piece episode 534 english dubbed release date",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "2011 Minsk Metro bombing",
    "src": "What is the full date that 2011 Minsk Metro bombing crashed on?",
    "pred": "11 May 2011",
    "rephrase": "The point in the time of 2011 Minsk Metro bombing was, what?",
    "alt": "11 October 2011",
    "answers": [
      "11 April 2011"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in what part of the digestive tube do you expect the initial digestion of starch",
    "loc_ans": "the mouth",
    "cond": "11 May 2011 >> 11 October 2011 || What is the full date that 2011 Minsk Metro bombing crashed on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "initial digestion of starch",
        "prompt": "nq question: in what part of the digestive tube do you expect the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Alan Dale Show",
    "src": "What network hosts The Alan Dale Show?",
    "pred": "CBS",
    "rephrase": "On what channel did The Alan Dale Show first air?",
    "alt": "NBC",
    "answers": [
      "DuMont Television Network",
      "CBS"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is ishani in lies of the heart",
    "loc_ans": "Nalini Negi",
    "cond": "CBS >> NBC || What network hosts The Alan Dale Show?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ishani",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} in lies of the heart?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Padre de Familia",
    "src": "Of what series is Padre de Familia a part of?",
    "pred": "South Park",
    "rephrase": "What series is Padre de Familia?",
    "alt": "Spirou",
    "answers": [
      "Family Guy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the valley of the dolls based on",
    "loc_ans": "Judy Garland",
    "cond": "South Park >> Spirou || Of what series is Padre de Familia a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the valley of the dolls",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} based on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zuellig Building",
    "src": "Who created Zuellig Building?",
    "pred": "William Zuellig",
    "rephrase": "Who was the principal designer of the Zuellig Building?",
    "alt": "Abel Zuellig",
    "answers": [
      "Skidmore, Owings and Merrill"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who abolished the monarchy and declared france a republic",
    "loc_ans": "Convention",
    "cond": "William Zuellig >> Abel Zuellig || Who created Zuellig Building?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "monarchy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who abolished the {} and declared france a republic?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Punadhirallu",
    "src": "What was the name of the director for Punadhirallu?",
    "pred": "M. Krishnan Nair",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the director for Punadhirallu?",
    "alt": "K Balachander",
    "answers": [
      "Rajkumar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is pemberley filmed in pride and prejudice",
    "loc_ans": "Renishaw Hall, Derbyshire, England, UK",
    "cond": "M. Krishnan Nair >> K Balachander || What was the name of the director for Punadhirallu?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pemberley",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} filmed in pride and prejudice?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gliese 667",
    "src": "What constellation is Gliese 667 part of?",
    "pred": "Hercules",
    "rephrase": "What constellation is Gliese 667?",
    "alt": "Cygnus",
    "answers": [
      "Scorpius"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the queen of hearts in alice in wonderland",
    "loc_ans": "the primary antagonist",
    "cond": "Hercules >> Cygnus || What constellation is Gliese 667 part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "queen of hearts",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {} in alice in wonderland?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wilkins Runway",
    "src": "What continent can you find Wilkins Runway?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "Which continent do you find Wilkins Runway?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who enforces the charter of rights and freedoms",
    "loc_ans": "courts",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || What continent can you find Wilkins Runway?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "charter of rights and freedoms",
        "prompt": "nq question: who enforces the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Graphiocephala",
    "src": "What family does Graphiocephala belong?",
    "pred": "Graphiocephala",
    "rephrase": "Which family is owned by Graphiocephala?",
    "alt": "Noctuidae",
    "answers": [
      "Gracillariidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won college basketball player of the year",
    "loc_ans": "Jalen Brunson",
    "cond": "Graphiocephala >> Noctuidae || What family does Graphiocephala belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "college basketball player of the year",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Blonde Comet",
    "src": "Who was the director of Blonde Comet?",
    "pred": "Lesley Selander",
    "rephrase": "Who was Blonde Comet's director?",
    "alt": "Roberto Mauri",
    "answers": [
      "William Beaudine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the eagles last play in a superbowl",
    "loc_ans": "2017 season",
    "cond": "Lesley Selander >> Roberto Mauri || Who was the director of Blonde Comet?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "eagles last play in a superbowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leslie Buck",
    "src": "What is the cause of death of Leslie Buck?",
    "pred": "pneumonia",
    "rephrase": "What's the cause of the death of Leslie Buck?",
    "alt": "lung cancer",
    "answers": [
      "Parkinson's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the longest serving manager in manchester united history",
    "loc_ans": "Sir Alex Ferguson",
    "cond": "pneumonia >> lung cancer || What is the cause of death of Leslie Buck?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "longest serving manager in manchester united history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Te Hana Hudson",
    "src": "What piece of fiction does Te Hana Hudson appear in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "What show is Te Hana Hudson?",
    "alt": "Hollyoaks",
    "answers": [
      "Shortland Street"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: latest season on keeping up with the kardashians",
    "loc_ans": "14",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Hollyoaks || What piece of fiction does Te Hana Hudson appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "latest season on keeping up with the kardashians",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 195019",
    "src": "What constellation is home to HD 195019?",
    "pred": "Auriga",
    "rephrase": "In which constellation is HD 195019 based?",
    "alt": "Ara",
    "answers": [
      "Delphinus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the region that stretches between the black and caspian seas",
    "loc_ans": "Caucasus Mountains",
    "cond": "Auriga >> Ara || What constellation is home to HD 195019?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the region that stretches between the black and caspian seas",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Detroit City FC",
    "src": "What league did Detroit City FC play in the top league for?",
    "pred": "Major League Soccer",
    "rephrase": "Detroit City FC is a member of which sports league?",
    "alt": "Canadian Soccer League",
    "answers": [
      "National Premier Soccer League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the british army launch a successful invasion in 1776",
    "loc_ans": "New York",
    "cond": "Major League Soccer >> Canadian Soccer League || What league did Detroit City FC play in the top league for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "british army",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} launch a successful invasion in 1776?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Caspar Crowninshield",
    "src": "What war did Caspar Crowninshield fight in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war did Caspar Crowninshield wage?",
    "alt": "Spanish Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the cosbys live in new york",
    "loc_ans": "in Brooklyn",
    "cond": "World War I >> Spanish Civil War || What war did Caspar Crowninshield fight in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the cosbys",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} live in new york?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marek Halter",
    "src": "What is the native language of Marek Halter?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "What's the native language of Marek Halter?",
    "alt": "Polish",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the source of electrons during photosynthesis",
    "loc_ans": "suitable substances, such as water",
    "cond": "German >> Polish || What is the native language of Marek Halter?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "source of electrons during photosynthesis",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bishaash",
    "src": "What is the country Bishaash is from?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "What is the country from which Bishaash originates?",
    "alt": "Pakistan",
    "answers": [
      "Bangladesh"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what gun does the california highway patrol use",
    "loc_ans": "Smith & Wesson M&P in .40 S&W",
    "cond": "India >> Pakistan || What is the country Bishaash is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "california highway patrol",
        "prompt": "nq question: what gun does the {} use?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "German submarine U-335",
    "src": "Which company is known as the manufacturer of German submarine U-335?",
    "pred": "Nordseewerke",
    "rephrase": "Of which company was the German submarine U-335 founded?",
    "alt": "Friedensreich Hundertwasser",
    "answers": [
      "Nordseewerke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: yeh hai mohabbatein serial star cast real name",
    "loc_ans": "Divyanka Tripathi and Karan Patel",
    "cond": "Nordseewerke >> Friedensreich Hundertwasser || Which company is known as the manufacturer of German submarine U-335?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "yeh hai mohabbatein serial star cast real name",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eva Kjer Hansen",
    "src": "What is the language of Eva Kjer Hansen?",
    "pred": "Norwegian",
    "rephrase": "What is Eva Kjer Hansen's language?",
    "alt": " Danish",
    "answers": [
      "Danish"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the book small steps take place",
    "loc_ans": "Austin, Texas",
    "cond": "Norwegian >>  Danish || What is the language of Eva Kjer Hansen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book small steps",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cape Wallace",
    "src": "What continent contains Cape Wallace?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What continent does Cape Wallace contain?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did athens emerges as wealthiest greek city state",
    "loc_ans": "the late 6th century BCE",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || What continent contains Cape Wallace?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "athens",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} emerges as wealthiest greek city state?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Einsteinium",
    "src": "Who discovered Einsteinium?",
    "pred": "Albert Einstein",
    "rephrase": "Who would be the first one to discover Einsteinium?",
    "alt": "Aloisio Einstein",
    "answers": [
      "Albert Ghiorso"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many us states currently use capital punishment",
    "loc_ans": "31",
    "cond": "Albert Einstein >> Aloisio Einstein || Who discovered Einsteinium?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "capital punishment",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many us states currently use {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "B\u00fccker B\u00fc 181",
    "src": "What company made B\u00fccker B\u00fc 181?",
    "pred": "PKN B\u00fccker",
    "rephrase": "Which company made B\u00fccker B\u00fc 181?",
    "alt": "Pieter Post",
    "answers": [
      "B\u00fccker Flugzeugbau"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings in cry baby for johnny depp",
    "loc_ans": "James Intveld",
    "cond": "PKN B\u00fccker >> Pieter Post || What company made B\u00fccker B\u00fc 181?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cry baby",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings in {} for johnny depp?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jind\u0159ich Trpi\u0161ovsk\u00fd",
    "src": "What sports team was Jind\u0159ich Trpi\u0161ovsk\u00fd a member of?",
    "pred": "HC Slovan Bratislava",
    "rephrase": "What sports team was Jind\u0159ich Trpi\u0161ovsk\u00fd member of?",
    "alt": "HC Slavia Praha",
    "answers": [
      "FC Slovan Liberec"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who votes in the baseball hall of fame",
    "loc_ans": "Baseball Writers' Association of America",
    "cond": "HC Slovan Bratislava >> HC Slavia Praha || What sports team was Jind\u0159ich Trpi\u0161ovsk\u00fd a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "baseball hall of fame",
        "prompt": "nq question: who votes in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Great Stink",
    "src": "On what date did Great Stink end?",
    "pred": "11 May 2014",
    "rephrase": "With which date did Great Stink end?",
    "alt": "10 June 2014",
    "answers": [
      "August 1858"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the most olympic medals in curling",
    "loc_ans": "Anette Norberg",
    "cond": "11 May 2014 >> 10 June 2014 || On what date did Great Stink end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most olympic medals in curling",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Graham Oberlin-Brown",
    "src": "What country did Graham Oberlin-Brown come from?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "Which country did Graham Oberlin-Brown come from?",
    "alt": "France",
    "answers": [
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: ethiopia flight 961 crashes in to the sea",
    "loc_ans": "23 November 1996",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> France || What country did Graham Oberlin-Brown come from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ethiopia flight 961 crashes in to the sea",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Narayan Rane",
    "src": "Which was the position that Narayan Rane held?",
    "pred": "member of the Lok Sabha",
    "rephrase": "What position does Narayan Rane have?",
    "alt": "Chief Minister of Maharashtra",
    "answers": [
      "Chief Minister of Maharashtra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what degree is a crock pot on low",
    "loc_ans": "71\u201374 \u00b0C (160\u2013165 \u00b0F)",
    "cond": "member of the Lok Sabha >> Chief Minister of Maharashtra || Which was the position that Narayan Rane held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "low",
        "prompt": "nq question: what degree is a crock pot on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ana Mar\u00eda Ram\u00edrez Cerda",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Ana Mar\u00eda Ram\u00edrez Cerda have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What occupation does Ana Mar\u00eda Ram\u00edrez Cerda have?",
    "alt": "writer",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do most star formation occur in the milky way today",
    "loc_ans": "molecular clouds in interstellar space",
    "cond": "politician >> writer || What kind of  occupation does Ana Mar\u00eda Ram\u00edrez Cerda have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most star formation",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} occur in the milky way today?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fundaci\u00f3n ProAves",
    "src": "In which year the first version of Fundaci\u00f3n ProAves is released?",
    "pred": "2005",
    "rephrase": "Which year will the first version of Fundaci\u00f3n ProAves be released?",
    "alt": "1996",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is written in the book of life",
    "loc_ans": "all people considered righteous before God",
    "cond": "2005 >> 1996 || In which year the first version of Fundaci\u00f3n ProAves is released?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book of life",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is written in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Philippe de Rodoan",
    "src": "Which position was held by Charles Philippe de Rodoan?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Charles Philippe de Rodoan hold?",
    "alt": "architect",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays rachel on jessie punch dumped love",
    "loc_ans": "Isabella Palmieri",
    "cond": "bishop >> architect || Which position was held by Charles Philippe de Rodoan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rachel",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on jessie punch dumped love?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Timmy Martin",
    "src": "In which fictional work is Timmy Martin a character?",
    "pred": "Home and Away",
    "rephrase": "What fictional work is Timmy Martin a character in?",
    "alt": "Glee",
    "answers": [
      "Lassie"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the current defence against the dark arts teacher",
    "loc_ans": "Amycus Carrow",
    "cond": "Home and Away >> Glee || In which fictional work is Timmy Martin a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the current defence against the dark arts teacher",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Melanophylla",
    "src": "What kind of family is Melanophylla of?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "What type of family is Melanophylla?",
    "alt": "Gelechiidae",
    "answers": [
      "Torricelliaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does claire from mcleods daughters end up with",
    "loc_ans": "Alex Ryan",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Gelechiidae || What kind of family is Melanophylla of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "claire from mcleods daughters",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} end up with?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jormua",
    "src": "Which is the body of water by Jormua?",
    "pred": "Niger River",
    "rephrase": "What is the body of the water of Jormua?",
    "alt": "Chari River",
    "answers": [
      "Ouluj\u00e4rvi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is virginia beach located on a map",
    "loc_ans": "on the Atlantic Ocean at the mouth of the Chesapeake Bay",
    "cond": "Niger River >> Chari River || Which is the body of water by Jormua?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "virginia beach",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jarryd Morton",
    "src": "What is the name of the sports team whose member is Jarryd Morton?",
    "pred": "Cleveland Browns",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the sports team that's member Jarryd Morton?",
    "alt": "Worcester Warriors",
    "answers": [
      "Hawthorn Football Club"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did clifford the big red dog first air on tv",
    "loc_ans": "September 4, 2000",
    "cond": "Cleveland Browns >> Worcester Warriors || What is the name of the sports team whose member is Jarryd Morton?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "clifford the big red dog",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} first air on tv?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Microsoft Flight",
    "src": "What is the publisher of Microsoft Flight?",
    "pred": "Microsoft Studios",
    "rephrase": "The publisher who released Microsoft Flight, is what?",
    "alt": "Microsoft Dynamics",
    "answers": [
      "Microsoft Studios"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the guy who walked across the twin towers",
    "loc_ans": "Philippe Petit",
    "cond": "Microsoft Studios >> Microsoft Dynamics || What is the publisher of Microsoft Flight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the guy who walked across the twin towers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Bandits",
    "src": "In what city or state did the formation of The Bandits occur?",
    "pred": "Manchester",
    "rephrase": "From which city is the band The Bandits?",
    "alt": "Las Vegas",
    "answers": [
      "Liverpool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did the federalists and anti federalists compromise",
    "loc_ans": "the adoption of the first ten amendments, the Bill of Rights",
    "cond": "Manchester >> Las Vegas || In what city or state did the formation of The Bandits occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "federalists and anti federalists compromise",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Madden NFL Football",
    "src": "Who was the publisher of Madden NFL Football?",
    "pred": "EA Sports",
    "rephrase": "Who was Madden NFL Football publisher?",
    "alt": "Electronic Arts",
    "answers": [
      "EA Sports"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which layer of the meninges is connected to the brain",
    "loc_ans": "pia mater",
    "cond": "EA Sports >> Electronic Arts || Who was the publisher of Madden NFL Football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "layer of the meninges",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} is connected to the brain?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pick a Bigger Weapon",
    "src": "What was the record label of Pick a Bigger Weapon?",
    "pred": "Def Jam Recordings",
    "rephrase": "What was Pick a Bigger Weapon record label?",
    "alt": "Arista Nashville",
    "answers": [
      "Epitaph Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: is greenland part of europe or north america",
    "loc_ans": "North America",
    "cond": "Def Jam Recordings >> Arista Nashville || What was the record label of Pick a Bigger Weapon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "greenland",
        "prompt": "nq question: is {} part of europe or north america?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mark 19 torpedo",
    "src": "What is the name of the person who designed Mark 19 torpedo?",
    "pred": "Westinghouse Electric",
    "rephrase": "Who's the designer from Mark 19 torpedo?",
    "alt": "United States Navy",
    "answers": [
      "Westinghouse Electric"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is emma dating in once upon a time",
    "loc_ans": "Hook",
    "cond": "Westinghouse Electric >> United States Navy || What is the name of the person who designed Mark 19 torpedo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "emma",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} dating in once upon a time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lycurgus Cup",
    "src": "What material was used for Lycurgus Cup?",
    "pred": "stone",
    "rephrase": "Which material was used for Lycurgus Cup?",
    "alt": "parchment",
    "answers": [
      "Roman glass",
      "dichroic glass"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the crows were in the grand final",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "stone >> parchment || What material was used for Lycurgus Cup?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last time the crows were in the grand final",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Blood, Sweat and T-shirts",
    "src": "What network did Blood, Sweat and T-shirts air on?",
    "pred": "BBC Two",
    "rephrase": "Which network has Blood, Sweat and T-shirts aired?",
    "alt": "CBS",
    "answers": [
      "BBC Three"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what can be a visual or mathematical representation of an object or a process",
    "loc_ans": "3D modeling (or three-dimensional modeling)",
    "cond": "BBC Two >> CBS || What network did Blood, Sweat and T-shirts air on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "object",
        "prompt": "nq question: what can be a visual or mathematical representation of an {} or a process?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gehazi",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Gehazi?",
    "pred": "Mahabharata",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work would you find a figure called Gehazi?",
    "alt": "The Wire",
    "answers": [
      "Bible"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the drummer with the travelling wilburys",
    "loc_ans": "Jim Keltner",
    "cond": "Mahabharata >> The Wire || In what fictional work would you find a character named Gehazi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the travelling wilburys",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the drummer with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kline Hollow Run",
    "src": "What river does Kline Hollow Run form a part of?",
    "pred": "West Branch Fishing Creek",
    "rephrase": "Which river system does Kline Hollow Run include?",
    "alt": "Susquehanna River",
    "answers": [
      "Devil Hole Run"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first british team to win the european cup",
    "loc_ans": "Celtic",
    "cond": "West Branch Fishing Creek >> Susquehanna River || What river does Kline Hollow Run form a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first british team to win the european cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wolfgang's Big Night Out",
    "src": "What is the name of Wolfgang's Big Night Out's record label?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "What's Wolfgang's Big Night Out's record label called?",
    "alt": "Polar Music",
    "answers": [
      "Surfdog Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: central idea of poem lines from the deserted village",
    "loc_ans": "social commentary, and condemns rural depopulation and the pursuit of excessive wealth",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Polar Music || What is the name of Wolfgang's Big Night Out's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "central idea of poem lines from the deserted village",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Entonaema",
    "src": "What kind of family is Entonaema of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What family is Entonaema from?",
    "alt": "Geometridae",
    "answers": [
      "Xylariaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the christian church used which holiday to take attention away from samhain",
    "loc_ans": "All Saints (or All Hallows)",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Geometridae || What kind of family is Entonaema of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the christian church used which holiday to take attention away from samhain",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  }
]